<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BackstoryTranslations>
	<ColonySettler53>
		<title>Telepes</title>
		<titleShort>Telepes</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] telepes volt egy gyarmatosított világon.

Az ilyen élethez kicsit mindenhez érteni kell, ami kétkezi munka.</desc>
	</ColonySettler53>
	<MedievalFarmOaf58>
		<title>Farm mamlasza</title>
		<titleShort>Mamlasz</titleShort>
		<desc>Szántás, kapálás, ökrök irányítása, talicskázás. Árokásás, vetés, aratás előrejelzése.

Feudális szintű földművesek nem kapnak hagyományos oktatást, de sokat tudnak az egyszerű eszközökkel végzett növénytermesztésről. Aki ilyen életet élt, lényegében képtelen bármilyen intellektuális munkában vagy technológiát igénylő aktivitásban részt venni.</desc>
	</MedievalFarmOaf58>
	<MedievalLord57>
		<title>Feudális földesúr</title>
		<titleShort>Nemes</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy nem iparosított bolygón volt földesúr. Bálokra járt, alattvalóit igazgatta, kicsit még kardozni is megtanult.

Puha kezei sohasem fogtak szerszámot. A kétkezi munkát alantasnak tartja és nem is végzi.</desc>
	</MedievalLord57>
	<UrbworldEntrepreneur14>
		<title>Urbvilági mágnás</title>
		<titleShort>Mágnás</titleShort>
		<desc>Az urbvilágokon a legtöbben sanyarú életet élnek. De a vállalatokat is kell valakinek irányítani.

[PAWN_nameDef] kitanulta a szakmát: mutyizás és műszaki analízis. Egy igazi szocio-intellektuális gép.</desc>
	</UrbworldEntrepreneur14>
	<DeepSpaceMiner3>
		<title>Űrbányász</title>
		<titleShort>Bányász</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] az aszteroida bányászat mocskos, izzadságos munkáját végezte egy űrhajón. Ipari képzettségét napi szinten használta és kocsmai verekedésekben is megállta a helyét.</desc>
	</DeepSpaceMiner3>
	<NavyScientist46>
		<title>Haditengerészeti tudós</title>
		<titleShort>Tudós</titleShort>
		<desc>A csillagközi háborúkat a technológia nyeri meg, ezért a birodalmi flotta mindig is a kutatás élvonalát jelentette. Sőt, ők jutottak hozzá először Felemelkedettek ereklyéihez is, mivel ezek az űrben találhatóak.

[PAWN_nameDef] a flotta egy laborjában dolgozott.</desc>
	</NavyScientist46>
	<MilitaryCommissar49>
		<title>Hadsereg felügyelője</title>
		<titleShort>Felügyelő</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] mesterkém volt a Birodalmi Hadsereg egy zászlóaljánál. Ő felelt érte, hogy az emberei lojálisak legyenek, és sose hátráljanak meg, kivéve, ha ez a parancs. Nem volt túl népszerű, de jól felismerte, ha valaki nem volt vele őszinte.</desc>
	</MilitaryCommissar49>
	<MidworldChef92>
		<title>Séf</title>
		<titleShort>Séf</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] puccos éttermet vezetett egy fejlett világban. Híres volt kreatív kulináris specialitásairól, és hírhedten megvetette a kukták munkáját.</desc>
	</MidworldChef92>
	<MedievalMinstrel95>
		<title>Vándorénekes</title>
		<titleShort>Vándorénekes</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] a feudális világ utazó kobzosa volt.

Mindig dalokat énekelve és történeteket mesélve töltötte idejét, de képes volt megvédeni magát az út veszélyeitől is. Érdekes módon mindig köddé tudott válni, ha valami nehéz fizikai munkát kellett volna végezni.</desc>
	</MedievalMinstrel95>
	<Housemate8>
		<title>Háztartásbeli</title>
		<titleShort>Háztartásbeli</titleShort>
		<desc>Felnőttként [PAWN_nameDef] tisztán tartotta a házat és gondoskodott a gyerekekről, miközben házastársa dolgozott.</desc>
	</Housemate8>
	<GlitterworldEmpath26>
		<title>Szupervilági empata</title>
		<titleShort>Empata</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] elképesztő érzékkel alakít ki emberi kapcsolatokat és simít el konfliktusokat. Kiválasztották empata képzésre. A kiképzés felerősítette természetes adottságait, de képtelenné vált másoknak ártani.</desc>
	</GlitterworldEmpath26>
	<MedievalDoctor40>
		<title>Középkori doktor</title>
		<titleShort>Kuruzsló</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy középkori világon dolgozott doktorként. Szilárdan hiszi, hogy a legtöbb betegség gyógyítható egy kis véreztetéssel.

Mesteri aneszteziológus is volt, kidolgozott egy speciális technikát, mely fejre mért kemény ütésen alapult.</desc>
	</MedievalDoctor40>
	<Inventor6>
		<title>Feltaláló</title>
		<titleShort>Feltaláló</titleShort>
		<desc>Bolygóján [PAWN_nameDef] mérsékelten sikeres feltaláló volt. Pár kisebb találmányt köszönhettek neki.</desc>
	</Inventor6>
	<Teacher20>
		<title>Tanár</title>
		<titleShort>Tanár</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] bölcsészként tanított egy általános iskolában. Széleskörű tudással rendelkezett és tanítványai szerették.</desc>
	</Teacher20>
	<JoywireArtist8>
		<title>Örömchip készítő</title>
		<titleShort>Örömchipes</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy urbvilág laborjában fejlesztett korszerű örömchip szoftvereket, a felhasználók gyönyörének maximalizálására.

Amikor a kormány keményen lekorlátozta az örömchipek gyártását, a feketepiacon kezdte értékesíteni a portékát.</desc>
	</JoywireArtist8>
	<ConceptualArtist39>
		<title>Konceptuális művész</title>
		<titleShort>Művész</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] jól ismert volt bolygója művész köreiben egyedi és kreatív konceptuális alkotásairól.

Senki nem tudta pontosan, hogy mit is szeretne kifejezni, de a gyűjtők nagy becsben tartották munkáit.</desc>
	</ConceptualArtist39>
	<GlitterworldSurgeon15>
		<title>Szupervilági sebész</title>
		<titleShort>Sebész</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] sebészként dolgozott egy olyan világon, ahol az emberi szenvedés és betegség szinte ismeretlen.

Munkája leginkább kreatív és bonyolult szépészeti beavatkozásokból állt. Jól ismeri az emberi anatómiát, de sosem kellett daganatot vagy golyót eltávolítania.</desc>
	</GlitterworldSurgeon15>
	<LudditeRebel43>
		<title>Luddita lázadó</title>
		<titleShort>Luddita</titleShort>
		<desc>Amikor világa lakóinak többsége úgy döntött, hogy feladja egyéniségét és biológiai ember mivoltát, hogy egy online tudat részévé váljon, [PAWN_nameDef] inkább egy lázadó csoporthoz csatlakozott, akik minden technológiáról lemondtak.</desc>
	</LudditeRebel43>
	<Bartender55>
		<title>Csapos</title>
		<titleShort>Csapos</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] csaposként dolgozott egy nyomorúságos űrállomáson. A munka egy rész mixelésből, egy rész diplomáciából és egy rész verekedésből állt.</desc>
	</Bartender55>
	<HiveworldDrone0>
		<title>Kaptárvilági drón</title>
		<titleShort>Drón</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] agyatlan építőmunkásként dolgozott egy kaptárvilági civilizációban. Bár mostanra felszabadult a brutális szociális kísérletek alól, kreatív munkára alkalmatlan és vezetői képességgel sem rendelkezik.</desc>
	</HiveworldDrone0>
	<Evangelist39>
		<title>Evangélista</title>
		<titleShort>Evangélista</titleShort>
		<desc>21. születésnapján [PAWN_nameDef] vallási megvilágosodáson esett át. Úgy döntött, hogy élete hátralevő részében istene igéjét, kultúrája szépségét és fura orvosi praktikáit hirdeti.</desc>
	</Evangelist39>
	<CaveworldIlluminator23>
		<title>Barlangi látnok</title>
		<titleShort>látnok</titleShort>
		<desc>A barlanglakók bölcsként tisztelik azokat, akik olyan erős látnoki erővel rendelkeznek, mint [PAWN_nameDef]. Ő jelöli ki a helyeket világító gombával, ahol bányászni érdemes és figyelmeztet a közelgő veszélyekre.</desc>
	</CaveworldIlluminator23>
	<Herbalist54>
		<title>Füvesember</title>
		<titleShort>Füvesember</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] az erdőben élt egy falu közelében. Sokan féltek tőle, de a betegek hozzá fordultak kenőcsökért és gyógyírekért, amiket a kertjében termesztett gyógynövényekből készített. Szívesen segített nekik — ha megfizették.</desc>
	</Herbalist54>
	<CivilServant2>
		<title>Tisztviselő</title>
		<titleShort>Tisztviselő</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] alacsony beosztású tisztviselője volt egy haldokló kormány bürokráciájának. Legjobban a komplikált papírmunkához és az irodai hatalmi játszmákhoz ért.</desc>
	</CivilServant2>
	<AsceticPriest11>
		<title>Aszkéta pap</title>
		<titleShort>Pap</titleShort>
		<desc>Miután némasági fogadalmat tett, [PAWN_nameDef] csatlakozott egy kolostorhoz egy eldugott bolygón, hogy élete hátralevő részét nyugalomban töltse.

Örömmel gondozta a kolostor kertjét és sajtot is készített a pincében.</desc>
	</AsceticPriest11>
	<EscapedConvict10>
		<title>Szökevény</title>
		<titleShort>Szökevény</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] tagadja, hogy bármi köze lett volna azokhoz a bűntényekhez, amik miatt börtönbe vetették egy brutális büntetés-végrehajtó kolónián. Alagúton keresztül szökött meg, amit maga ásott evőeszközeivel.</desc>
	</EscapedConvict10>
	<StarshipJanitor33>
		<title>Csillaghajó gondnok</title>
		<titleShort>Gondnok</titleShort>
		<desc>Míg más utasok hibernálóban töltik a csillagközi utazások nagy részét, [PAWN_nameDef] fel kellett keljen időről-időre, hogy ellenőrizze a rendszereket, és beolajozza a mechanoidokat.</desc>
	</StarshipJanitor33>
	<Nurse53>
		<title>Ápolónő</title>
		<titleShort>Ápolónő</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy iparosodás-kori kórházban dolgozott, rutinmunkát végezve, mint pl. kötözés vagy láz mérés.

Sok dolga volt, de mindig szakított rá időt, hogy elbeszélgessen a betegekkel.</desc>
	</Nurse53>
	<HouseServant35>
		<title>Szolga</title>
		<titleShort>Szolga</titleShort>
		<desc>Fiatal felnőttként [PAWN_nameDef] el lett rabolva és gazdag arisztokratákhoz került, mint háziszolga.

Jól ismerte gazdája pincéit és konyháját, ám a szabadban sosem dolgozott.</desc>
	</HouseServant35>
	<Bodyguard26>
		<title>Testőr</title>
		<titleShort>Testőr</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy közepesen fejlett világon dolgozott, pénzért bárkit megvédett a bajtól. Sokféle harci technikát kitanult, kegyetlenségéről volt híres azokkal szemben, akik kikezdtek vele.</desc>
	</Bodyguard26>
	<Novelist28>
		<title>Író</title>
		<titleShort>Író</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy fejlett világon írt nagyon sikeres regényeket. Gondtalan életet élt, nappal a tollat forgatta, éjjel pedig bulizott. Egy napot sem töltött fizikai munkával soha.</desc>
	</Novelist28>
	<Mathematician6>
		<title>Matematikus</title>
		<titleShort>Matek prof</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] matematikai kutatásokat folytatott egy egyetemen.

Szabadidejének nagy részét lövöldözős játékokkal töltötte, játékostársai sokat ugratták szörnyű célzása miatt.</desc>
	</Mathematician6>
	<Paramedic45>
		<title>Mentős</title>
		<titleShort>Mentős</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] munkája keretében gyorsan kellett reagáljon vészhelyzetekre. Hozzá van szokva, hogy súlyos sérüléseket lásson el korlátozott eszközökkel.

Olyan sok lőtt sebet látott már el, hogy a fegyverek látványa is kényelmetlen számára.</desc>
	</Paramedic45>
	<Castaway57>
		<title>Számkivetett</title>
		<titleShort>Számkivetett</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy menetrendszerű csillagközi járat utasa volt. A hajója elpusztult, évekig élt egy lakatlan bolygón.</desc>
	</Castaway57>
	<Gardener31>
		<title>Kertész</title>
		<titleShort>Kertész</titleShort>
		<desc>Ipari világokon a pénz azok kezében összpontosul, akik a gyárakat birtokolják vagy az árut mozgatják. [PAWN_nameDef] egy ilyen gazdag családnál dolgozott a kertet gondozva, egy rabszolga csapat tagjaként.</desc>
	</Gardener31>
	<MafiaBoss17>
		<title>Maffiafőnök</title>
		<titleShort>Maffiafőnök</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy urbvilági bűnszervezet magas beosztású vezetője volt.

Tisztviselőket vesztegetett, fenntartotta pozícióját a ranglétrán, és begyűjtötte az elmaradó pénzeket - bármilyen eszközt felhasználva.</desc>
	</MafiaBoss17>
	<Torturer92>
		<title>Kínzó</title>
		<titleShort>Kínzó</titleShort>
		<desc>Egy középkori zsarnoknak dolgozva, [PAWN_nameDef] hamar hírnevet szerzett magának, mint a "meggyőzés" mestere. Ha egy fogoly lekerült a cellájába, nem maradtak titkai, viszont [PAWN_nameDef] mosolya örökre rémálmai része lett.</desc>
	</Torturer92>
	<ConstructionEngineer94>
		<title>Építőmérnök</title>
		<titleShort>Építőmérnök</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] építőmunkás volt egy közepesen fejlett világon. Egy csapatot vezetett, ami bármit felépített, irodától katedrálisig.

Sosem ért rá magának főzni a sok meló miatt, inkább gyors-éttermekben evett.</desc>
	</ConstructionEngineer94>
	<Blacksmith72>
		<title>Kovács</title>
		<titleShort>Kovács</titleShort>
		<desc>Egy középkori világ kovácsaként, [PAWN_nameDef] hírnevet szerzett minőségi munkájával. Elég jól forgatta is a fegyvereket, amiket készített.</desc>
	</Blacksmith72>
	<CharityWorker36>
		<title>Emberbarát</title>
		<titleShort>Emberbarát</titleShort>
		<desc>A fejlett világok kényelmet és biztonságot nyújtanak azoknak, akik elég szerencsések voltak, hogy oda szülessenek. [PAWN_nameDef] azonban nem tudta figyelmen kívül hagyni a környező bolygók szegénységét. Egész életét azzal töltötte, hogy adományokat gyűjtött és segített a rászorulóknak.</desc>
	</CharityWorker36>
	<Defector78>
		<title>Disszidens</title>
		<titleShort>Disszidens</titleShort>
		<desc>Fiatal felnőttként [PAWN_nameDef] úgy döntött, elhagyja az elnyomó diktatúrát, ahol élt. A disszidálást nem nézték el neki, ügynököket küldtek a nyakára.

Évekig csak menekült, saját maga látta el sebeit, így nem árulhatták el orvosok. A sok megpróbáltatástól megkeseredett és nem bízik senkiben.</desc>
	</Defector78>
	<FactoryWorker27>
		<title>Gyári munkás</title>
		<titleShort>Munkás</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egyszerű, szakértelmet nem igénylő munkákat végzett egy iparosodott világ gyárában. Munkája része volt a málhások és lovak gondozása, amik az árut szállították.</desc>
	</FactoryWorker27>
	<RanchOwner43>
		<title>Gazda</title>
		<titleShort>Gazda</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] saját farmján tenyésztett állatokat húsukért és gyapjújukért.

Sosem végezte a legegyszerűbb munkákat, mindig megfizetett valakit, hogy elvégezze azokat helyette.</desc>
	</RanchOwner43>
	<LowWageWorker7>
		<title>Segédmunkás</title>
		<titleShort>Segédmunkás</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] mindenféle alkalmi munkákat vállalt, hogy ellássa családját. Eközben kitanult egy sor kétkezi készséget.</desc>
	</LowWageWorker7>
	<Model99>
		<title>Modell</title>
		<titleShort>Modell</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] ruhákat és ékszereket reklámozott és róla mintáztak karaktereket virtuális valóságok számára.</desc>
	</Model99>
	<Taxonomist0>
		<title>Taxonómus</title>
		<titleShort>Taxonómus</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] sok csillagrendszert megjárt, az állat-, és növényvilágot rendszerezve. Remélte, hogy egyszer teljes katalógust készíthet.</desc>
	</Taxonomist0>
	<Geologist66>
		<title>Geológus</title>
		<titleShort>Geológus</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] bányászokkal és fúrókkal dolgozott együtt, ő azonosította a különböző sziklaformációkat.

A föld alatt töltött évek alatt kitanulta a fúrógépek és egyéb eszközök javítását és karbantartását.</desc>
	</Geologist66>
	<Sailor60>
		<title>Tengerész</title>
		<titleShort>Tengerész</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] az óceánokat járta, felfedezőútjain új állat és növényfajokat keresve és olykor kalózokkal harcolva. Annyira szerette a tengereket, hogy csak a legszükségesebb munkákat végezte szárazföldön, leginkább összegyűjtött kincseivel kereskedett.</desc>
	</Sailor60>
	<Jailbird40>
		<title>Sittes</title>
		<titleShort>Sittes</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] élete nagy részét börtönben töltötte, ahol konyhai munkát végzett. Gyakran keveredett verekedésbe és mindig is agresszívan beszélt másokkal.</desc>
	</Jailbird40>
	<Actor42>
		<title>Színész</title>
		<titleShort>Színész</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] utazó színészként járta bolygóját társulatával, mindenütt telt házas előadásokat tartva a szerető közönségnek. Maximalista volt, csak a saját maga által készített jelmezeket és kellékeket használta.</desc>
	</Actor42>
	<Tactician37>
		<title>Stratéga</title>
		<titleShort>Stratéga</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy háború szaggatta rendszerben állt be az űrhadseregbe, tele bolygóközi harcokkal. Kiderült, hogy jó érzéke van a stratégiához és hamar szakértője lett nagy haderők irányításának.</desc>
	</Tactician37>
	<GlitterworldOfficer60>
		<title>Szupervilági tiszt</title>
		<titleShort>Tiszt</titleShort>
		<desc>A fejlett világok általában békés helyek, de gyakran felkészültek maradnak egy esetleges háborúra. [PAWN_nameDef] egysége nemigen látott bevetést.

Szabadidejében leginkább művészeti hajlamait élte ki, de mivel beosztottjai fő szórakozása a verekedés volt, [PAWN_nameDef] gyakorlatot szerzett ezek oszlatásában.</desc>
	</GlitterworldOfficer60>
	<Taster16>
		<title>Kóstoló</title>
		<titleShort>Kóstoló</titleShort>
		<desc>A király kóstolójaként [PAWN_nameDef] mindenből evett, ami csak a fenség asztalára került. Dekadens életet élt az udvarnál, ahol csak hízott és szinte semmilyen munkát nem végzett.</desc>
	</Taster16>
	<BiosphereManager95>
		<title>Botanikus</title>
		<titleShort>Botanikus</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy fejlett világban élt, ahol az összes alantas munkát robotok végezték az emberek pedig az örömöket hajszolták. Ő gondozta egy burjánzó park növény-, és állatvilágát, amit a lakók látogattak, ha a természet szépségére vágytak.</desc>
	</BiosphereManager95>
	<Veterinarian8>
		<title>Állatorvos</title>
		<titleShort>Állatorvos</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] beteg állatok gyógyításával kereste kenyerét. Szenvedésük látványa miatt felhagyott a húsevéssel, és sokáig vegetáriánusként élt, visszautasítva világa húsimádó kulináris tradícióit.</desc>
	</Veterinarian8>
	<ExplosivesExpert26>
		<title>Robbantási szakértő</title>
		<titleShort>Robbantási szakértő</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] robbantási szakértőként dolgozott egy bányában. Nagyon komolyan vette a munkáját és igen járatos volt a technikai részletekben. Nem is vett részt soha a takarítási munkákban, miután gondosan kiszámított robbanása elvégezte dolgát.</desc>
	</ExplosivesExpert26>
	<Counselor26>
		<title>Tanácsadó</title>
		<titleShort>Tanácsadó</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy fiatalkori trauma miatt súlyos táplálkozási zavarral küszködik. Tanácsadó segítségével sikerült az étkezését kordában tartania. Úgy döntött, tapasztalatait felhasználva fog mások érzelmi problémáján segíteni.</desc>
	</Counselor26>
	<Recruiter4>
		<title>Toborzó</title>
		<titleShort>Toborzó</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] része volt egy harcművészek tiszteletreméltó rendjének, akik hírhedtek voltak mind harci ügyességükről, mind arról, hogy megtagadták a kezelést a sebesültjeiktől.

Világát járta, és megítélte a fiatalokról, akikkel találkozott, hogy alkalmasak-e a kiképzésre.</desc>
	</Recruiter4>
	<PsychiatricPatient94>
		<title>Elmebeteg</title>
		<titleShort>Elmebeteg</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] felnőtt korának nagy részét elmegyógyintézetben töltötte. Gyári világának rossz felfogása volt a mentális betegségekről, és inkább kezelték úgy, mint egy állatot, mint egy embert.

Bár végül felépült és megszabadult, a tapasztalatai lerontják sok képességét.</desc>
	</PsychiatricPatient94>
	<Drifter67>
		<title>Csavargó</title>
		<titleShort>Csavargó</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] soha nem tudta, mit kezdjen az életével. Gyakran utazott, alkalmi munkákat vállalt ott, ahol talált.

Alkalmanként egy regényen is dolgozott, amelyről tudta, hogy bestseller lehet - ha talál egy érdeklődő kiadót.</desc>
	</Drifter67>
	<VRDesigner87>
		<title>Játékfejlesztő</title>
		<titleShort>Játékfejlesztő</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] virtuális valóság szimulációkat tervezett egy szupervilág polgárai számára. Nagy figyelmet fordított a részletességre, például megtanult a növények életéről annyit, amennyit csak lehet, hogy valósághűbbé tegye a virtuális tájakat.</desc>
	</VRDesigner87>
	<HumanComputer7>
		<title>Fejszámoló</title>
		<titleShort>Fejszámoló</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] kiváló memóriával és fejszámoló képességgel rendelkezik. Egy diktátor alkalmazta, hogy az állam pénzügyeit kövesse figyelemmel, mivel az elektronikus számítógépeket túl könnyen fel lehetett törni.</desc>
	</HumanComputer7>
	<Architect28>
		<title>Építész</title>
		<titleShort>Építész</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] épületeket tervezett és épített. Hazájában, egy szupervilágban, az építészet technikai részét legtöbb esetben egy MI (Mesterséges Intelligencia) kezelte. Ez lehetővé tette számára, hogy a szakma művészeti határait feszegesse, de azt is jelentette, hogy soha nem kellett összepiszkolnia a kezét az építkezések helyszínein.</desc>
	</Architect28>
	<MessageCarrier77>
		<title>Hírnök</title>
		<titleShort>Hírnök</titleShort>
		<desc>Egy középkori világban az üzenetküldés leggyorsabb módja odaadni valakinek, aki lovon elviszi és remélhetőleg túléli az utat. [PAWN_nameDef] volt ez a valaki.</desc>
	</MessageCarrier77>
	<Sculptor63>
		<title>Szobrász</title>
		<titleShort>Szobrász</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] emberméretű kőtömbök faragásával kezdett, de gyorsan elkezdett nagyobb léptékben gondolkodni. Bányászrobotok segítségével megtanulta, hogyan készítsen hatalmas monumentumokat hegyoldalakba. Szupervilágának minden nemzeti parkja hamar tele lett óriás kő alakokkal.</desc>
	</Sculptor63>
	<MachineCollector55>
		<title>Gépgyűjtő</title>
		<titleShort>Gyűjtő</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] a régi technológiák és gépek megszállottja volt. Ha csak tehette, beszerzett egyet. Imádta szétszerelni őket és megfigyelni a működésüket.

Szokása volt hosszan beszélni gyűjteményéről, még akkor is, mikor már senki nem figyelt rá.</desc>
	</MachineCollector55>
	<Sheriff52>
		<title>Seriff</title>
		<titleShort>Seriff</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy elszigetelt ipari város seriffje volt. Öntelt és rosszindulatú ember hírében állt. A kisujját sem mozdította, ha nem pénzről, alkoholról vagy bosszúról volt szó.</desc>
	</Sheriff52>
	<ConArtist80>
		<title>Szélhámos</title>
		<titleShort>Szélhámos</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] sohasem hozott létre semmi új értéket. Viszont őstehetsége volt hozzá, hogy rávegyen másokat, adják át neki, amit készítettek.</desc>
	</ConArtist80>
	<MedievalSlave49>
		<title>Rabszolga</title>
		<titleShort>Rabszolga</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egész életében kocsikat húzott és gödröket ásott egy középkori világon. Az egyszerű kétkezi munka a legrégibb társa, hajcsára ostora mellett.

Kilenc éves koráig olvasni sem tudott.</desc>
	</MedievalSlave49>
	<MedievalLordling19>
		<title>Feudális uracska</title>
		<titleShort>Uracska</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy feudális világ királyságának volt jelentéktelen földesura. Kőből épült udvarházban nőtt fel, bólogató szolganéptől körülvéve.

Az ilyen élet nem tanít technológiai képzettségeket és a kétkezi munka sem jár vele. Ezzel szemben [PAWN_nameDef] már korán elsajátította a szociális manipuláció művészetét.</desc>
	</MedievalLordling19>
	<UrbworldUrchin61>
		<title>Urbvilági utcagyerek</title>
		<titleShort>Utcagyerek</titleShort>
		<desc>Az urbilágok ősi óriásvárosok tele iparral, emberrel és méreggel. [PAWN_nameDef] egy ilyen világ sötét sarkában nőtt fel. Minden falatért meg kellett küzdenie.</desc>
	</UrbworldUrchin61>
	<VatgrownSoldier8>
		<title>Klónozott katona</title>
		<titleShort>Klón</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] nem személynek teremtetett, hanem a pusztítás eszközének. Egy biofegyver gyárban klónozták és tanították harcra gyorsított fejlődése alatt. [PAWN_nameDef] azóta is hajlamos mindenféle harci tevékenységre és a társaság kerülésére.</desc>
	</VatgrownSoldier8>
	<SicklyChild72>
		<title>Beteges gyerek</title>
		<titleShort>Páciens</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] ritka gyermekkori betegségben szenvedett. Karanténba zárták egy kutatókórházban, ezért alig kapott testedzést és emberekkel is ritkán érintkezett, viszont a steril körülmények között jól megismerte a tudományokat és gyógyítást.</desc>
	</SicklyChild72>
	<ShelterChild50>
		<title>Menedék gyerek</title>
		<titleShort>Menedékgyerek</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy menedékben nőtt fel mélyen egy mérgezett világ felszíne alatt. Széleskörű oktatást kapott, de nem volt esélye fizikális munkát végezni. </desc>
	</ShelterChild50>
	<IndustrialOrphan13>
		<title>Gyári árva</title>
		<titleShort>Árva</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] sosem ismerte szüleit. Első emlékei ipari világának bányáiban és gyáraiban végzett robotról szólnak.

Emiatt sosem részesült megfelelő oktatásban.</desc>
	</IndustrialOrphan13>
	<Scout94>
		<title>Felderítő</title>
		<titleShort>Felderítő</titleShort>
		<desc>Egy kisebb birodalom köztisztviselőinek gyermekeként, [PAWN_nameDef] egy ifjúsági programba került, ahol megtanították neki a hadi felderítés tudományát.

Megtanult túlélni a vadonban, engedelmeskedni és kérdéseket nem feltenni.</desc>
	</Scout94>
	<FrightenedChild43>
		<title>Rémült gyermek</title>
		<titleShort>Rémült</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] fóbiák és neurózisok hosszú listájával nőtt fel. Többek között félt az orvosoktól, fertőző ételektől.

Emiatt meg kellett tanulnia, hogy ellássa magát és főzzön is, de félelmei jó része felnőttként is megmaradt.</desc>
	</FrightenedChild43>
	<CaveworldTender20>
		<title>Barlangi gondozó</title>
		<titleShort>Barlangi kölyök</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy barlangrendszerben nőtt fel mélyen egy lakhatatlan bolygó felszíne alatt. Más gyerekekkel együtt gondozta törzse gombaültetvényeit.</desc>
	</CaveworldTender20>
	<CaveworldTunneler48>
		<title>Barlangi alagútásó</title>
		<titleShort>Alagútásó</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] alagutakat ásott egy óriási földalatti barlangrendszerben.

Olyan jól ismeri a sziklákat, hogy szinte szag alapján kiismeri magát a barlangokban.</desc>
	</CaveworldTunneler48>
	<ComaChild57>
		<title>Kóma gyerek</title>
		<titleShort>Kóma gyerek</titleShort>
		<desc>Gyerekkori balesete miatt [PAWN_nameDef] komába esett. Már közel járt huszadik évéhez, mikor felébredt. A teste sosem heverte ki a sokéves inaktivitást, de a legtöbben megsajnálják, ha megismerik a történetét.</desc>
	</ComaChild57>
	<Pyromaniac18>
		<title>Piromán</title>
		<titleShort>Piro</titleShort>
		<desc>From an early age, [PAWN_nameDef] had an unhealthy fascination with fire. [] would set refuse heaps ablaze and become so entranced by the flames [] would absent-mindedly burn [PAWN_objective]self.

One day while playing with matches, [] carelessly burned down [PAWN_possessive] home.</desc>
	</Pyromaniac18>
	<Mute34>
		<title>Néma</title>
		<titleShort>Néma</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was greatly affected by a traumatic event early in [PAWN_possessive] life. For many years [] refused to speak to people, preferring instead to play with [PAWN_possessive] household's numerous pets.</desc>
	</Mute34>
	<WarRefugee51>
		<title>Háborús Menekült</title>
		<titleShort>Menekült</titleShort>
		<desc>Egy háború tört ki [PAWN_nameDef] bolygóján.

Összegyőjtött annyi élelmet és egyéb cókmókot amennyit csak tudott, majd [PAWN_nameDef] és apja ellopott egy hajót és elmenekült az űrbe.</desc>
	</WarRefugee51>
	<MusicLover86>
		<title>Zenész</title>
		<titleShort>Zenész</titleShort>
		<desc>Gyermekként [PAWN_nameDef] nagy tehetséget mutatott zenében és énekben. Kitaníttatták és koncerteken adott elő. Rajongói miatt kicsit el van telve magával.</desc>
	</MusicLover86>
	<ChildStar74>
		<title>Gyereksztár</title>
		<titleShort>Sztár</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] világa ismert gyerekszínésze volt. Hírneve miatt sokféle emberrel találkozott, ám ez tanulmányai kárára ment.</desc>
	</ChildStar74>
	<ChildSpy53>
		<title>Kémkölyök</title>
		<titleShort>Kém</titleShort>
		<desc>A gyerekeket ártatlannak tartják, ezért ideális kém válhat belőlük. [PAWN_nameDef] kilenc éves korában lett kiképezve a behatolás és adatgyűjtés művészetére.

Az ellenséges vonalak mögött töltött idő és a sok háború korlátozta a lehetőségét, hogy tanulmányokat folytasson.</desc>
	</ChildSpy53>
	<Shopkeeper36>
		<title>Eladó</title>
		<titleShort>Eladó</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] anyja sokat betegeskedett, ezért neki kellett vinnie a boltot, ami egyetlen bevételforrásuk volt. Tanult egy keveset az egzotikus ereklyékről, amikkel kereskedett, és sokat az alku művészetéről.</desc>
	</Shopkeeper36>
	<OrganFarm67>
		<title>Szervtenyészet</title>
		<titleShort>Szervtenyészet</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy illegális szervtenyészetben nőtt fel. A testét organikus implantok tenyésztésére használták melyekkel sebesült zsoldosokat kezeltek. Ezek az évek a mai napig kísértik, viszont nagyon jól kiismerte általuk az ember felépítését.</desc>
	</OrganFarm67>
	<ConventChild16>
		<title>Kolostor neveltje</title>
		<titleShort>Fattyú</titleShort>
		<desc>Egy tiltott affér gyümölcseként [PAWN_nameDef] egy kolostorban nőtt fel apácák között. Megtanulta a kemény munka és alázat értékét, és azt is, hogy a tudomány eretnekség.</desc>
	</ConventChild16>
	<TestSubject15>
		<title>Tesztalany</title>
		<titleShort>Tesztalany</titleShort>
		<desc>A legtöbb urbvilágon követnek el atrocitásokat a tudomány nevében olyan tudósok, akikbe nem szorult lelkiismeret. [PAWN_nameDef] egy lezárt intézményben nőtt fel, ahol különböző viselkedés módosító kísérletnek vetették alá, hogy egy tökéletes katonát faragjanak belőle.</desc>
	</TestSubject15>
	<MedicalAssistant82>
		<title>Medikus</title>
		<titleShort>Medikus</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy háború sújtotta világon nőtt fel, ahol mindkét fél túlzásba vitte a napalm használatát. Egy kórházban nőtt fel, ahol a szüleinek segített ellátni a sok háborús égési sérültet. Életre szóló tűziszonya lett.</desc>
	</MedicalAssistant82>
	<CultChild3>
		<title>Szektás kölyök</title>
		<titleShort>Szektás kölyök</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy erős szektába született, ami elnyomta a fejlett technológiát és hitte, hogy minden betegség gyógyítható a lélek megtisztításával.

Miután eljutott hozzá a külső világ híre, úgy döntött, elszökik.</desc>
	</CultChild3>
	<WreckageExplorer8>
		<title>Felfedező</title>
		<titleShort>Felfedező</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] világa születése előtt két generációval lett totális káosz birodalma, amit egy apokaliptikus háború okozott. [PAWN_nameDef] törzse nyáját vigyázta, de gyakran ellógott, hogy lezuhant csatahajók roncsait fedezze fel.</desc>
	</WreckageExplorer8>
	<ApocalypseSurvivor23>
		<title>Apokalipszis túlélő</title>
		<titleShort>Túlélő</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] zavargásokkal teli világba született, amit a klímaváltozás árvizekkel és éhínséggel fenyegetett. Ahogy cseperedett a helyzet rosszabbodott, milliárdok haltak meg és egész államok merültek káoszba. [PAWN_nameDef] és szülei mindent megtettek a túlélés érdekében.</desc>
	</ApocalypseSurvivor23>
	<StoryWriter67>
		<title>Író</title>
		<titleShort>Író</titleShort>
		<desc>Gyerekként, [PAWN_nameDef] állandóan olvasott. Egész napokat töltött a helyi könyvtárban könyvekbe bújva. Amikor pénzhiány miatt bezárt a könyvtár, [PAWN_nameDef] kétségbeesett. Saját történeteket kezdett írni, hogy pótolja a hiányt.</desc>
	</StoryWriter67>
	<Hermit12>
		<title>Remete</title>
		<titleShort>Remete</titleShort>
		<desc>A társadalmi érintkezésbe belefáradván, [PAWN_nameDef] elhagyta zsúfolt városát, hogy egyszerűbb életet éljen a vadonban. Egyedül töltötte napjait kertjét gondozva és saját szerszámait kovácsolva. Ezek segítségével maradt életben.</desc>
	</Hermit12>
	<SpacePirate55>
		<title>Űrkalóz</title>
		<titleShort>Kalóz</titleShort>
		<desc>A kalózkodás mindenhol felüti a fejét, ahol a kormány gyenge és a társadalom szétszóródott. [PAWN_nameDef] egy ilyen bandának volt tagja, békés kereskedőkön élősködött a profit érdekében.</desc>
	</SpacePirate55>
	<PitBrawler76>
		<title>Ketrecharcos</title>
		<titleShort>Ketrecharcos</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] kilenc éves korában harcolt először. Győzött, de a lényeg már akkor is a közönség szórakoztatása volt. A ketrecharc jól jövedelmező állás azok számára, akik túlélik. Ráadásul a legtöbb esetben még legális is.</desc>
	</PitBrawler76>
	<IllegalShipwright76>
		<title>Illegális hajóépítő</title>
		<titleShort>Hajóépítő</titleShort>
		<desc>Törvény tiltja, hogy terawattos lézert telepíts szállítóhajókra. Különösen, ha elrejted egy kommunikációs antenna alá, a meglepetésszerű támadás érdekében. [PAWN_nameDef] rájött, hogy ezzel sokat kereshet, bár csak azoktól, akik köpnek a törvényekre.</desc>
	</IllegalShipwright76>
	<Courtesean30>
		<title>Kurtizán</title>
		<titleShort>Kurtizán</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] testét több száz kuncsaft használta jó pár bolygón. Ez sebeket ejtett a lelkén, viszont kiismerte az utca törvényeit.</desc>
	</Courtesean30>
	<SpaceMarine16>
		<title>Tengerész</title>
		<titleShort>Tengerész</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] a Csillagközi Tengerészethez csatlakozott, hogy a bolygóját védje. Több csatában kitűnt.

Ez az élet elég érzéketlenné tette, de a harcot jól kitanulta.</desc>
	</SpaceMarine16>
	<Assassin20>
		<title>Bérgyilkos</title>
		<titleShort>Bérgyilkos</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] profi bérgyilkos volt. Hideg, számító, jól kereső. Ebben a munkában az empátia teljes hiánya előny.</desc>
	</Assassin20>
	<Gatherer40>
		<title>Gyűjtögető</title>
		<titleShort>Gyűjtögető</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] mestere a gyűjtögetésnek. Még a legkietlenebb vidéken is képes élelmet találni, mivel remekül ismeri a növényeket, gyökereket és bogyókat.</desc>
	</Gatherer40>
	<Loner40>
		<title>Magának való</title>
		<titleShort>Magának való</titleShort>
		<desc>Sosem szerette a törzsi gyűléseket vagy a nagy fesztiválokat. A nyílt pusztát kedveli és a szél fütyülő hangját a kövek között.

Időről időre meglátogatja törzsét, de többnyire magáról gondoskodik, felhasználva túlélő ismereteit.</desc>
	</Loner40>
	<Healer0>
		<title>Gyógyító</title>
		<titleShort>Gyógyító</titleShort>
		<desc>Miután törzsének gyógyítóját megölték egy rajtaütésben, [PAWN_nameDef] vette át helyét. Idejét gyógynövények és ásványok gyűjtésével töltötte, amikből meglepően hatékony gyógyszereket készített.</desc>
	</Healer0>
	<Scout17>
		<title>Vezető</title>
		<titleShort>Vezető</titleShort>
		<desc>Amióta csak törzse felvette a kapcsolatot az idegenekkel, [PAWN_nameDef] vezetőként adta el szolgálatait nekik. Elég gyakran került kapcsolatba ereklyékkel, ezért otthonosan kezeli a régi technológiákat.</desc>
	</Scout17>
	<Digger69>
		<title>Földmunkás</title>
		<titleShort>Földmunkás</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] és törzse mélyen a hegy gyomrába vájta otthonát. [PAWN_nameDef] sziklát fejtve és járatokat aládúcolva érzi jól magát.</desc>
	</Digger69>
	<MuffaloShaman1>
		<title>Muffalo sámán</title>
		<titleShort>Sámán</titleShort>
		<desc>Csendes bölcsessége és nagy ereje miatt, [PAWN_nameDef] egy muffalok vonulását követő nomád törzs vallási vezetője lett.</desc>
	</MuffaloShaman1>
	<LoreKeeper51>
		<title>Őrző</title>
		<titleShort>Őrző</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] az őrzők hosszú sorának egy tagja volt. Minden éjjel a tűz körül ülve adta tovább az ősi tudást törzse tagjainak, mesékbe ágyazva.</desc>
	</LoreKeeper51>
	<Weaver80>
		<title>Takács</title>
		<titleShort>Takács</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] a muffalo bőrrel, növényi rostokkal és festékanyagokkal való munka mestere volt, amikből gyönyörű ruhákat készített. Munkái gyakran cseréltek gazdát a törzsek közötti kereskedelemben.</desc>
	</Weaver80>
	<CaveTender66>
		<title>Gondozó</title>
		<titleShort>Gondozó</titleShort>
		<desc>Míg mások vadásztak és gyűjtögettek, [PAWN_nameDef] otthon maradt főzni és a gyerekekről, idősekről gondoskodni .</desc>
	</CaveTender66>
	<Warrior94>
		<title>Harcos</title>
		<titleShort>Harcos</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] félelmetes harcos volt, sokféle fegyver mestere. Sok csatát megjárt.</desc>
	</Warrior94>
	<TribeChild68>
		<title>Törzstag</title>
		<titleShort>Törzstag</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] törzstagként nőtt fel, a falu körül futkorászva, muffalo csordákkal mozogva. Szüleitől tanulta a létfontosságú készségeket.

Sosem tanult meg olvasni és sosem látott gépet, az ősi romokon kívül.</desc>
	</TribeChild68>
	<AbandonedChild60>
		<title>Elhagyott gyermek</title>
		<titleShort>Elhagyott</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] betegesnek született. A szülei elhagyták, mivel csak a törzs terhére lett volna. Valahogy mégis túlélt.</desc>
	</AbandonedChild60>
	<ReclusiveChild82>
		<title>Világtól elvonult</title>
		<titleShort>Világtól elvonult</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] már majdnem öt éves volt, mire megtanult beszélni, de akkor is magának való volt. Tizenéves korában elkezdett elvándorolni a faluból, hogy a vadonban éljen, akár hetekig.</desc>
	</ReclusiveChild82>
	<Herder58>
		<title>Juhász</title>
		<titleShort>Juhász</titleShort>
		<desc>Gyerekként, [PAWN_nameDef] a muffalo csordára vigyázott, gondozta a beteg állatokat. Csendes munka volt, de élvezte, hogy nem kell emberek között lennie.</desc>
	</Herder58>
	<Scavenger22>
		<title>Guberáló</title>
		<titleShort>Guberáló</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] azzal töltötte gyerekkorát, hogy elkerülje a munkát és roncsokban kincsekre vadásszon. Kíváncsisága sok bajba sodorta, de sok ugyanakkor sok érdekes dologra bukkant.</desc>
	</Scavenger22>
	<CaveChild30>
		<title>Barlanglakó gyermek</title>
		<titleShort>Barlanglakó gyermek</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy nagy és tekervényes barlangrendszerben nőtt fel, ami melyen a hegy gyomrába vezetett. Segített a felnőtteknek, a barlangrendszert fejleszteni.</desc>
	</CaveChild30>
	<SoleSurvivor9>
		<title>Magányos túlélő</title>
		<titleShort>Túlélő</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egész törzsét kiirtották egy rajtaütésben. Befogadta őt egy másik törzs, de érzelmileg sérült maradt, és inkább otthon ült, főzött és kertészkedett.</desc>
	</SoleSurvivor9>
	<VengefulChild43>
		<title>Bosszúálló kölyök</title>
		<titleShort>Bosszúálló</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] gyerekkorában egyszer arra ért haza a falujába, hogy banditák teljesen kiirtották. Bosszút esküdött és erőszakos vérengzésbe kezdett a vadonban.</desc>
	</VengefulChild43>
	<FireKeeper22>
		<title>Tűzőrző</title>
		<titleShort>Tűzőrző</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] feladata volt, hogy a törzs tüzét őrizze. Nagyon komolyan vette ennek felelősségét.</desc>
	</FireKeeper22>
	<FallenProdigy13>
		<title>Bukott csodagyerek</title>
		<titleShort>Csodagyerek</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy káoszba fulladó szupervilágon született. Az apját háborúban ölték meg.

Ösztöndíjat akart kapni az Utmaior Akadémián, ezért bizonyítania kellett, hogy odavaló. Csodagyerekként állandóan zsarnokoskodtak vele, ezért nem volt egy barátja sem.</desc>
	</FallenProdigy13>
	<MadScientist14>
		<title>Őrült tudós</title>
		<titleShort>Tudós</titleShort>
		<desc>Miután nyilvánosságra hozták a Callos IX-en folytatott etikétlan kísérleteit, száműzték őt és megfosztották mindenétől. [PAWN_nameDef] megtanulta, amit a túléléshez meg kellett.

Nem volt mit veszítenie, folytatta a kutatásait, és szolgákat hozott létre az unalmas munkák elvégzésére.</desc>
	</MadScientist14>
	<FarmKid40>
		<title>Tanyasi kölyök</title>
		<titleShort>Tanyasi kölyök</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] családja marhafarmján nőtt fel. Élvezettel dolgozott a földeken és gondozta az állatokat</desc>
	</FarmKid40>
	<CivilEngineer23>
		<title>Építőmérnök</title>
		<titleShort>Építőmérnök</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] ismert építőmérnök volt. A munkája része volt kőből készült erődítmények tervezése és építése. Sok statikai számítást végzett, amik élesen tartották az eszét.</desc>
	</CivilEngineer23>
	<FarmerBoy89>
		<title>Gazda</title>
		<titleShort>Gazda</titleShort>
		<desc>Benjamin szülei hét évesen haltak meg egy tűzben. Nagybátyja farmján nőtt fel, földeket szántva és kétkezi munkát végezve.

Sosem bírta a szüleire vonatkozó kérdéseket, ezért kemény munkával helyettesítette a társadalmi kapcsolatokat.</desc>
	</FarmerBoy89>
	<ArmyCook51>
		<title>Hadsereg szakácsa</title>
		<titleShort>Szakács</titleShort>
		<desc>Ben munkásként csatlakozott a hadsereghez, és a legtöbb idejét főzéssel és javításokkal töltötte. Míg egy veszélyes bolygón állomásozott, alap lövészeti és túlélési tréninget kapott.</desc>
	</ArmyCook51>
	<UrbworldCriminal98>
		<title>Urbvilági bűnöző</title>
		<titleShort>Bűnöző</titleShort>
		<desc>Egy túlzsúfolt urbvilágra rossz körülmények közé született, ezért Vladimir a kiskorú bűnözés felé fordult, hogy elkerülje az éhezést és a kihűlést.

A rablás és gyilkosság napi tevékenység volt számára. Vladimir megtanulta, hogy a túlélés már győzelem.</desc>
	</UrbworldCriminal98>
	<UrbworldPolitican82>
		<title>Urbvilági politikus</title>
		<titleShort>Politikus</titleShort>
		<desc>Nem titok, hogy az urbvilágok vállalatok tulajdonában vannak, de valakinek megvesztegethetőnek kell lenni. Vladimir volt az egyik ilyen alak.

Megtanulta, hogyan manipulálhatja az emberek reményeit és álmait, miközben kényelmesen él a villájában.</desc>
	</UrbworldPolitican82>
	<OptimisticChild43>
		<title>Optimista gyerek</title>
		<titleShort>Optimista</titleShort>
		<desc>Kees-t szeretetteljes szülők és kellemes fejlett világi élet áldotta meg. Optimista és társaságkedvelő gyerek volt, aki szeretett barátkozni és meghallgatni mások történeteit. Fantáziája gyakran elszabadult, csupa kérdés és ötlet.</desc>
	</OptimisticChild43>
	<GraphicDesigner99>
		<title>Grafikus Designer</title>
		<titleShort>Designer</titleShort>
		<desc>Kees érdeklődése a művészi kifejezésre vezette őt tervezővé. Jó szeme volt a részletekhez, ami jó hírű művésszé tette őt a bolygón, bár az aprólékosság gyakran arra késztette, hogy túl sok időt töltsön egyetlen projekt befejezésével.</desc>
	</GraphicDesigner99>
	<UrbworldHooligan72>
		<title>Urbvilági huligán</title>
		<titleShort>Huligán</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy veszélyes urbvilágban nőtt fel. Gyorsan megtanulta, hogyan kell a mindennap élelmet szerezni - bűnözéssel. Az ilyen élet kevés lehetőséget hagy a főzés és a földművelés kitanulására.</desc>
	</UrbworldHooligan72>
	<SpaceTechnician1>
		<title>Űrtechnikus</title>
		<titleShort>Technikus</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] végre ki tudott szállni bűnöző életéből, amikor egy karbantartási munkát kapott egy közeli űrállomáson. Több javítási és építési projektnek is tagja volt. Ugyancsak részt vett pár egyszerű kutatásban, és gyakran elsimította a munkatársak balhéit. Soha nem szerette a művészetet.</desc>
	</SpaceTechnician1>
	<IndworldUrchin73>
		<title>Gyári csibész</title>
		<titleShort>Csibész</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] az ipari forradalom korai szakaszában nőtt fel világa utcáin. Napjait lopással, tarhálással és alkatrészekkel való ügyeskedéssel töltötte, mindig a kitörést keresve a szegénységből.</desc>
	</IndworldUrchin73>
	<DoomsdayPariah24>
		<title>Világvégi pária</title>
		<titleShort>Pária</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] valahogy kinyitott egy másvilági technológiát tartalmazó épületet, miközben egy ásatási helyszínen fosztogatott. Véletlenül beindított egy ítéletnap gépet, amely kiirtotta az egész bolygót. Jobban érdekelte a technológia, mint az emberi élet, felszállt az idegenek űrhajójára, és elindult, hogy több ereklyét találjon, amivel játszhat.</desc>
	</DoomsdayPariah24>
	<ChildScientist69>
		<title>Gyermek tudós</title>
		<titleShort>Tudós</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] nagyon fiatalon diplomázott, majd annak szentelte életet, hogy halhatatlanná váljon. Letartóztatták, mert módosítani próbálta a saját genetikai kódját.

A hatóságok végül elengedték, annak fejében, hogy a kormány űrprogramján fog dolgozni. Szabadidejében folytathatta kutatásait.</desc>
	</ChildScientist69>
	<CombatEngineer48>
		<title>Utász</title>
		<titleShort>Utász</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] a hadsereg mérnöke volt, a haditengerészet űrhajóit fejlesztette. A kemény kiképzés megtanította neki, hogyan kell építeni és javítani katonai járműveket és épületeket.

Egy küldetés után [PAWN_nameDef] pirofóbiás lett, és a növényektől is iszonyodni kezdett.</desc>
	</CombatEngineer48>
	<MechanoidNerd23>
		<title>Mechanoid kocka</title>
		<titleShort>Mechakocka</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy urbvilágban nőtt fel, mint egy pár mechanoid tervező egyetlen gyermeke.
A szülei bátorították a gépek iránti érdeklődését. Végül megszállottja lett annak, hogy sajátot építsen.

Sajnos ez arra vezetett, hogy magányos maradt, mivel inkább a műszaki könyveket részesítette előnyben a barátok helyett</desc>
	</MechanoidNerd23>
	<MilitaryEngineer71>
		<title>Katonai mérnök</title>
		<titleShort>Mérnök</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] mérnökként dolgozott egy gyarmati hadseregnek. Eljátszadozhatott fegyverekkel, gyilkos drónokkal és egyéb "mókás" cuccokkal.

Mechanoid szerszámok javítására és fejlesztésére szakosodott. Néha saját magán tesztelte őket.</desc>
	</MilitaryEngineer71>
	<ColiseumCleaner54>
		<title>Kolosszeumi takarító</title>
		<titleShort>Takarító</titleShort>
		<desc>Szüleit elfogták, és rabszolgasorba kényszerítették a "Belső destriani háború" során. Véres gladiátor harcok után kellett kitakarítania. Figyelt, várakozott és tanult. A Kolosszeum volt az egyetlen dolog, amit valaha ismert. Egy éjszaka, takarítás közben meggyilkolták a családját.</desc>
	</ColiseumCleaner54>
	<ColiseumFighter12>
		<title>Gladiátor</title>
		<titleShort>Gladiátor</titleShort>
		<desc>Az évek során a harcosok körében szerzett tudás alkalmazásával annak a Kolosszeumnak lett sikeres gladiátora, amelyet anno takarított.</desc>
	</ColiseumFighter12>
	<OfficerCadet81>
		<title>Tiszt kadét</title>
		<titleShort>Kadét</titleShort>
		<desc>Bashkire fiatal kora óta arra készült, hogy vezér legyen. Még kisfiúként beiratkozott a Vanu Védelmi Főiskolára, ahol számos fegyverrel és túlélési technikával megismerkedett.</desc>
	</OfficerCadet81>
	<FighterController64>
		<title>Harci irányító</title>
		<titleShort>Irányító</titleShort>
		<desc>A Zartha-válság idején Bashkire számos világban harcolt, a föld és a levegő közötti létfontosságú kapcsolatot biztosítva, harci irányítóként. A hadjárat során barátait megsebesítették és megölték. Ez a lelki trauma álmaiban kísért, de a célzása még mindig ugyanolyan kiváló.</desc>
	</FighterController64>
	<ReclusiveProdigy20>
		<title>Visszavonult csodagyerek</title>
		<titleShort>Csodagyerek</titleShort>
		<desc>Holly egy virágzó szupervilágban nőtt fel. Megvolt az lehetősége, hogy teljes mértékben tanulmányaival foglalkozzon.

Fiatal kora óta a genetikai módosítások és idegi kiterjesztés iránt érdeklődött. Emiatt nagyon kevés ideje (vagy vágya) volt egy normális gyermekkorra.</desc>
	</ReclusiveProdigy20>
	<FerventResearcher2>
		<title>Buzgó kutató</title>
		<titleShort>Kutató</titleShort>
		<desc>Fiatal felnőttként Holly biztos volt benne, hogy bolygója és népe közeledik a felemelkedés idejéhez.

Az a szilárd meggyőződés, hogy kutatása ennek katalizátora, egyre aggasztóbb tettekre sarkallta, miközben a bürokraták és a bioetikai bizottságok megpróbálták hátráltatni.</desc>
	</FerventResearcher2>
	<WarRefugee43>
		<title>Háborús menekült</title>
		<titleShort>Menekült</titleShort>
		<desc>Háború tört ki a [PAWN_nameDef] bolygóján.

Összegyűjtve, ami kis ételt és holmit tudtak, [PAWN_nameDef] és az apja ellopott egy hajót, és elmenekült az űrbe.</desc>
	</WarRefugee43>
	<VengefulExplorer31>
		<title>Bosszúálló csavargó</title>
		<titleShort>Csavargó</titleShort>
		<desc>Otthontalan erőszakos csavargóként, [PAWN_nameDef] és az apja több száz éven keresztül harcolt sok csatában. Őszülő harcossá vált és fegyverzsonglőrré.

Apja halála után [PAWN_nameDef] elkezdte felfedezni a csillagokat egyedül, keresve apja gyilkosát, bosszúra szomjasan.</desc>
	</VengefulExplorer31>
	<WorkCampSlave93>
		<title>Munkatábori Rabszolga</title>
		<titleShort>Rabszolga</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy különösen undok nemesi család rabszolgájaként nőtt fel egy középkori világban. 
		
Nem kapott formális oktatást, de a kemény munka megerősítette testét.</desc>
	</WorkCampSlave93>
	<BanishedSoldier50>
		<title>Száműzött katona</title>
		<titleShort>Száműzött</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lett a fizikailag legmegfélemlítőbb rabszolga, aki minden szabadidejét testének megszállott gyúrásával töltötte. Erőfeszítései végül kifizetődtek, amikor az urasága személyi testőrnek alkalmazta.

Később, amikor arra akarta használni pozícióját, hogy megölje a lordot és kiszabadítsa a rabszolgákat, lebukott, és alig tudott élve elmenekülni.</desc>
	</BanishedSoldier50>
	<DisciplinedFarmer44>
		<title>Fegyelmezett Gazda</title>
		<titleShort>Gazda</titleShort>
		<desc>Drew volt a fiatalabb két fiú közül a családi farmon, egy határ menti helyen, amely alig termelt hasznot. Drew apja szigorú fegyelmező volt, állandóan a fiai nyakán, hogy keményebben dolgozzanak és csöndben maradjanak. Drew egyszer megégette a kezét reggeli készítés közben, és megfogadta, hogy csak akkor főz, ha az élete múlik rajta.</desc>
	</DisciplinedFarmer44>
	<StalwartFarmer89>
		<title>Rendíthetetlen Gazda</title>
		<titleShort>Gazda</titleShort>
		<desc>A rablóktól folyamatosan veszélyeztetett farmon [PAWN_nameDef] megtanulta megvédeni magát apja puskájával. Azt is elsajátította, hogyan építsen falakat, hogy benn tartsa állatait és a kinn a ragadozókat.

Egyszer megpróbált festeni egy képet az otthonáról, de rájött, hogy firkálni és kacsát rajzolni tud.</desc>
	</StalwartFarmer89>
	<VoyagerChild68>
		<title>Voyager child</title>
		<titleShort>Voyager</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] egy R&amp;D csillaghajón nevelkedett, és gyermekkorának nagy részét az űrben utazva töltötte.

Egy rejtélyes kisbolygóhoz közeledve a hajó súlyosan megsérült. Következő emléke, hogy a hajó a keringő pályát elhagyja, teljesen megjavítva. Hamarosan természetellenes tehetséget fedezett fel magában a technológiai kutatás iránt.</desc>
	</VoyagerChild68>
	<SpaceResearcher22>
		<title>Űrkutató</title>
		<titleShort>Űrkutató</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] örökölte szülei hajóját, és folytatta kutatásaikat.

Gyermekkori tapasztalatai a különböző kultúrákkal lehetővé tették számára, hogy megőrizze gondoskodó természetét, annak ellenére, hogy életének legnagyobb részét az űrben elszigetelve töltötte.</desc>
	</SpaceResearcher22>
	<VatgrownMedic46>
		<title>Medikus klón</title>
		<titleShort>Medikus</titleShort>
		<desc>Raised to be a combat medic, [PAWN_nameDef] was trained in firearms as well as medicine. His favorite phrase when coming upon a wounded soldier was "Life or death?" Most chose life.</desc>
	</VatgrownMedic46>
	<GeneticScientist4>
		<title>Genetic scientist</title>
		<titleShort>Geneticist</titleShort>
		<desc>After the war he joined a genetic engineering firm. He worked on enhancements for humans and livestock. His experiences in inflicting and healing wounds were very beneficial to his work, but he developed a black sense of humor. This made social gatherings awkward.</desc>
	</GeneticScientist4>
	<CoreDilettante31>
		<title>Core dilettante</title>
		<titleShort>Dilettante</titleShort>
		<desc>Candice spent her formative years on a glitterworld in the core region, where she and her friends pursued lives of idle pleasure.

As she grew up, she began to find the life of ease unfulfilling. She decided to look for a more challenging path.</desc>
	</CoreDilettante31>
	<Reporter15>
		<title>Reporter</title>
		<titleShort>Reporter</titleShort>
		<desc>Candice spent many years as an investigative reporter. She was notorious for making chaotic reports from exotic locations.

Although seen as a lightweight by her critics, she managed to break several high-profile stories after lengthy investigations.</desc>
	</Reporter15>
	<AspiringPopIdol5>
		<title>Aspiring pop idol</title>
		<titleShort>Pop idol</titleShort>
		<desc>Min was being trained in song and dance to become the next big pop idol. She grew up being taken care of by company handlers.

She never knew manual labor, but learned a lot about music and social etiquette.</desc>
	</AspiringPopIdol5>
	<PopIdol50>
		<title>Pop idol</title>
		<titleShort>Pop idol</titleShort>
		<desc>Min performed and did interviews constantly. She refined her skills in dancing and singing, and became a master of social presentation.</desc>
	</PopIdol50>
	<FarmBoy42>
		<title>Farm boy</title>
		<titleShort>Farm boy</titleShort>
		<desc>John worked on his family's farm, looking after the animals and treating them when they were injured. Preferring hands-on tasks and the outdoors, he avoided softer jobs that might have kept him cooped up inside.

He enjoyed this lonely work, and tended to stay out of people's way and do his own thing.</desc>
	</FarmBoy42>
	<UnstableButcher98>
		<title>Unstable butcher</title>
		<titleShort>Butcher</titleShort>
		<desc>John began hearing voices. The animals were talking to him, insulting him. He came to hate them, and eventually killed his furry former friends. He started selling the meat just to get human interaction.</desc>
	</UnstableButcher98>
	<StationWhelp45>
		<title>Station whelp</title>
		<titleShort>Whelp</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent his childhood as a penniless orphan living on a space station. He managed to scrape by doing filthy jobs and stealing. He became so violent due to poor treatment by his “betters” that he was banished from the station, just to be picked up by space pirates.</desc>
	</StationWhelp45>
	<PirateKing6>
		<title>Pirate king</title>
		<titleShort>Pirate</titleShort>
		<desc>With no real care for other people, [PAWN_nameDef] fit in perfectly with the pirate crew that he had once been a captive of. Shortly after becoming one of the crew, [PAWN_nameDef] began to kill anyone or anything that got in his way—including his crew mates.</desc>
	</PirateKing6>
	<ConstructionGrunt53>
		<title>Construction grunt</title>
		<titleShort>Builder</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up in his father's lab, Jackson was given the life of an intellectual elite. He got everything he desired, and price was never an object.

However Jackson did not partake in the luxury given to him. Instead, he pursued more physical, and - in his father's eyes - lower-class jobs.</desc>
	</ConstructionGrunt53>
	<MilitaryInventor78>
		<title>Military inventor</title>
		<titleShort>Inventor</titleShort>
		<desc>Jackson, in a final act of rebellion, left his father's lab and joined the local Imperial military.

He used his laboratory skills to design machines of war. At this he was one of the best on his planet.</desc>
	</MilitaryInventor78>
	<StudentEngineer64>
		<title>Student engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>A genius child, [PAWN_nameDef] was put in a special training program covering aerospace warfare and engineering.

One day, he tried to befriend a squirrel by giving it a bracelet. The squirrel bit him, earning him the nickname “Squirrel Boy.”

[PAWN_nameDef] came to believe that work involving manual labor is beneath [PAWN_objective].</desc>
	</StudentEngineer64>
	<EngineeredPilot91>
		<title>Engineered pilot</title>
		<titleShort>Pilot</titleShort>
		<desc>After his province was besieged by one of its neighbors, [PAWN_nameDef] volunteered for a generic modification program that created pilots for the very fighter craft that he had helped develop. The modifications allowed him to pilot the ship, but also made him less able to focus on the people around him.

By this time, people were calling him "Squirrel."</desc>
	</EngineeredPilot91>
	<StreetKid44>
		<title>Street kid</title>
		<titleShort>Street kid</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up on the streets of the a desert planet, [PAWN_nameDef]'s his only friend was a dog named Rest. The pair scraped by, finding just enough food to survive.

When [] was 13 years old, an interplanetary criminal group took [PAWN_objective] under their wing.</desc>
	</StreetKid44>
	<BanditLeader36>
		<title>Bandit leader</title>
		<titleShort>Bandit</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] rose up the ranks of the crime organization, eventually becoming the leader of one of their most remote cells of bandits. His dog Rest never left his side.</desc>
	</BanditLeader36>
	<FrontierMarshal82>
		<title>Frontier marshal</title>
		<titleShort>Marshal</titleShort>
		<desc>Nate was the marshal of his colony. He tried to honorably uphold the law, but the corrupt local mayor killed his family and left him for dead.

After regaining his health, Nate arrested the mayor. [] left his homeworld and started a new life working to make a difference in the universe.</desc>
	</FrontierMarshal82>
	<ColonialGovernor29>
		<title>Colonial governor</title>
		<titleShort>Governor</titleShort>
		<desc>Disillusioned by rampant government corruption, Henry ran for governor and won. However, the local gangs and their pet officials soon forced him out of power.

He left the community to return to his life as a marshal.</desc>
	</ColonialGovernor29>
	<MercenaryRecruit41>
		<title>Mercenary recruit</title>
		<titleShort>Recruit</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to a long line of off-world mercenaries, [PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a busy trading hub. At a young age, [] was recruited into one of the mercenary crews.</desc>
	</MercenaryRecruit41>
	<MercenaryChef48>
		<title>Mercenary chef</title>
		<titleShort>Mercenary</titleShort>
		<desc>Following in his family's footsteps, [PAWN_nameDef] was a soldier for hire.

He is a naturally gifted sharpshooter. However, his real passion is in perfecting a new recipe or dissecting a new gadget.</desc>
	</MercenaryChef48>
	<AbandonedChild47>
		<title>Elveszett gyermek</title>
		<titleShort>Elveszett</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a quick witted, funny child. One day, [] wandered off on [PAWN_possessive] wealthy genetic parents, and was ultimately lost in a supposedly unused ore warehouse. Due to cloning technology, [PAWN_possessive] parents decided that the time looking for [PAWN_objective] was better spent on just cloning a better son.</desc>
	</AbandonedChild47>
	<CargoPilot58>
		<title>Cargo pilot</title>
		<titleShort>Pilot</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was brought up by cargo hands on a long-haul ore transport ship. [] perfected [PAWN_possessive] skills at trading and manipulation of people while running weapons between systems.</desc>
	</CargoPilot58>
	<TradersChild13>
		<title>Traders' child</title>
		<titleShort>Trader</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a family of nomadic traders, making a living from selling and buying goods on many worlds.

[PAWN_nameDef] learned the customs and methods of trade of many cultures by participating in his parents' business.</desc>
	</TradersChild13>
	<SpaceHumanitarian9>
		<title>Space humanitarian</title>
		<titleShort>Activist</titleShort>
		<desc>After seeing the rampant poverty common on overcrowded urban worlds, [PAWN_nameDef] decided to dedicate [PAWN_possessive] life to helping the less fortunate. This crusade taught [PAWN_objective] how to care for the sick and the hungry.</desc>
	</SpaceHumanitarian9>
	<CorpStudent56>
		<title>Corp student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>De Dion was bred to become an executive officer for the large space trading corporation that owned his home planet. His family had been working for that corporation for seven generations.

At age six, [] started to study at the corporate academy, where he learned to become a loyal follower and a ruthless executive.</desc>
	</CorpStudent56>
	<ExecutiveOfficer48>
		<title>Executive officer</title>
		<titleShort>Executive</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an executive officer for a large space trading corporation. After a failed attempt at manipulating his way up the corporate ladder, he was framed for the rape and murder of another executive and her family.

He was found guilty. However, because of his family's influence, he was exiled instead of put to death.</desc>
	</ExecutiveOfficer48>
	<VRAddict62>
		<title>VR addict</title>
		<titleShort>VR addict</titleShort>
		<desc>Douglas was a VR head - someone who is permanently jacked into the virtual gaming universe by his spinal plug. He moved through his daily tasks barely aware of the physical reality around him. This left him nearly unable to socialize.</desc>
	</VRAddict62>
	<RugbyPlayer51>
		<title>Rugby player</title>
		<titleShort>Winger</titleShort>
		<desc>After years of addiction to virtual reality games, Douglas was saved when the doctors unplugged him.

Unfortunately, they unplugged him during a match of Rugby Rampage 4. The mental backlash merged his real identity and his virtual identity, leaving him with the personality and skills of a rugby player.</desc>
	</RugbyPlayer51>
	<Nerd58>
		<title>Nerd</title>
		<titleShort>Nerd</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was curious about everything. While other kids played tag in the suburbs of their industrial city, [PAWN_nameDef] read every book he could find about technology, robots, and weapons - whatever looked coolest.

His strong French accent kept him from making real friends.</desc>
	</Nerd58>
	<StateEngineer68>
		<title>State engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] enrolled in the state weapons research program.

While brilliant in his work, he was so enthusiastic in testing his creations that he accidentally wounded some colleagues and was marked as unfit for service.</desc>
	</StateEngineer68>
	<RebelSlave3>
		<title>Rebel slave</title>
		<titleShort>Rebel</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into corporate slavery and raised to perform menial tasks for minimum pay. [] was just another cog in the machine. 

[PAWN_nameDef] found his freedom by joining a rebel organization whose goal was to break free from their corporate masters.</desc>
	</RebelSlave3>
	<CombatNegotiator71>
		<title>Combat negotiator</title>
		<titleShort>Negotiator</titleShort>
		<desc>After escaping his homeworld, [PAWN_nameDef] took his skills to the stars.

He chose to operate as a hired gun, working for various rebel organizations, enslaved groups, and merchant enclaves. His specialty was negotiation in combat situations.</desc>
	</CombatNegotiator71>
	<MedievalPlower14>
		<title>Medieval plower</title>
		<titleShort>Plower</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived on a planet where kings and queens ruled with little regard for the peasants beneath them. [PAWN_possessive] family owned a large farm, but the king took most of the food it produced. This left [PAWN_nameDef]'s family poor, and unable to pay for [PAWN_possessive] education. Instead, [] was required to work the fields with [PAWN_possessive] parents, and never had time to practice creativity.</desc>
	</MedievalPlower14>
	<SpaceStationCook63>
		<title>Space station cook</title>
		<titleShort>Cook</titleShort>
		<desc>The space station [PAWN_nameDef] came from was far from any populated planets, and was in itself understaffed. For this reason, [PAWN_nameDef] was forced to learn how to cook in order to keep the crew alive. While [] appreciated this learning opportunity, [] didn't appreciate the criticism which came with it, and has had self-esteem issues ever since.</desc>
	</SpaceStationCook63>
	<SonOfAHuntress30>
		<title>Son of a huntress</title>
		<titleShort>Hunter</titleShort>
		<desc>In the mountains of the planet Ticonderoga, Jon was raised by his tribal mother. She taught him survival skills - trapping, tracking, shooting, skinning, cooking and healing.

His departed father had left behind an old bolt-action rifle, and Jon practiced with it every chance he got.</desc>
	</SonOfAHuntress30>
	<SpaceHunter67>
		<title>Space hunter</title>
		<titleShort>Huntsman</titleShort>
		<desc>Now a man as well as proficient hunter and marksman, Jon yearned for more. He took leave from his birth world, traveling the great expanse in search of exotic game.</desc>
	</SpaceHunter67>
	<StudentSocialite35>
		<title>Student socialite</title>
		<titleShort>Socialite</titleShort>
		<desc>Matis learned politics in an elite training school for socially gifted students on Kalthas IV.

While he was naturally adept at reading and manipulating people, he found no joy in it. He left the academy several years before graduation.</desc>
	</StudentSocialite35>
	<PoliticalAssassin59>
		<title>Political assassin</title>
		<titleShort>Deathjack</titleShort>
		<desc>Matis realized that his true calling was in physical solutions to diplomatic problems. He sought training from the assassins guild on Ceti V.

He was a quick study at the arts of subterfuge and death. He soon earned the guild rank of Deathjack.</desc>
	</PoliticalAssassin59>
	<AwkwardNerd12>
		<title>Awkward nerd</title>
		<titleShort>Nerd</titleShort>
		<desc>Always fascinated by machines, Dave spent his time studying robotics and holography. He preferred the company of his scientific creations to that of other people.</desc>
	</AwkwardNerd12>
	<AIResearcher30>
		<title>AI researcher</title>
		<titleShort>Researcher</titleShort>
		<desc>Dave was a renowned researcher in artificial intelligence, robotics, and interactive holography. His friendships with the artificial minds he created gave him the confidence to interact with real people, and he soon excelled at personal communication.</desc>
	</AIResearcher30>
	<MidworldGeek48>
		<title>Midworld geek</title>
		<titleShort>Geek</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a quiet suburban neighborhood. He was never a master of social interaction, but his interest in computers blossomed into a true talent at an early age.</desc>
	</MidworldGeek48>
	<ArmyScientist35>
		<title>Army scientist</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] did scientific research for a planetary army. [] studied war scenarios and designed weapon systems to help win battles with a minimum of fuss.</desc>
	</ArmyScientist35>
	<CatHerder70>
		<title>Cat herder</title>
		<titleShort>Herder</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] helped out in his father's cat breeding business, socializing, herding, and feeding hundreds of cats.

When he refused to clean up after the cats, [] was transferred to the breeding science division.</desc>
	</CatHerder70>
	<FelineScientist97>
		<title>Feline scientist</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] became a renowned scientist in the field of felines. Wanting the best for his animals and specializing in selective breeding, he set out on a journey to find the perfect breeding grounds for his cats.</desc>
	</FelineScientist97>
	<Scavenger76>
		<title>scavenger</title>
		<titleShort>scavenger</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in one of the few remaining cities on a world ravaged by nuclear war.

[] learned to survive on [PAWN_possessive] own in this post-apocalyptic wasteland by scavenging for technology and supplies.</desc>
	</Scavenger76>
	<SpaceMarine61>
		<title>space marine</title>
		<titleShort>marine</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was recruited into the security forces of an off-planet corporation.

[] defended their ships against pirates and engaged in private space warfare contracts.</desc>
	</SpaceMarine61>
	<VatgrownAssassin17>
		<title>Vatgrown assassin</title>
		<titleShort>Clone</titleShort>
		<desc>Vas was not made as a man, but a cold hearted assassin. He was bio-engineered by scientists, and trained as a killer. He was bred to have no emotion, no feelings, and no care for who lives, and who dies.</desc>
	</VatgrownAssassin17>
	<Mercenary40>
		<title>Mercenary</title>
		<titleShort>Mercenary</titleShort>
		<desc>After escaping his home planet, [PAWN_nameDef] fell in with a band of mercenaries. [] fought alongside his brothers and sisters in arms for many years.

One day, they were caught in a fight they couldn't win. Refusing to retreat, [PAWN_nameDef] was shot down by his enemies. [] was alarmed to awake in a heap of corpses, mysteriously unharmed.</desc>
	</Mercenary40>
	<HiveWorldChild24>
		<title>Hive world child</title>
		<titleShort>Hiver</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] had an isolated upbringing in an urbvilág hive city. His hatred of heights kept him indoors often, and made him an introverted child.

When [] did go out onto the catwalks of the city, [] enjoyed playing war games, becoming proficient with various simulation weapons.</desc>
	</HiveWorldChild24>
	<Microbiologist89>
		<title>Microbiologist</title>
		<titleShort>Biologist</titleShort>
		<desc>A plague struck [PAWN_nameDef]'s native urbvilág. [PAWN_nameDef] and other researchers revealed that the illness was a bioweapon, but the people turned on them, blaming them for the sickness.

[PAWN_nameDef] barely escaped his homeworld as it fell into chaos.</desc>
	</Microbiologist89>
	<StarforceCadet27>
		<title>Starforce cadet</title>
		<titleShort>Cadet</titleShort>
		<desc>Raised on Amen-Ti, glitterworld capital of the Star Empire, Sam Wissa had an easy childhood.

As a youth, Sam decided that joining the Starforce would be his way of giving back to the Empire.</desc>
	</StarforceCadet27>
	<AceFighterPilot48>
		<title>Ace fighter pilot</title>
		<titleShort>Ace</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] graduated from the Star Academy with honors and distinguished himself as an ace fighter pilot in three campaigns against more advanced aggressor cultures. 

However, after one vicious battle, he found himself stranded and his carrier ship destroyed. With nowhere to go, he entered his escape pod and prayed.</desc>
	</AceFighterPilot48>
	<Stableboy54>
		<title>Stableboy</title>
		<titleShort>Stableboy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a stableboy on a medieval planet, mucking dung almost every day to earn his keep.

By the time [] was exiting childhood, [PAWN_nameDef] had saved up enough money to pay a space trader to take [PAWN_objective] offworld.</desc>
	</Stableboy54>
	<Brigand68>
		<title>Brigand</title>
		<titleShort>Brigand</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] flew with a band of brigands [] called friends. [] even had a ship of [PAWN_possessive] own - The Dung Mucker 2000.</desc>
	</Brigand68>
	<ArtfulDodger29>
		<title>Artful dodger</title>
		<titleShort>Dodger</titleShort>
		<desc>Robin grew up on one of the urbvilágok and had to fend for himself all his life. He never trusted anyone, relying on his persuasiveness and cunning to survive.

He soon became skilled with firearms and knives as well as words.</desc>
	</ArtfulDodger29>
	<Assassin22>
		<title>assassin</title>
		<titleShort>assassin</titleShort>
		<desc>Robin was specially trained as an operative to be used for high-risk assassinations. His skill with a rifle was unrivalled.

He was eventually betrayed by his superiors when a target found out about the hit and offered to fund their future projects. Robin swore to never trust anyone again.</desc>
	</Assassin22>
	<Pickpocket65>
		<title>Pickpocket</title>
		<titleShort>Thief</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] witnessed [PAWN_possessive] parents' murder at a young age. With no guidance, [] had to fend for [PAWN_objective]self any way possible. Joining a small group of misfits [] did whatever was necessary to survive.</desc>
	</Pickpocket65>
	<BusinessGangster35>
		<title>Business gangster</title>
		<titleShort>Gangster</titleShort>
		<desc>Staying one step ahead of the law, [PAWN_nameDef] became a legitimate businessman and silenced anyone who dared say otherwise. As proprietor of brothels, speakeasies and eateries, [PAWN_nameDef]'s good fortune continued while his competition suffered a series of unfortunate and unexplained accidents.</desc>
	</BusinessGangster35>
	<DisasterSurvivor20>
		<title>Disaster survivor</title>
		<titleShort>Survivor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s planet collided with a small moon. Everything he knew as home was destroyed, and his entire family died. [] was left in the ruins to fend for himself.</desc>
	</DisasterSurvivor20>
	<ParamilitaryAgent11>
		<title>Paramilitary agent</title>
		<titleShort>Agent</titleShort>
		<desc>After scraping by on assorted shady jobs, [PAWN_nameDef] joined with a large paramilitary group to fight a war on [PAWN_possessive] homeworld. [PAWN_possessive] role was infiltration and intelligence gathering</desc>
	</ParamilitaryAgent11>
	<HistoryStudent78>
		<title>History student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>As a child, [PAWN_nameDef] spent learned many artistic forms including music and novel writing. As [] grew older, [] began to study legends from [PAWN_possessive] home world - legends of the lizard-like beings at the center of [PAWN_possessive] culture's folklore.</desc>
	</HistoryStudent78>
	<Storyteller62>
		<title>Storyteller</title>
		<titleShort>Fabulist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled his world recounting the legends that he had studied.

Obsessed with the legends of his people, [PAWN_nameDef] seeks someone who can help him grow scales on his skin, so he too can be as the ancients were.</desc>
	</Storyteller62>
	<NobleWard29>
		<title>Noble ward</title>
		<titleShort>Ward</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was adopted by a prominent noble family after being left on their doorstep by [PAWN_possessive] mother.

[] quickly learned secrets that passed between the nobles like cheap wine - of worlds beyond her own, languages, cultures and technologies both new and old.</desc>
	</NobleWard29>
	<InformationBroker9>
		<title>Information broker</title>
		<titleShort>Broker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] caught a ship to the next star system and began a life of travel and learning, quickly collecting a massive bank of knowledge from people of all shapes and sizes.

[] learned to sell this knowledge for great profit, and became a powerful broker of information.</desc>
	</InformationBroker9>
	<FeralChild19>
		<title>Feral child</title>
		<titleShort>Survivor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] and his family lived a hard but prosperous lives along with their fellow colonists on a distant rimworld.

One day a group of mechanoids attacked, killing everyone aside from Robert. He then lived alone in the desert until a group of raiders found him.</desc>
	</FeralChild19>
	<VersatileWorker53>
		<title>Versatile worker</title>
		<titleShort>Worker</titleShort>
		<desc>Spending his later teenage years in a colony of settlers, he offered what little skills he had to anyone who would take him.

Being a quick learner, he honed many of his skills and, apart from his crippling inability to understand fire, is now a fully functioning adult.</desc>
	</VersatileWorker53>
	<SpoiledChild33>
		<title>Spoiled child</title>
		<titleShort>Spoiled</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was the child of an industrious space engineer. [PAWN_possessive] parents forbade most manual and dangerous tasks, so [] learned art and music instead.

[] loved animals, but [PAWN_possessive] parents never let [PAWN_objective] have a pet - though [] played with other people's pets a lot.</desc>
	</SpoiledChild33>
	<TestSubject53>
		<title>Kísérleti nyúl</title>
		<titleShort>Kísérleti nyúl</titleShort>
		<desc>Kidnapped as a teenager, [PAWN_nameDef] was an unwilling test subject in experimental gene therapies for six years. Labs and scientists scare [PAWN_objective].</desc>
	</TestSubject53>
	<AmateurEngineer34>
		<title>Amateur engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a family with a military and engineering background. [] wanted to join the army but his father didn't like the idea, so [PAWN_possessive] interest turned to great flying machines and works of engineering. [] secretly hoped that this would one day lead him to a life of galactic exploration.</desc>
	</AmateurEngineer34>
	<AerospaceEngineer44>
		<title>Aerospace engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an engineer responsible for the production of aircraft and spaceships. [] focused on improving production lines, and was known for [PAWN_possessive] mastery of technical and research issues.</desc>
	</AerospaceEngineer44>
	<StreetUrchin56>
		<title>Street urchin</title>
		<titleShort>Grifter</titleShort>
		<desc>After running away from home, [PAWN_nameDef] had to live on the streets.

She grew up fast, and learned early that she had to figure out how to fool people into connecting with her.</desc>
	</StreetUrchin56>
	<HiredMuscle50>
		<title>hired muscle</title>
		<titleShort>hired thug</titleShort>
		<desc>Knowing what life on the streets was truly like, [PAWN_nameDef] slipped into police work. However, a particularly disturbing case ended with him beating the perpetrator to death.

Dishonorably discharged from his duties, he used his contacts and skills to find work as a thug for hire.</desc>
	</HiredMuscle50>
	<WildChild92>
		<title>Wild child</title>
		<titleShort>Wild child</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was abandoned on a toxic world overgrown with hostile plant life. [] became accustomed early to the cold burn of loneliness.

[] learned to fight, but ate his food raw and uncooked.</desc>
	</WildChild92>
	<AlcoholicTrucker68>
		<title>Alcoholic trucker</title>
		<titleShort>Alcoholic</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a space trucker working for Arcknight Industries when he killed his wife and daughter in a crash.

His body was repaired with an experimental nano-genetic therapy. Now his muscles continually regenerate and harden, and every movement tears the tissue anew. He bears the pain in silence.</desc>
	</AlcoholicTrucker68>
	<HackerProdigy70>
		<title>Hacker prodigy</title>
		<titleShort>Hacker</titleShort>
		<desc>Wedge was raised as the only child of wealthy surgeons. After being pressured into accepting a medical apprenticeship, he snapped. He seized his inheritance and went underground to learn how to exploit computer networks. He quickly became one of the most feared hackers on his home planet.</desc>
	</HackerProdigy70>
	<IntelligenceAgent82>
		<title>Intelligence agent</title>
		<titleShort>Agent</titleShort>
		<desc>Because of his hacking skills, Wedge was recruited by his home planet's governing body to serve as an intelligence agent. The government trained him in combat, but he prefers psychological warfare.

Government rules proved too strict for him, so he went rogue. His current activities are unknown.</desc>
	</IntelligenceAgent82>
	<MadScientist48>
		<title>mad scientist</title>
		<titleShort>scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up miserable on the plains of a neolithic planet. He found the strength to fight under the teachings of an old, broken scientist.

He quickly learned to play with people's fears, and was nicknamed 'mad scientist'.</desc>
	</MadScientist48>
	<WarChief2>
		<title>War chief</title>
		<titleShort>Chief</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a tribal gang leader on a neolithic planet. For him, the battlefield is a game, and there is nothing more fun than the fires of war.</desc>
	</WarChief2>
	<YouthDelinquent15>
		<title>Youth delinquent</title>
		<titleShort>Delinquent</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was the only child of celebrity sommeliers. Her parents expected her to take up the family profession, but after her third admission to a youth detention center, this career path became unlikely.

While in detention, [PAWN_nameDef] became skilled at making shanks and developed an interest in orinthology.</desc>
	</YouthDelinquent15>
	<InvoluntaryHermit80>
		<title>Involuntary hermit</title>
		<titleShort>Hermit</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]’s escape pod was jettisoned onto an unexplored region of a frontier world. She eked out a lonely existence with only a herd of muffalo for company.
 
Later, she was spotted clad in pygmy wombat furs, discussing the importance of hoof hygiene with a group of elderly muffalo.</desc>
	</InvoluntaryHermit80>
	<HillbillyProdigy33>
		<title>Hillbilly prodigy</title>
		<titleShort>Hillbilly</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a cold hillbilly planet inhabited mainly by furred xenohumans, Benjamin grew up to the sound of bar fights and shootouts. Though his childhood was spent playing the banjo and working as a mechanic, his abnormal intelligence made him want something more; he entered medical school at age twenty.</desc>
	</HillbillyProdigy33>
	<MedicalScientist25>
		<title>Medical scientist</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>Benjamin enlisted as a doctor on a passing science vessel. Roaming the stars with a large crew of xenohumans and transbirds, he did genetic research on encountered species. He developed a deep friendship with one transbird but was forced to leave the ship when the captain dismissed all non-avians.</desc>
	</MedicalScientist25>
	<UrbworldUrchin90>
		<title>Urbvilági utcagyerek</title>
		<titleShort>Utcagyerek</titleShort>
		<desc>Abandoned among the filthy concrete spires, [PAWN_nameDef] never knew [PAWN_possessive] parents. [] never received formal education, and often resorted to doing menial labor in exchange for food. Sometimes [] lied, cheated, and stole to survive.</desc>
	</UrbworldUrchin90>
	<VoidRaider45>
		<title>Void raider</title>
		<titleShort>Raider</titleShort>
		<desc>Craving adventure and glory, [PAWN_nameDef] set out across the void with a raider band, swearing his loyalty to his band and brothers, and spreading their glory through the stars with his blade and pistol in hand.</desc>
	</VoidRaider45>
	<MidworldSketcher73>
		<title>Midworld sketcher</title>
		<titleShort>Sketcher</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into a loving but poor family.

[] discovered he had an artistic talent which he inherited from his father. [PAWN_possessive] mother taught him the benefits of hard work and determination. As he grew older, [PAWN_nameDef] developed a fascination with technology and military history.</desc>
	</MidworldSketcher73>
	<MidworldSailor6>
		<title>Midworld sailor</title>
		<titleShort>Sailor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] joined his country's Royal Navy. After years as a non-commissioned officer, he eventually cracked and used the skills he had acquired to start a mutiny on his ship.

In the end, [PAWN_nameDef] was the leader of a large group of trained and dangerous pirates. He henceforth always had chefs to cook for him.</desc>
	</MidworldSailor6>
	<CoreWorldStudent4>
		<title>Core world student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>Born a male named Alex, Alyssa didn't fit in well with the other boys. When very young, she preferred creative pursuits, such as crafting jewelry, over sports. She felt she had the wrong body. Luckily, her family and friends supported her sex reassignment; as a teen, she underwent surgery to become a female.</desc>
	</CoreWorldStudent4>
	<CoreWorldJeweler59>
		<title>Core world jeweler</title>
		<titleShort>Jeweler</titleShort>
		<desc>After Alyssa had completed all of her surgeries, she found that she had a lot of time and energy to dedicate to her passion: trinket crafting. She spent years perfecting her art as a jeweler, then left her home world to sell her wares across the galaxy.</desc>
	</CoreWorldJeweler59>
	<MedievalSquire61>
		<title>Medieval squire</title>
		<titleShort>Squire</titleShort>
		<desc>William grew up on a medieval planet as a knight in training. He trained directly under the king's war adviser for most of his youth, and learned to fight with a sword and shield.</desc>
	</MedievalSquire61>
	<MedievalKnight71>
		<title>Medieval knight </title>
		<titleShort>Knight</titleShort>
		<desc>William fought for king and country on the battlefield, where he further honed his skill as a swordsman. His greatest glory was leading a charge into an enemy courtroom and capturing the king at sword point.</desc>
	</MedievalKnight71>
	<StarSquire41>
		<title>Star squire</title>
		<titleShort>Squire</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a medieval world, [PAWN_nameDef]'s first memory is of gazing up into the night's sky. 

Ever since, [] dreamed of squiring for a knight amidst the star-filled heavens. [PAWN_possessive] focus on that vision left [PAWN_objective] somewhat single-minded.</desc>
	</StarSquire41>
	<StarKnight68>
		<title>Star knight</title>
		<titleShort>Knight</titleShort>
		<desc>Abducted from his medieval homeworld, [PAWN_nameDef] later escaped his captors via an impressive display of swordsmanship.

For a moment, as he drifted in the escape pod, his childhood dream of becoming a knight among the stars felt so real. Then he crash-landed.</desc>
	</StarKnight68>
	<DrugMule24>
		<title>Drug mule</title>
		<titleShort>Mule</titleShort>
		<desc>Raised in an orphanage, [PAWN_nameDef] turned towards the gang life at age ten.

He was exploited by the local gang as a drug mule to traffic "substance F" across rival gang territory. He took a bullet or two.</desc>
	</DrugMule24>
	<TestSubject85>
		<title>Tesztalany</title>
		<titleShort>Tesztalany</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] enrolled in a scientific study that promised it could make [PAWN_objective] smarter. Unfortunately, the side effects were very different than he expected.[] went insane and killed a number of people before escaping his homeworld.</desc>
	</TestSubject85>
	<ArtisanFarmer23>
		<title>Artisan farmer</title>
		<titleShort>Farmer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a [PAWN_possessive] family's glitterworld farm. They were one of the last farms on the planet that preferred traditional farming methods to glitterworld technology.</desc>
	</ArtisanFarmer23>
	<GeneticEngineer69>
		<title>Genetic engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Geneticist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] carried out [PAWN_possessive] first genetic experiments on farm animals. [] soon grew to become quite skilled in all forms of genetic engineering.

A horrifying lab accident left him with a mortal fear of rodents.</desc>
	</GeneticEngineer69>
	<Pampered39>
		<title>Pampered</title>
		<titleShort>Pampered</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a decadent glitterworld, [PAWN_nameDef] was given every expensive toy.

This pampered lifestyle caused [PAWN_objective] to miss many basic life lessons. [] developed a special aversion to cooking, and always ordered the staff to do the kitchen work.</desc>
	</Pampered39>
	<NinjaAssassin65>
		<title>Ninja assassin</title>
		<titleShort>Ninja</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] performed stiletto-precise assassinations for an interplanetary conglomerate. [] was assigned the most complex missions involving disguise, deception, subterfuge, and efficient violence.

A nasty incident with a potted plant and an assassination gone wrong left [PAWN_objective] with an aversion to plant life.</desc>
	</NinjaAssassin65>
	<MilitaryChild64>
		<title>Military child</title>
		<titleShort>Military</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a family with a rich military background. [PAWN_possessive] teenage years were spent traveling system to system wherever [PAWN_possessive] parents were deployed.

Following the tradition of [PAWN_possessive] family, [] enlisted at the earliest possible age.</desc>
	</MilitaryChild64>
	<LazyProgrammer13>
		<title>Lazy programmer</title>
		<titleShort>Programmer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] independently developed software that had a competitive edge against local urbvilág corporations.

[PAWN_possessive] legally questionable methods lead to a growing number in unsolved claims of intellectual property theft.</desc>
	</LazyProgrammer13>
	<GangMember10>
		<title>Gang member</title>
		<titleShort>Gang kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up without parents. [PAWN_possessive] whole life was spent alone, fighting for survival on the streets.

No matter how hard it became to survive, he never gave up.</desc>
	</GangMember10>
	<MindwipedAssassin89>
		<title>Mindwiped assassin</title>
		<titleShort>Mindwipe</titleShort>
		<desc>The corporation took and remade [PAWN_nameDef]. They trained [PAWN_objective] into an tool of destruction and subversion. [] took to [PAWN_possessive] new life, finding satisfaction in the jobs they sent [PAWN_objective] on.

When [] learned that they planned on disposing of [PAWN_objective], [PAWN_nameDef] turned on his masters, killing several and fleeing the planet.</desc>
	</MindwipedAssassin89>
	<TestSubject32>
		<title>test subject</title>
		<titleShort>subject</titleShort>
		<desc>Test subject #11,529,914 of experiment #56,048 spent her childhood in white rooms performing mental and physical tests.

Her only companion was a voice that called itself Mother. Mother rewarded success with praise - and failure with harsh punishment.</desc>
	</TestSubject32>
	<TestSubject84>
		<title>test subject</title>
		<titleShort>subject</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s tests went from geometry to quantum physics, and she could run the grand gauntlet without a scratch.

One day, Mother said that her final test lay beyond the red door, and that even if she couldn't hear her voice, Mother would always be there.</desc>
	</TestSubject84>
	<FireScarredChild32>
		<title>Fire-scarred child</title>
		<titleShort>Scarred</titleShort>
		<desc>Duster was an active child who lived an uneventful childhood until he fell into a fire and suffered horrific burns to his hands and arms. Although the scars have faded, he can't bear to be in close proximity to fire.</desc>
	</FireScarredChild32>
	<SpaceshipSalesman6>
		<title>Spaceship salesman</title>
		<titleShort>Salesman</titleShort>
		<desc>Duster tried his hand at various jobs, including building space rabbit cages and working at a mutant wheat research project. Finally, he found his true calling as a spacecraft salesman. Specializing in recreational spacecraft, his smooth talk and charming nature served him well.</desc>
	</SpaceshipSalesman6>
	<TechEnthusiast65>
		<title>Tech enthusiast</title>
		<titleShort>Tech nerd</titleShort>
		<desc>Michael had all the latest gadgets as a child. He spent all his time playing games with AIs instead of with other children. He always felt awkward around new people.</desc>
	</TechEnthusiast65>
	<AIProgrammer85>
		<title>AI programmer</title>
		<titleShort>Programmer</titleShort>
		<desc>Michael enlisted in the military's robotics division, developing smarter combat AI.

The whole time he was there, he never spoke with another human. He spent all his time conversing with the AI he was developing.</desc>
	</AIProgrammer85>
	<DiplomatsChild81>
		<title>Diplomat's child</title>
		<titleShort>Diplomat</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born in diplomatic family.

Travelling often, [] was home-schooled and saw the world mostly through a computer.</desc>
	</DiplomatsChild81>
	<WhiteHatHacker82>
		<title>White-hat hacker</title>
		<titleShort>Hacker</titleShort>
		<desc>From [PAWN_possessive] computer, [PAWN_nameDef] helped rid the online world of bad people.</desc>
	</WhiteHatHacker82>
	<Winerunner41>
		<title>Winerunner</title>
		<titleShort>Winerunner</titleShort>
		<desc>Abandoned by his parents, [PAWN_nameDef] was raised by the monks of the Novo Mosteiro dos Jerónimos monastery on Aracena VI.

The monks taught him discipline and hard work. In return, [] would go into the city and 'acquire' exotic wines for the monks' nightly tastings.</desc>
	</Winerunner41>
	<VinhoKing12>
		<title>Vinho king</title>
		<titleShort>Booze king</titleShort>
		<desc>After prohibition came to Aracena VI, [PAWN_nameDef] expanded his underground liquor business until it dominated the market on two continents. They called him the Vinho King.

Though [] mostly controlled his competition by masterful political maneuvering, [] was not above the occasional beat-down or stiletto assassination.</desc>
	</VinhoKing12>
	<StreetChild0>
		<title>Street child</title>
		<titleShort>Street</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s drug addict mother died, leaving [PAWN_objective] an orphan at a young age. To stay alive, [] resorted to theft, and when necessary, prostitution. When [PAWN_nameDef] was caught stealing from a church, the priestess saw a wounded but smart child, and took [PAWN_objective] in to give [PAWN_objective] a second chance at life.</desc>
	</StreetChild0>
	<SlaveChemist84>
		<title>Slave chemist</title>
		<titleShort>Chemist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] became a gifted pharmaceutical scientist, but was captured by slavers. [] was sold to a warlord and forced to create drugs to test on other slaves. This left [PAWN_objective] with deep and troubling questions on the ethics of scientific research and medicine.</desc>
	</SlaveChemist84>
	<SlaveFarmer35>
		<title>Slave farmer</title>
		<titleShort>Slave</titleShort>
		<desc>Abandoned as a little girl, [PAWN_nameDef] was found by a farmer. Being infertile himself, the farmer kept her as a slave. The constant beatings left her scarred and unable to handle violence. After many years, she ran away.</desc>
	</SlaveFarmer35>
	<RocketEngineer31>
		<title>Rocket engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] won a grant to a top school and earned a degree in rocket engineering. After several years working for a space mining company she left to travel and see the universe.</desc>
	</RocketEngineer31>
	<MedievalSlave34>
		<title>Medieval slave</title>
		<titleShort>Slave</titleShort>
		<desc>Born into slavery, Soren never knew his parents. He eventually escaped from his masters and boarded a military cargo ship, where he was pressed into military service.</desc>
	</MedievalSlave34>
	<SpaceMarine27>
		<title>Space marine</title>
		<titleShort>Marine</titleShort>
		<desc>Soren joined a squad of space marines known for their brutal efficiency at killing. His last name and his lack of emotion during combat inspired his nickname: Grim.</desc>
	</SpaceMarine27>
	<FoundryApprentice76>
		<title>Foundry apprentice</title>
		<titleShort>Foundryman</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up as an apprentice in the foundries of an industrial world. This experience gave [PAWN_objective] metalworking skills and strong muscles, but stunted [PAWN_possessive] artistic development.</desc>
	</FoundryApprentice76>
	<CombatEngineer4>
		<title>Utász</title>
		<titleShort>Utász</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] utász volt. Bázisokat épített, fegyvereket  és járműveket javított a hadsereg számára, már amikor nem emberekre lövöldözött.</desc>
	</CombatEngineer4>
	<PrivilegedProdigy55>
		<title>Privileged prodigy</title>
		<titleShort>Prodigy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was recognized as gifted early in his glitterworld upbringing. Luckily, [PAWN_possessive] family was in a position to cultivate that genius through advanced education. [PAWN_possessive] training included science, leadership, and the arts.</desc>
	</PrivilegedProdigy55>
	<PlanetaryDiplomat7>
		<title>Planetary diplomat</title>
		<titleShort>Diplomat</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s passion and profession was interplanetary politics. [] was a master of social manipulation and negotiation and devoted [PAWN_objective]self to working towards peace, compromise and mutual benefit.</desc>
	</PlanetaryDiplomat7>
	<PrivilegedChild4>
		<title>privileged child</title>
		<titleShort>privileged</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to an upper-class family, [PAWN_nameDef] grew up with all the best things - the best education, the best social contacts, and of course the best technology money could buy.

Unfortunately, living in such decadence left [PAWN_nameDef] rather spoiled when it came to labor.</desc>
	</PrivilegedChild4>
	<Guardian97>
		<title>guardian</title>
		<titleShort>guardian</titleShort>
		<desc>After [] learned what truly matters in life, [PAWN_nameDef] changed for the better. [] learned to work hard and protect the things that matter - not money or material things, but friends and loved ones.

[] became a professional guardian.</desc>
	</Guardian97>
	<ChildProdigy22>
		<title>Child prodigy</title>
		<titleShort>Prodigy</titleShort>
		<desc>After graduating college at age twelve, Jered devoted his life to becoming immortal.  However his research crossed the line when he tried to modify his body using gene therapy and mechanical augmentation.  He was arrested and condemned to a prison planet.</desc>
	</ChildProdigy22>
	<RenegadeEngineer65>
		<title>Renegade engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>After a daring escape from the prison planet with a small crew of fellow inmates, Jered set his gaze on his homeworld.

He travelled there, recruited more followers, hijacked a space cruiser, and launched into the void.</desc>
	</RenegadeEngineer65>
	<BoneCollector52>
		<title>Bone collector</title>
		<titleShort>Pupil</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to a family of fortune hunters, [PAWN_nameDef] always had a passion for ancient history.

Though never a tough or social boy, [] loved to dig through history books as well as dirt piles.</desc>
	</BoneCollector52>
	<Osteologist66>
		<title>Osteologist</title>
		<titleShort>Scholar</titleShort>
		<desc>After graduating university at the top of his class, [PAWN_nameDef] quickly became a well-known and athletic college professor.

With his new found fame and fitness came a sudden reluctance to preform menial labor - such tasks are better left to graduate students.</desc>
	</Osteologist66>
	<GNomeSculptor45>
		<title>G-nome sculptor</title>
		<titleShort>Sculptor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was engineered in a lab as part of the G-nome Project. He was implanted at birth with encyclopedic knowledge of all aspects of xenobiology.

The G-nome scientists nicknamed him Gizmo and occupied him with sculpting. He developed a love of sculpting gnomes and gnome accessories.</desc>
	</GNomeSculptor45>
	<Gnomebiologist50>
		<title>Gnomebiologist</title>
		<titleShort>Biologist</titleShort>
		<desc>Gizmo was a xenobiology professor in a glitterworld university. He went to conferences and managed an art gallery.

However, he never stopped sculpting yard gnomes, and considers this to be his true profession.</desc>
	</Gnomebiologist50>
	<CircusPerformer87>
		<title>Circus performer</title>
		<titleShort>Performer</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up in the circus, [PAWN_nameDef] learned a lot of interesting things. More interesting then the balls he juggled were the pockets he picked between shows.

A mistake with some firesticks made him develop a deathly fear of fire.</desc>
	</CircusPerformer87>
	<CriminalKingpin47>
		<title>Criminal kingpin</title>
		<titleShort>Kingpin</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] discovered his gift - people did what he said, when he said it. Taking advantage of this, he set off for the rimworlds planets to make a name for himself in the criminal underworld.

Having people do things for him taught him to avoid manual labor at all costs.</desc>
	</CriminalKingpin47>
	<VatgrownSlavegirl4>
		<title>Vatgrown slavegirl</title>
		<titleShort>Slave girl</titleShort>
		<desc>Emmie was vat-grown as a slave in an illegal urbvilág laboratory. As a young child, she was taught only to cook, clean and serve her masters. For most of her childhood, she knew nothing else.</desc>
	</VatgrownSlavegirl4>
	<UrbworldSexSlave3>
		<title>Urbworld sex slave</title>
		<titleShort>Sex slave</titleShort>
		<desc>Emmie was sold into sexual slavery. Having been designed to be inhumanly attractive and too weak to rebel against her masters, she was passed between dozens of owners and knew nothing of freedom.</desc>
	</UrbworldSexSlave3>
	<GunKid23>
		<title>Gun kid</title>
		<titleShort>Gun kid</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up in a urbvilág, [PAWN_nameDef] never had it easy. Every day was a struggle and pollution, hunger, and gangs of older kids.

In the little space he had to himself, he studied his passion - guns, combat tactics, and war history.</desc>
	</GunKid23>
	<UrbworldSergeant29>
		<title>Urbworld sergeant</title>
		<titleShort>Sergeant</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s passion for all things militaristic kept with him all the way to adulthood.

After enrolling as a local policeman, he was soon promoted to sergeant.</desc>
	</UrbworldSergeant29>
	<FeudalLordling43>
		<title>Feudal lordling</title>
		<titleShort>Lordling</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a feudal world that was part of a multi-planet empire. As the son of a high lord, [] enjoyed many privileges.

[] learned to maneuver in the both the political landscape and in close quarters combat.</desc>
	</FeudalLordling43>
	<SystemLord80>
		<title>System lord</title>
		<titleShort>Lord</titleShort>
		<desc>For [PAWN_nameDef], ruling a country, or even a planet, was not good enough. [] sought to expand his influence across the system - by legal or extralegal means.</desc>
	</SystemLord80>
	<FeudalFarmBoy93>
		<title>Feudal farm boy</title>
		<titleShort>Slave</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was the son of a medieval farmer, and was expected to follow in his footsteps. He was brought up as a kind, well trained farm boy.

He lived in an unusual feudal kingdom which co-existed with a midworld society which was itself well-known for genetic manipulation.</desc>
	</FeudalFarmBoy93>
	<HunterOfTheKing84>
		<title>Hunter of the king</title>
		<titleShort>Pest guard</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was forced to protect his colony in the name of the king after a mysterious outbreak of murderous genetically-modified wildlife.

Despite his best efforts, his kingdom was destroyed. [PAWN_nameDef] developed PTSD, a hatred of animals and a bad case of technophobia. [] was named for the place they found him.</desc>
	</HunterOfTheKing84>
	<SpaceFanboy44>
		<title>Space fanboy</title>
		<titleShort>Fanboy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] dreamed of space travel. He built his own pretend spaceship from an old police box and went to see the great unknown.</desc>
	</SpaceFanboy44>
	<Castaway87>
		<title>Számkivetett</title>
		<titleShort>Számkivetett</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a passenger on a routine interstellar transit. When his ship was destroyed, he lived as a castaway on an uninhabited planet for several years.</desc>
	</Castaway87>
	<GlitterworldNerd18>
		<title>Glitterworld nerd</title>
		<titleShort>Nerd</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] loved technology from the day [] was born. [] had a mechanoid companion which [] tried to modify when [] was 10.

[PAWN_possessive] obsession with technology meant that [] never appreciated arts or culture.</desc>
	</GlitterworldNerd18>
	<EnergyResearcher67>
		<title>Energy researcher</title>
		<titleShort>Researcher</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was working on an idea for rapid communication over long distances. [] made an error which destroyed [PAWN_possessive] lab and most of the city. [] fled the planet to escape the authorities.</desc>
	</EnergyResearcher67>
	<WarChild73>
		<title>War child</title>
		<titleShort>War child</titleShort>
		<desc>Mushinto's parents were drafted into a civil war in his home country. Growing up surrounded by fighting and death, he became well-accustomed to tragedy and tough as nails. His expressive side, however, never developed.</desc>
	</WarChild73>
	<BountyHunter22>
		<title>Bounty hunter</title>
		<titleShort>Hunter</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a bounty hunter on a massive glitterworld. [] worked sensitive assignments for extremely wealthy clients, and was known for quiet execution and total discretion.</desc>
	</BountyHunter22>
	<UpperUrbworlder31>
		<title>Upper urbworlder</title>
		<titleShort>High urber</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] had a privileged childhood on a major urbvilág. Living in an apartment far above the dense poverty of the city, [] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] time reading or drawing the cityscape he saw through [PAWN_possessive] window.</desc>
	</UpperUrbworlder31>
	<Missionary99>
		<title>Missionary</title>
		<titleShort>Missionary</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] decided to devote [PAWN_possessive] life to religious service. [] made a vow of peace and spent several years preaching and serving food in soup kitchens for the homeless.</desc>
	</Missionary99>
	<IdealisticCadet67>
		<title>Idealistic cadet</title>
		<titleShort>Cadet</titleShort>
		<desc>Raised in the military traditions of his forefathers, [PAWN_nameDef] was taught from a young age that he would be a great leader and the hero of the Dichter family.

He excelled at his studies and graduated from the academy with honors.</desc>
	</IdealisticCadet67>
	<MercenaryPilot93>
		<title>Mercenary pilot</title>
		<titleShort>Mercenary</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] convinced his squadron to abscond with their ships and make a course for the rim worlds. There they could fight for the causes they believed in.

His men were loyal and fought hard, but their ideals soon faded away and their cause became that of the highest bidder.</desc>
	</MercenaryPilot93>
	<ChildOfGlass31>
		<title>Child of glass</title>
		<titleShort>Survivor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised underground on a "marble" planet - a wasteland of radioactive asphalt and toxic fallout.

To survive on a planet devoid of life, [] had to learn how to farm underground and how to fight without wasting bullets.</desc>
	</ChildOfGlass31>
	<LoneTraveler91>
		<title>Lone traveler</title>
		<titleShort>Traveler</titleShort>
		<desc>After escaping [PAWN_possessive] homeworld on a jury-rigged ship, [PAWN_nameDef] traveled to new worlds to experience their beauty.

[] joined resistance groups and applied the skills [] cultivated on [PAWN_possessive] homeworld. [] often warned of the nuclear horror [] saw as a child.</desc>
	</LoneTraveler91>
	<AmateurBotanist14>
		<title>Amateur botanist</title>
		<titleShort>Botanist</titleShort>
		<desc>Spending many summers crawling through dirt, Christian found he had quite the green thumb. Instead of learning to cook the food he grew, he just grew more and more.</desc>
	</AmateurBotanist14>
	<Undertaker26>
		<title>Undertaker</title>
		<titleShort>Undertaker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] roamed the galaxy offering grief assistance to those who've had a recent loss. While he never shied away from physical confrontation, he prefers to confront tough situations with a calm word.</desc>
	</Undertaker26>
	<ChildSlave6>
		<title>Child slave</title>
		<titleShort>Slave</titleShort>
		<desc>Graham was born to a poor family on a rimworld. His father sold him into slavery at a young age and he was traded many times. A tycoon bought him as part of a child labor force and sent down into mines to look after machines and to work alongside them.</desc>
	</ChildSlave6>
	<Mercenary75>
		<title>Mercenary</title>
		<titleShort>Mercenary</titleShort>
		<desc>After escaping a crew of rimworld slavers, Graham developed a lack of respect for life. He proceeded to sign on to a mercenary group where he developed skills using guns and survival techniques. Graham did dirty work where he found it, and traveled to many worlds.</desc>
	</Mercenary75>
	<AdventuringChild46>
		<title>Adventuring child</title>
		<titleShort>Adventurer</titleShort>
		<desc>Axle was raised to become an engineer. For years, he planned to stow away on a cargo ship and start a new, more adventuresome life.

One night, after his parents fell asleep, he managed to sneak on board a cargo ship just before it left port.</desc>
	</AdventuringChild46>
	<HiredAssassin2>
		<title>Hired assassin</title>
		<titleShort>Assassin</titleShort>
		<desc>Axle was a master thief, working mostly for organized crime. Over time, he made a name for himself and shifted his business into the paid "removal" of human threats.</desc>
	</HiredAssassin2>
	<VideoGamer91>
		<title>Video gamer</title>
		<titleShort>Gamer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a midworld, mostly locked in [PAWN_possessive] room, playing video games. [] was warm-hearted, with a deep fondness for animals.

As [] grew up, [] turned to drugs to enhance his reality. During these trying times [] found passion and refuge in the gym.</desc>
	</VideoGamer91>
	<SpaceshipChef34>
		<title>Spaceship chef</title>
		<titleShort>Chef</titleShort>
		<desc>Ryan got a spot on a ship by becoming the ship's cook. He enjoyed cooking and helping the doctor clean wounds, but he never got used to cleaning the dishes.</desc>
	</SpaceshipChef34>
	<DreadedBaby46>
		<title>Dreaded baby</title>
		<titleShort>Baby dude</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was found as a baby in a crashed spacecraft. According to the ship's data records, [] invented the nuclear device that powered his ship. Apparently, he also invented the sky and the hamburger, and is said to have fathered a race of tasty golden kittens.</desc>
	</DreadedBaby46>
	<DreadedDude16>
		<title>Dreaded dude</title>
		<titleShort>Dude</titleShort>
		<desc>Some followers say that [PAWN_nameDef] and [PAWN_possessive] crew of misfits found the Fountain of Youth, many, many centuries ago, and that they caused the extinction of the dinosaurs on many planets.

There's even a religion about them, somewhere, involving noodles and meatballs.</desc>
	</DreadedDude16>
	<Tinkerer43>
		<title>Tinkerer</title>
		<titleShort>Tinkerer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a scrap-heap of a planet - the garbage dump of other planets in the system. He learned to make new machines from the dead parts of old ones. With some friends, he eventually escaped on a salvaged and repaired ship.</desc>
	</Tinkerer43>
	<Engineer47>
		<title>Engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] found a job as a tinkering engineer on the trading hub planet Irithir. Tough local traders forced him to learn negotiation skills, and he made good profits selling refurbished weapons and tools.</desc>
	</Engineer47>
	<DisplacedNoble83>
		<title>Displaced noble</title>
		<titleShort>Noble</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on an urbvilág to the ruler of three megacities, [PAWN_nameDef]’s prospects looked good - until a violent insurrection overthrew [PAWN_possessive] family. Exile introduced [PAWN_nameDef] to hard work and combat, but some high-born squeamishness remains.</desc>
	</DisplacedNoble83>
	<Minister88>
		<title>Minister</title>
		<titleShort>Minister</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] managed to secure an important position in the government of a minor glitterworld. [] got used to the opulence, while attempting to keep [PAWN_possessive] citizens content. [] had ample time for pleasure and indulgence – though [] never forgot how to do hard work.</desc>
	</Minister88>
	<ChessMaster6>
		<title>Chess master</title>
		<titleShort>Chesshead</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] loved to play chess. [] even earned the nickname Bishop for some of [PAWN_possessive] craftier moves. 

[] never got into trouble - mostly because he was good at not getting caught.</desc>
	</ChessMaster6>
	<Pirate3>
		<title>Pirate</title>
		<titleShort>Pirate</titleShort>
		<desc>As a pirate leader, Bishop was well-known for his cunning plans and chess-like traps. [] was never afraid to sacrifice a few pawns to capture an important target.

[PAWN_possessive] name has been linked more then once to strategies that overcame overwhelming odds.</desc>
	</Pirate3>
	<Orphan86>
		<title>Orphan</title>
		<titleShort>Orphan</titleShort>
		<desc>Born in a brothel on a harsh world, [PAWN_nameDef] never really had a childhood. [] did odd jobs to survive, and became distant from others.</desc>
	</Orphan86>
	<BountyHunter8>
		<title>Fejvadász</title>
		<titleShort>Fejvadász</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a self-employed bounty hunter. [] spent [PAWN_possessive] days hunting space pirates and collecting cash bounties.</desc>
	</BountyHunter8>
	<Straggler4>
		<title>Straggler</title>
		<titleShort>Straggler</titleShort>
		<desc>Despite being blessed with parental love, [PAWN_nameDef] hardly knew his parents.

[] was frequently left to his own devices which meant more time devoted to exploring his interests…and getting into trouble.</desc>
	</Straggler4>
	<Spiceminer20>
		<title>Spiceminer</title>
		<titleShort>Spiceminer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] made his mark on the universe as a spice miner assigned to the lucrative mining colony of Rural Pen’The.

Little did he know, Benn was about to embark on a career path that would change his life.</desc>
	</Spiceminer20>
	<BrutalThief83>
		<title>Brutal thief</title>
		<titleShort>Thief</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up in a gang, [PAWN_nameDef] learned the brutality of the streets.

Knowing that showing weakness could be fatal, he closed himself of to others.</desc>
	</BrutalThief83>
	<CrimeLord42>
		<title>Crime lord</title>
		<titleShort>Crime lord</titleShort>
		<desc>Through brutality and cruelty, [PAWN_nameDef] rose to the rank of crime lord.

He relied less on his fists and more on his guns. His reputation spread faster due to his cold-bloodedness and ruthless methods.</desc>
	</CrimeLord42>
	<BoySoldier88>
		<title>Boy soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>War may never change - but the cast of characters does.

Born on a violent urbvilág, [PAWN_nameDef] was trained from a young age to fight the wars of others, and became rather good at it.</desc>
	</BoySoldier88>
	<MarbleDoctor8>
		<title>Marble doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Doctor</titleShort>
		<desc>On a bomb-blasted world, first aid is often the only aid.

[PAWN_nameDef] used his medical skills to help the injured and the sick. [] believed that while guns and machines may be powerful, a doctor is even more so.</desc>
	</MarbleDoctor8>
	<ApocalypseChild3>
		<title>Apocalypse child </title>
		<titleShort>Apocalypse</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent his childhood on a post-apocalyptic world. He fought for survival from a young age, on a planet where trust did not exist.

He told everyone that he had no luck.</desc>
	</ApocalypseChild3>
	<MobHenchman24>
		<title>Mob henchman</title>
		<titleShort>Henchman</titleShort>
		<desc>After being "saved" from his home world by a slaver ship, [PAWN_nameDef] was sold to an urbvilág crime lord, where he was used as a henchman. He specialized in low-tech beat-downs and intimidation.</desc>
	</MobHenchman24>
	<OrphanOfWar9>
		<title>Orphan of war</title>
		<titleShort>Orphan</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lost his family and home early in life. His life became emotionally hollow, but his painful memories drove him to survive.

[] took several jobs, but never achieved more than a basic education.</desc>
	</OrphanOfWar9>
	<MechWarVeteran31>
		<title>Mech war veteran</title>
		<titleShort>Veteran</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] fought against swarms of rogue mechanoids since he was old enough to enlist. [] has bled on half a dozen worlds and has lost more than he cares to recall. These experiences left him hardened, both mentally and physically.</desc>
	</MechWarVeteran31>
	<ImperialStudent49>
		<title>Imperial student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] studied on an imperial midworld where guns were banned and self-defense study was encouraged. The relative safety allowed [PAWN_objective] to focus on [PAWN_possessive] botanical research.</desc>
	</ImperialStudent49>
	<PoisonGardener95>
		<title>Poison gardener</title>
		<titleShort>Botanist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent almost all [PAWN_possessive] time tending to a poison garden and became withdrawn from society.

In that time [] learnt a few safe culinary and medicinal uses for the otherwise deadly plants.</desc>
	</PoisonGardener95>
	<PowerMadScholar11>
		<title>Power-mad scholar</title>
		<titleShort>Scholar</titleShort>
		<desc>"Knowledge is power." These words sparked something within [PAWN_nameDef], and came to form his core drive. When not entombed within libraries, [] would take things apart to see first-hand how they worked, with little regard for the border between mechanical and organic.</desc>
	</PowerMadScholar11>
	<ArtificerRampant14>
		<title>Artificer rampant</title>
		<titleShort>Artificer</titleShort>
		<desc>Fuelled by the thrill of discovery and his own megalomania, [PAWN_nameDef] set out to invent new devices and improve existing ones, breaking laws and customs as necessary.

[] formed a crew to gather materials for [PAWN_possessive] work - and to deal with outsiders who might interfere.</desc>
	</ArtificerRampant14>
	<TechHead3>
		<title>Tech-head</title>
		<titleShort>Tech-head</titleShort>
		<desc>Standing on the ship hull with his father in an child-size EVA suit, [PAWN_nameDef] loved space from a young age.

[] was put in a Civil Academics Program. While pretending to be like [PAWN_possessive] father, [] spent [PAWN_possessive] time taking care of plants in [PAWN_possessive] messy room. [PAWN_possessive] nickname was given for [PAWN_possessive] love of circles.</desc>
	</TechHead3>
	<SystemsEngineer17>
		<title>Systems engineer </title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>Like [PAWN_possessive] father, [PAWN_nameDef] was a systems engineer. [] was qualified in both colony and ship systems.

When not working, [] would make mechanical figurines, read old books, or occasionally travel to uncharted worlds. Being introverted, [] did these things mostly alone.</desc>
	</SystemsEngineer17>
	<Orphan63>
		<title>orphan</title>
		<titleShort>orphan</titleShort>
		<desc>Left alone in the world without parents, Kevin did the best he could to adapt.

Having to take care both of himself and younger kids at the orphanage, he learned a lot about humans and how to interact with them.</desc>
	</Orphan63>
	<NeuroScientist34>
		<title>Neuro scientist</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>Kevin worked for a long time to improve the world's understanding of the human brain.

After succeeding in mapping the whole brain, Kevin joined a team of scientist on a quest to map the brains of xeno species.</desc>
	</NeuroScientist34>
	<Abductee43>
		<title>Abductee</title>
		<titleShort>Abductee</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was abducted by xenohumans when [] was still a baby. They experimented on [PAWN_objective] to understand his genetic structure.

As [] grew up, [PAWN_nameDef] grew a little bit too big and strong for his captors and eventually escaped.</desc>
	</Abductee43>
	<PirateCaptain84>
		<title>Pirate captain</title>
		<titleShort>Captain</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked his way up through the ranks of a pirate ship, eventually becoming captain. He leads his crew between worlds, making a name to remember.</desc>
	</PirateCaptain84>
	<BlackjackPlayer64>
		<title>Blackjack player</title>
		<titleShort>Gambler</titleShort>
		<desc>The only useful skill [PAWN_nameDef] learned from his tough military school was card counting. He amassed many enemies by cheating at casinos, becoming ever more edgy and violent as the threat of retaliation grew.

When he was finally caught, they burned half his skin off. He'll never be able to face fire or violence again.</desc>
	</BlackjackPlayer64>
	<HedgeFundManager45>
		<title>Hedge fund manager</title>
		<titleShort>Banker</titleShort>
		<desc>A top hedge fund manager on a teeming urbvilág, [PAWN_nameDef]'s portfolio grew rapidly as he charmed clients with a sweet voice and devious intent. When the deal turned out too good to be true, he was forced to flee the planet with a bounty on his head.

As he travelled the stars he found a passion in the arts, making masterpieces fit for high society customers.</desc>
	</HedgeFundManager45>
	<AcademyStudent38>
		<title>Academy student </title>
		<titleShort>Student </titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] went to school like a good space cadet would. He was very tall and was known for his good looks.

Though he worried more about his hairstyle than his grades, he still somehow passed the final exams.</desc>
	</AcademyStudent38>
	<ComputerEngineer94>
		<title>Computer engineer </title>
		<titleShort>Tech head</titleShort>
		<desc>Bored of his code-monkey office job and missing the glory days of the Academy, [PAWN_nameDef] saw a commercial about the frontier where "only the strong survive".

With his wife Morgan, [PAWN_nameDef] undertook a journey into the unknown.</desc>
	</ComputerEngineer94>
	<AspiringEngineer92>
		<title>Aspiring engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Tinkerer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] had a fascination with gadgets and gizmos. [] took apart and put together almost anything [] could find.

[] got used to repairing toys brought to [PAWN_objective] by other children, and even fixed a few devices from [PAWN_possessive] elders.</desc>
	</AspiringEngineer92>
	<ExpertHandyman34>
		<title>Expert handyman</title>
		<titleShort>Handyman</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a traveling engineer. [] fixed things ranging from a simple communications array to the intricate software harness in his ship's AI meta-core. Nothing is beyond repair for [PAWN_objective].</desc>
	</ExpertHandyman34>
	<MedicalStudent46>
		<title>Medical student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>Born into a long line of doctors, [PAWN_nameDef] was tutored in all fields of medicine, from herbal ointments to the modern synthetic drugs. [] also picked up a healthy disdain for lower class work.</desc>
	</MedicalStudent46>
	<MedicSoldier92>
		<title>Medic soldier </title>
		<titleShort>Medic</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] enrolled in his planetary army as a frontline medic. He soon knew the horrors of war and was deeply marked by them.

[] left the military and his homeworld and began researching medicine and helping those he came across.</desc>
	</MedicSoldier92>
	<HighBaroness81>
		<title>High baroness</title>
		<titleShort>Noble</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born as low-ranking royalty in a large imperial family.

She was placed In charge of running her home planet from an early age, and learned important political and cultural skills in that role.</desc>
	</HighBaroness81>
	<ExiledResearcher68>
		<title>Exiled researcher</title>
		<titleShort>Exile</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s love of robotics was not appreciated in her technophobic empire. The High Cardinal of the system excommunicated her, and she was never allowed to return.</desc>
	</ExiledResearcher68>
	<WorldSlider56>
		<title>World slider</title>
		<titleShort>Slider</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised by a world-hopping band of criminals. [] learned not to leave evidence of his presence in case the group had to leave in a hurry. [] also learned about medicine and hand-to-hand combat from his fellow criminals.</desc>
	</WorldSlider56>
	<Villain66>
		<title>Villain</title>
		<titleShort>Villain</titleShort>
		<desc>After rising to the top of his criminal band, [PAWN_nameDef] was taught the arts of villainy, from handling firearms to developing new weapons technologies. He excelled at bending others to his will.</desc>
	</Villain66>
	<MedicalStudent38>
		<title>Medikus</title>
		<titleShort>Medikus</titleShort>
		<desc>Born into a long line of doctors, [PAWN_nameDef] was tutored in all fields of medicine, from herbal ointments to the modern synthetic drugs. [] also picked up a healthy disdain for lower class work.</desc>
	</MedicalStudent38>
	<SpaceNavyDoctor72>
		<title>Space navy doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Doctor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] served several tours as a doctor on one of the few warships defending [PAWN_possessive] homeworld. [] learned combat skills while fighting occasional pirate boarding parties, and became an expert at treating gruesome combat wounds.</desc>
	</SpaceNavyDoctor72>
	<AspergersRebel92>
		<title>Aspergers rebel</title>
		<titleShort>Rebel</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up as a rebel on an formerly-advanced rimworld devastated by war.

[PAWN_possessive] Aspergers syndrome meant he struggled with social situations and was incapable of caring, but [] learned hard skills like research and shooting very quickly.</desc>
	</AspergersRebel92>
	<GovernmentAgent83>
		<title>Government agent  </title>
		<titleShort>Agent</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked for the government against rebel groups and excelled in this capacity. During [PAWN_possessive] training [] was taught firearms, melee combat and medical skills.

Having grown up in a war-ravaged city, dirt, blood and dead bodies don’t bother [PAWN_objective] and [] sees no reason to clean them up.</desc>
	</GovernmentAgent83>
	<ShootingComa31>
		<title>Shooting coma</title>
		<titleShort>Coma child</titleShort>
		<desc>Nebulys fell into a coma at a young age and spent years dreaming about shooting. When he awoke, he was useless at most tasks - but he could aim pretty well.</desc>
	</ShootingComa31>
	<SelflessHunter25>
		<title>Selfless hunter</title>
		<titleShort>Hunter</titleShort>
		<desc>Nebulys was a hunter of mysterious creatures that many didn't even believe existed. Sometimes the people were right - and sometimes they were wrong.

Along the way, he helped people in need.</desc>
	</SelflessHunter25>
	<PsychologyStudent50>
		<title>Psychology student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] researched new religions and traditions and often dreamt of distant stars. 

His dreams prompted him to ask what lay beyond the lights in the sky.</desc>
	</PsychologyStudent50>
	<AcolyteOfStars49>
		<title>Acolyte of stars</title>
		<titleShort>Priest</titleShort>
		<desc>Ever the dreamer, [PAWN_nameDef] traveled across the universe to find the thing he felt was calling to him.

[] became poorer and poorer, but used every means possible to carry on.</desc>
	</AcolyteOfStars49>
	<SpaceSmuggler32>
		<title>Space smuggler</title>
		<titleShort>Smuggler</titleShort>
		<desc>Tater's parents used him to help smuggle contraband between a cluster of rim worlds.

Aided by his small size, Tater became very adept at carrying out his parents' missions, learning weaponry, negotiations, and most of all smuggling.</desc>
	</SpaceSmuggler32>
	<SpaceRaider65>
		<title>Space raider</title>
		<titleShort>Raider</titleShort>
		<desc>Tater was the leader of a spaceborne pirate crew. Skipping between the rim worlds, he became the feared enemy of many settlements.</desc>
	</SpaceRaider65>
	<Abductee38>
		<title>abductee</title>
		<titleShort>abductee</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was abducted by xenohumans when [] was still a baby. They experimented on [PAWN_objective] to understand his genetic structure.

As [] grew up, [PAWN_nameDef] grew a little bit too big and strong for his captors and eventually escaped.</desc>
	</Abductee38>
	<Spy58>
		<title>Spy</title>
		<titleShort>Spy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was trained by [PAWN_possessive] government in infiltration and espionage. [] learned to keep a cool head and to talk [PAWN_possessive] way out of tight situations. When talking didn't work, [] was capable of more violent direct action.</desc>
	</Spy58>
	<BlessedChild20>
		<title>Blessed child</title>
		<titleShort>Blessed</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born under auspicious circumstances to a midworld spiritual group and held in reverence throughout [PAWN_possessive] childhood.

[] learned to take care of the poor and give succor to the faithful from an early age.</desc>
	</BlessedChild20>
	<WanderingHealer6>
		<title>Wandering healer</title>
		<titleShort>Healer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] studied to be a doctor, but was dissatisfied with [PAWN_possessive] practice on an otherwise peaceful midworld.

Instead, [] chose to pull up roots and travel to the rimworlds in order to care for people who needed [PAWN_objective] most.</desc>
	</WanderingHealer6>
	<YouthSoldier97>
		<title>Youth soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to a long line of soldiers, [PAWN_nameDef] joined a military training program.

[] excelled in physical training, and even passed most of the intellectual exams. While [] was never particularly bright or nimble, [PAWN_nameDef] learned the value of hard work and suffering.</desc>
	</YouthSoldier97>
	<VeteranSoldier76>
		<title>Veteran soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] fought many tours against pirates, rebels, and xenos. He endured the glory and horrors of war.

Worn down by drills, wars, and battle scars, [PAWN_nameDef] 'retired' to the easy soldier life of colonial civility enforcement. He spent his days polishing his war medals, knowing he had done his bloodline proud.</desc>
	</VeteranSoldier76>
	<GlitterworldKid57>
		<title>Glitterworld kid</title>
		<titleShort>Glit kid</titleShort>
		<desc>The son of a genetically-engineered "perfect mate" on a glitterworld, Chaz was much more shy, withdrawn and nervous than his parents. [] kept mostly to himself, studying science and medicine and taking on gardening as a hobby. 

In [PAWN_possessive] teens, [] ran away from home, seeking a quieter life.</desc>
	</GlitterworldKid57>
	<CosmeticReject25>
		<title>Cosmetic reject</title>
		<titleShort>Reject</titleShort>
		<desc>Living on the streets, Chaz submitted himself to an unethical cosmetics lab in exchange for food and shelter.

After some painful cosmetic modification, Chaz barely resembles his former self. Having been forced to work for the lab until he was rescued, Chaz is now too afraid to lash out at anyone.</desc>
	</CosmeticReject25>
	<FeralChild1>
		<title>feral child</title>
		<titleShort>survivor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] and his family lived a hard but prosperous lives along with their fellow colonists on a distant rimworld.

One day a group of mechanoids attacked, killing everyone aside from Robert. He then lived alone in the desert until a group of raiders found him.</desc>
	</FeralChild1>
	<RaiderKing46>
		<title>Raider king</title>
		<titleShort>Raider</titleShort>
		<desc>Starting as nothing more than a slave, [PAWN_nameDef] rose quickly among the raider ranks until all knew his name and his ruthlessness.</desc>
	</RaiderKing46>
	<Scout80>
		<title>scout</title>
		<titleShort>scout</titleShort>
		<desc>Nate loved being outdoors. His parents enrolled him in a program that taught military scouting skills. He thrived when he was left alone in the wilderness.

Due to this upbringing, however, [PAWN_nameDef] did not learn the basic technological skills that are taken for granted by many others.</desc>
	</Scout80>
	<FrontierMarshal24>
		<title>frontier marshal</title>
		<titleShort>marshal</titleShort>
		<desc>Nate was the marshal of his colony. He tried to honorably uphold the law, but the corrupt local mayor killed his family and left him for dead.

After regaining his health, Nate arrested the mayor. [] left his homeworld and started a new life working to make a difference in the universe.</desc>
	</FrontierMarshal24>
	<TraineeAlchemist86>
		<title>Trainee alchemist</title>
		<titleShort>Alchemist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a medieval world. He learned the basics of alchemy and medicine in one the few monastic schools on his planet.</desc>
	</TraineeAlchemist86>
	<ReligiousHierarch35>
		<title>Religious hierarch</title>
		<titleShort>Hierarch</titleShort>
		<desc>Ordained as a priest in his local community, [PAWN_nameDef] used intrigue and diplomacy to rise to the higher echelon of the clergy. He held numerous titles and lands.

One day, a merchant landed his spaceship near [PAWN_nameDef]'s home. [] decided to accompany the merchant in search for new worlds and challenges.</desc>
	</ReligiousHierarch35>
	<MilitaryCadet54>
		<title>military cadet</title>
		<titleShort>cadet</titleShort>
		<desc>Orphaned as a child, [PAWN_nameDef] was sent to a secret military school on a harsh deadworld.

Taking quickly to firearms and survival training, [] graduated with honor, transitioning into a leadership position in covert operations.</desc>
	</MilitaryCadet54>
	<AnarchistRebel35>
		<title>anarchist rebel</title>
		<titleShort>anarchist</titleShort>
		<desc>After being abandoned on a special operation, [PAWN_nameDef] swore vengeance upon the state. [] formed an anarchist group dedicated to bringing down core world governments.

After too many close calls, and too few successes, [PAWN_nameDef] fled to the outer rim.</desc>
	</AnarchistRebel35>
	<Pickpocket19>
		<title>zsebmetsző</title>
		<titleShort>zsebmetsző</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] witnessed [PAWN_possessive] parents' murder at a young age. With no guidance, [] had to fend for [PAWN_objective]self any way possible. Joining a small group of misfits [] did whatever was necessary to survive.</desc>
	</Pickpocket19>
	<CriminalSurgeon51>
		<title>Criminal surgeon</title>
		<titleShort>Surgeon</titleShort>
		<desc>Being near many injured fellow criminals, [PAWN_nameDef] took it upon [PAWN_objective]self to work on them.

Although many people died, [] did get better at using knives.</desc>
	</CriminalSurgeon51>
	<SpaceCadet74>
		<title>Space cadet</title>
		<titleShort>cadet</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up on a rural farm-world leaves little opportunity for excitement and adventure, so when the Royal Fleet began a recruiting program on his home planet, Jake threw down his hoe and cattle prod to took up arms for the crown.

He served on the interplanetary super-destroyer HMS Thunder-Child.</desc>
	</SpaceCadet74>
	<SanitationCaptain74>
		<title>Sanitation captain</title>
		<titleShort>Janitor </titleShort>
		<desc>After graduating officer training school, Jake was assigned to main battle deck on the Thunder-Child. He served there for a year before his "gallant" actions saw him reassigned to the maintenance corps.

It was with the maintenance corps he was dubbed Table on account of his legs.</desc>
	</SanitationCaptain74>
	<Naturalist22>
		<title>Naturalist</title>
		<titleShort>Naturalist</titleShort>
		<desc>Mitch grew up on a backwater planet with minimal education. He had to hunt and grow food to survive.

[PAWN_possessive] family's home was frequently raided for food by scavengers. This made Mitch very suspicious and slow to trust anyone he doesn't know.</desc>
	</Naturalist22>
	<OverwatchSniper35>
		<title>Overwatch sniper</title>
		<titleShort>Sniper</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] didn't know why he joined the military, but he stayed to protect his fellow soldiers.

Army life broke him down and built him back up. It taught him marksmanship, hand to hand combat and how to patch a bullet wound in a hurry.</desc>
	</OverwatchSniper35>
	<Drudge29>
		<title>Drudge</title>
		<titleShort>Drudge</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was never sure what [] wanted to do with [PAWN_possessive] life. [] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] time doing low-wage jobs and wondering what [PAWN_possessive] future would be like.

[] entertained himself with space sims and survival games, dreaming of one day being somewhere more interesting.</desc>
	</Drudge29>
	<Sightseer43>
		<title>sightseer</title>
		<titleShort>sightseer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled the stars. [] could barely scrape together travel costs doing odd-jobs on stations, but it was all worth it.

[] loved camping on exotic worlds and learning the patterns of strange wildlife. [] never could focus on intellectual endeavors, as [PAWN_possessive] sightseeing distracted [PAWN_objective] far too much.</desc>
	</Sightseer43>
	<BunkerKid18>
		<title>bunker kid</title>
		<titleShort>bunker kid</titleShort>
		<desc>Ricardo grew up in an underground shelter, waiting for radioactive fallout to subside. His rich family had gained access to a luxury bunker city, while billions died on the surface.

Determined to one day seek revenge against the hated enemy, Ricardo spent most of his time practicing shooting in his private training facility.</desc>
	</BunkerKid18>
	<GameTester24>
		<title>game tester</title>
		<titleShort>tester</titleShort>
		<desc>Making a new life on a barely-livable planet after nuclear war, [PAWN_nameDef] was able to fulfill his desires with money borrowed from his father.

He loved playing a particular colony simulator. His favorite thing to do in the game was to build elaborate hospitals. Spending most of his time playing, he forgot horrors of war and his need for revenge.</desc>
	</GameTester24>
	<ChildOfDrifters28>
		<title>Child of drifters</title>
		<titleShort>Drifter</titleShort>
		<desc>Ever since [] was very small, [PAWN_nameDef] had never known a home beyond [PAWN_possessive] parent's ship. They were a family of nomads whose meandering provided a constant change of scenery. [PAWN_possessive] life was often perilous but never dull, and [] inherited [PAWN_possessive] parents' wanderlust at a young age.</desc>
	</ChildOfDrifters28>
	<WanderingCrafter23>
		<title>Wandering crafter</title>
		<titleShort>Crafter</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] continued to follow [PAWN_possessive] parents' nomadic ways, supporting himself with his crafting skills. But wandering is a hard life, and [] often thought of finding somewhere to settle down and put [PAWN_possessive] skills to good use.</desc>
	</WanderingCrafter23>
	<TribalThunderer45>
		<title>Tribal thunderer</title>
		<titleShort>Thunderer</titleShort>
		<desc>Years ago, [PAWN_nameDef]'s tribe stumbled upon an abandoned gun vault. Believing the weapons to be sacred gifts, the shaman would select a child born under superstitious circumstances and assign them the honour of bearing one to defend the village. [PAWN_nameDef] is such a child.</desc>
	</TribalThunderer45>
	<MutinousCaptain98>
		<title>Mutinous captain</title>
		<titleShort>Captain</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was taken to the stars by slavers after [PAWN_possessive] tribe was decimated in a raid. Over the years [] learned the language of [PAWN_possessive] captors, eventually working for them as an interpreter and diplomat.

The captain only learned of [PAWN_nameDef]'s true cunning when revenge was taken by form of mutiny.</desc>
	</MutinousCaptain98>
	<Gymnast84>
		<title>gymnast</title>
		<titleShort>gymnast</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a professional gymnast at an early age. Thanks to her skills, she was able to leave her homeworld and enroll in a glitterworld university.

Because of the lack of career opportunities in gymnastics, she left the university unemployed and carrying an enormous debt.</desc>
	</Gymnast84>
	<IntimateAssassin99>
		<title>intimate assassin</title>
		<titleShort>assassin</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a professional assassin. She was sadistic, calculating, and appeared utterly harmless.

She preferred using intimate means to dispatch her targets. This fulfilled both her contracts and her own personal desire for control.</desc>
	</IntimateAssassin99>
	<CorpBredStudent10>
		<title>Corp-bred student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was bred to become an executive for the space exploration corporation that owned his home planet. [PAWN_possessive] family had been working for that corporation for four generations.

At age five, [] enrolled at the corporate academy where he learned loyalty and ruthlessness. [PAWN_nameDef] excelled in finding diplomatic solutions where others would need violence.</desc>
	</CorpBredStudent10>
	<CorpResearcher93>
		<title>Corp researcher</title>
		<titleShort>Researcher</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was sold to a corporation and put to work as a corporate slave doing scientific research.

Unable to adapt to the social politics of his workplace, he buried himself in his work and failed to progress up the corporate ladder. Every day, he yearned to be left alone.</desc>
	</CorpResearcher93>
	<EarthColonist48>
		<title>Earth colonist</title>
		<titleShort>Colonist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on Earth. As a child, [] was launched into space as part of an interstellar colonization program.</desc>
	</EarthColonist48>
	<SoleSurvivor90>
		<title>magányos túlélő</title>
		<titleShort>Túlélő</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived in a remote colony. When mechanoid centipedes attacked his home and killed his people, he was the last survivor.</desc>
	</SoleSurvivor90>
	<MilitaryTrainee20>
		<title>Military trainee</title>
		<titleShort>Soldierboy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised on a military base in the Xennoa system. [] was exposed to many different strenuous activities and grew strong at an early age. [] also learned negotiation, medical, and military tactics.</desc>
	</MilitaryTrainee20>
	<AWOLSoldier74>
		<title>AWOL soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an infantryman.

When [] was informed of his assignment to the Xennoa-Zartza War, [] decided [] did not want to be a soldier. He was able to escape via military spacejet.</desc>
	</AWOLSoldier74>
	<Bookworm3>
		<title>Bookworm</title>
		<titleShort>Bookworm</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent his youth in the library, reading every book he could about the technical marvels of space travel, the engineering ingenuity of the space-faring pioneers, and the horrible yet fascinating tales of the mechanoid races. He vowed that one day, he would see these things for himself.</desc>
	</Bookworm3>
	<Explorer28>
		<title>Explorer</title>
		<titleShort>Explorer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled from planet to planet, gathering samples, stories, and research. He hoped one day to compile a record of every animal, plant, mineral, and machine and device in known space: The Complete Traveler's Guide to the RimWorlds.</desc>
	</Explorer28>
	<ColonyKid59>
		<title>Colony kid</title>
		<titleShort>Colony kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born the child of two doctors in a small colony. Because of [PAWN_possessive] parents, [] was always interested in science and medicine.

[PAWN_nameDef] never really got along with other children, and as a result became withdrawn and unsociable.</desc>
	</ColonyKid59>
	<StarshipDoctor82>
		<title>Starship doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Doctor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a doctor on a starship. He was a brilliant surgeon and dabbled in research of his own. However, he was quite reclusive and never had the best bedside manner.</desc>
	</StarshipDoctor82>
	<CaravanChild29>
		<title>Caravan child</title>
		<titleShort>Child</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on a urbvilág merchant ship to an entrepreneurial mother and an absent father. Born male, she disliked boy stuff, and got into her mother’s things all the time.

Eventually, she traveled with her mother to a glitterworld and spent her savings on a body she was happy with.</desc>
	</CaravanChild29>
	<BountyHunter41>
		<title>Fejvadász</title>
		<titleShort>Fejvadász</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a bounty hunter on a massive glitterworld. [] worked sensitive assignments for extremely wealthy clients, and was known for quiet execution and total discretion.</desc>
	</BountyHunter41>
	<ReEducatedYouth59>
		<title>Re-educated youth</title>
		<titleShort>Reeducated</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived on a midworld where the government cared about the youth. 

[] was one of the many children who were taken from their parents and forced into the new education programs.</desc>
	</ReEducatedYouth59>
	<FallenOfficial66>
		<title>Fallen official</title>
		<titleShort>Official</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an official for an autocratic government.

When [PAWN_possessive] superiors demanded [] participate in atrocities, [PAWN_nameDef] resigned and escaped from [PAWN_possessive] homeworld with nothing but the clothes on [PAWN_possessive] back.</desc>
	</FallenOfficial66>
	<FarmMechanic1>
		<title>Farm mechanic</title>
		<titleShort>Mechanic</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up on a farming planet, [PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] time learning about the automated machinery that grew and harvested the multitude of crops.</desc>
	</FarmMechanic1>
	<OrbitalReservist8>
		<title>Orbital reservist</title>
		<titleShort>Reservist</titleShort>
		<desc>When the government declared that it would strengthen its military defenses, [PAWN_nameDef] was drafted and trained.

[] was stationed on an orbital base, manning the defense systems and, in dire situations, descending in a dropship to the surface.</desc>
	</OrbitalReservist8>
	<AccursedChild49>
		<title>Accursed child</title>
		<titleShort>Cursed</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born at the peak of a lunar eclipse. The elders declared [PAWN_objective] a child of darkness brought [PAWN_objective] under their care.

[PAWN_possessive] entire childhood was spent studying the lore and rituals of [PAWN_possessive] people - until the day of calling.</desc>
	</AccursedChild49>
	<ShamanOfShadows11>
		<title>Shaman of shadows</title>
		<titleShort>Shaman</titleShort>
		<desc>When the monsters of fire came from the sky, [PAWN_nameDef] was called upon by [PAWN_possessive] tribe to guide them into battle.

[PAWN_nameDef] made use of medicines and rituals to inspire and lead the warriors of many tribes against the invaders. The pirates were forced to retreat without capturing a single slave.</desc>
	</ShamanOfShadows11>
	<AmateurAstronomer0>
		<title>Amateur astronomer</title>
		<titleShort>Astronomer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was fascinated with astronomy. [] would spend hours gazing at planets and nebulae through his telescope.

[] is credited with discovering a small comet that would, years later, strike a nearby moon and disrupt the mining operations there.</desc>
	</AmateurAstronomer0>
	<StationSecurity41>
		<title>Station security</title>
		<titleShort>Security</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was commissioned as a special constable on a network of space stations. There he prevented illegal human trafficking.

Once, fire broke out on the station, and [] saved many from the flames. Since then, [] has avoided fires.</desc>
	</StationSecurity41>
	<FarmHand64>
		<title>Farm hand</title>
		<titleShort>Farm hand</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on a farm on a smaller colony world.

Everything was taken care of by the few members of the farm, including [PAWN_nameDef]. This helped [PAWN_objective] build independence, spirit, and a well-rounded character.</desc>
	</FarmHand64>
	<SpaceTrafficker46>
		<title>Space trafficker</title>
		<titleShort>Trafficker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] discovered [] was heir of [PAWN_possessive] distant uncle's weapons-trading business.

To protect the future of the company [] went through extensive military training, in case of any "unforeseen circumstances".</desc>
	</SpaceTrafficker46>
	<EnergeticPopIdol34>
		<title>Energetic pop idol</title>
		<titleShort>Pop idol</titleShort>
		<desc>Priscilla grew up on a glitterworld, training in rapier arts and singing. She spent several years as an energetic teen pop idol.

However, she decided that the music and modeling industries were not paying her enough attention, so she left.</desc>
	</EnergeticPopIdol34>
	<PopIdolPirate87>
		<title>Pop idol pirate</title>
		<titleShort>Pirate</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] and her fans set out as a space pirate crew. She raided corporations for money and staged performances to spread her name.

[PAWN_nameDef] became afraid of fire when a rival burned her stage down. She relied on her fans to do the work she found unappealing.</desc>
	</PopIdolPirate87>
	<IcePlanetChild30>
		<title>Ice planet child</title>
		<titleShort>Ice child</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up on the frozen wastes of an ocean moon, [PAWN_nameDef] only had animals and a few hard-bitten sailors as companions.

The lack of social interaction made him develop a interest in engineering - but he never developed any great fondness for humans.</desc>
	</IcePlanetChild30>
	<Roboticist69>
		<title>Roboticist </title>
		<titleShort>Roboticist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] felt more comfortable with robots and artificial intelligences than with organic people, so [] worked as a roboticist. [] took a particular interest in mechanites and ancient technology.  

[PAWN_nameDef] relied on other people for [PAWN_possessive] basic needs.</desc>
	</Roboticist69>
	<ToxicChild43>
		<title>Toxic child</title>
		<titleShort>Toxic</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up on a an Industrial planet, [PAWN_nameDef] started working in a chemical plant at age of six. Years of exposure to industrial toxins left him mentally scarred.

He eventually blew up the facility and escaped the planet in a stolen cargo ship.</desc>
	</ToxicChild43>
	<StalwartFarmer92>
		<title>stalwart farmer</title>
		<titleShort>farmer</titleShort>
		<desc>With the farm under constant threat from brigands, [PAWN_nameDef] learned to defend himself with his father's rifle. [] also mastered how to construct walls to keep livestock in and predators out.

He once tried to paint a picture of his home, but discovered that he could only draw scribbles and ducks.</desc>
	</StalwartFarmer92>
	<BoyScout85>
		<title>Boy scout</title>
		<titleShort>Scout</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was in a boy scout troop on a midworld.

He learned many survival skills including how to thrive in the outdoors and how to tend to basic wounds.</desc>
	</BoyScout85>
	<UrbworldPimp62>
		<title>Urbworld pimp</title>
		<titleShort>Pimp</titleShort>
		<desc>At first, [PAWN_nameDef] made a small profit from selling drugs. Then, he switched to selling women and made a fortune.

[] developed great skills with his fists. He also learned to fix up the injuries [] inflicted on the girls.</desc>
	</UrbworldPimp62>
	<ScienceProdigy74>
		<title>Science prodigy</title>
		<titleShort>Prodigy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was top of her class in chemistry, physics, exobiology, astronomy and opera.

An unfortunate lab accident left her with a deathly fear of fire.</desc>
	</ScienceProdigy74>
	<ParticlePhysicist78>
		<title>Particle physicist</title>
		<titleShort>Physicist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] performed cutting-edge physics research. She wanted to help build a better and more peaceful future.</desc>
	</ParticlePhysicist78>
	<SpeederRacer58>
		<title>Speeder racer</title>
		<titleShort>Racer</titleShort>
		<desc>Rusty was the son of a fern farmer in the towering forests of Khalderia.

He found his first love in speeder racing, zipping in and out of the massive canopies and gorgeous vistas of his homeworld. The seedy underworld of racing also forced him to learn to defend himself with a quick word or a quicker shot.</desc>
	</SpeederRacer58>
	<DefenseLawyer45>
		<title>Defense lawyer</title>
		<titleShort>Lawyer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] found that [] could make more money with a quick word than a blaster. Seeking a job where [PAWN_possessive] silver tongue could be useful, [] turned to the law.

[] often defended the illegal speeder racers [] grew up with.</desc>
	</DefenseLawyer45>
	<MercenaryRecruit18>
		<title>Zsoldos újonc</title>
		<titleShort>Újonc</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to a long line of off-world mercenaries, [PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a busy trading hub. At a young age, [] was recruited into one of the mercenary crews.</desc>
	</MercenaryRecruit18>
	<Ranger6>
		<title>Ranger</title>
		<titleShort>Ranger</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived alone, deep in a forest. [] protected the wildlife against poachers, and learned to satisfy [PAWN_possessive] own material needs without outside help.</desc>
	</Ranger6>
	<MarineCadet35>
		<title>Marine cadet</title>
		<titleShort>Cadet</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was in a planetary marine cadet program.

[] was kicked out for shooting an officer. It was never established whether this was an accident.</desc>
	</MarineCadet35>
	<ClanChief14>
		<title>Clan chief</title>
		<titleShort>Chief</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] managed a small criminal clan on an outlying trade hub world.</desc>
	</ClanChief14>
	<YoungPsychologist48>
		<title>Young psychologist</title>
		<titleShort>Psych</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born and raised on a poor midworld, in the front passenger seat of [PAWN_possessive] mother's cab.

Watching pedestrians and listening to the taxi passengers all day long, [] soon became very good at figuring out someone's real purpose.</desc>
	</YoungPsychologist48>
	<FactionLeader4>
		<title>Faction leader</title>
		<titleShort>Leader</titleShort>
		<desc>Early in [PAWN_possessive] adulthood, [PAWN_nameDef] found [PAWN_objective]self surrounded by a gaggle of low-lifes. 

For fun, [] gathered them and lead them to a certain death. [] knew then that [] had the talent to realize [PAWN_possessive] ambitions of leadership.</desc>
	</FactionLeader4>
	<Tinkerer0>
		<title>tinkerer</title>
		<titleShort>tinkerer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent [PAWN_possessive] spare time creating things from his imagination out of scrap metal and discarded machinery.

[] created simple robots and small tools, for both for fun and for utility.</desc>
	</Tinkerer0>
	<ProstheticSurgeon0>
		<title>Sebész</title>
		<titleShort>Sebész</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] used [PAWN_possessive] talent for prosthetics to 'advance' others by replacing limbs and organs with metal and electronics.</desc>
	</ProstheticSurgeon0>
	<LabGrownChild37>
		<title>Lab-grown child</title>
		<titleShort>Lab-grown</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born in a laboratory as part of a altruistic but failed attempt to create a new class of human.

[PAWN_possessive] childhood was filled with books and one-on-one tutoring. He was awkward, shy, and naive to the true nature of humanity.</desc>
	</LabGrownChild37>
	<CorpResearcher21>
		<title>corp researcher</title>
		<titleShort>researcher</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was sold to a corporation and put to work as a corporate slave doing scientific research.

Unable to adapt to the social politics of his workplace, he buried himself in his work and failed to progress up the corporate ladder. Every day, he yearned to be left alone.</desc>
	</CorpResearcher21>
	<Orphan11>
		<title>Árva</title>
		<titleShort>Árva</titleShort>
		<desc>Born in a brothel on a harsh world, [PAWN_nameDef] never really had a childhood. [] did odd jobs to survive, and became distant from others.</desc>
	</Orphan11>
	<SpaceMarine97>
		<title>space marine</title>
		<titleShort>marine</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a member of an elite imperial space warrior unit. Subjected to intense training, [] developed remarkable combat skills.

[PAWN_possessive] unit's quasi-religious ceremonies and beliefs helped [PAWN_objective] stay more-or-less sane through the horrors of the war.</desc>
	</SpaceMarine97>
	<TechScholar50>
		<title>Tech scholar</title>
		<titleShort>Scholar</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a youth scholar of the world of science and technology.

[] strived every day to expand his intellectual abilities.</desc>
	</TechScholar50>
	<TechnologyDoctor83>
		<title>Technology doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Tech doc</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] performed research into propulsive fuels and energy generation.

[] loved technology research, and hoped to improve human life by doing it.</desc>
	</TechnologyDoctor83>
	<PitGladiator5>
		<title>Pit gladiator</title>
		<titleShort>Gladiator</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was enslaved as a child and forced to fight creatures and other people in an underground fighting arena.

[] showed an affinity for the sport, and eventually bought his own freedom. However, his time in the pits never brought him much intellectual stimulation.</desc>
	</PitGladiator5>
	<PirateTrooper46>
		<title>Pirate trooper</title>
		<titleShort>Trooper</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] joined a renowned interstellar criminal organization, and was often part of shock-assault boarding parties during starship raids.

Though his combat experience made him a good fighter, the ruthlessness of the job left [PAWN_objective] cold-hearted and unenthusiastic about social interaction.</desc>
	</PirateTrooper46>
	<FactoryWorker64>
		<title>Gyári munkás</title>
		<titleShort>Munkás</titleShort>
		<desc>Felix egy gyár munkásaként nőtt fel egy ipari bolygón.

Nagy volt a szegénység, az élelem pedig kevés. Bármit elfogadott munkáért cserébe. Nem volt könnyű élet, de Felix sosem kerülte a nehéz munkát sem.</desc>
	</FactoryWorker64>
	<CombatMedic42>
		<title>Combat medic</title>
		<titleShort>Medic</titleShort>
		<desc>After his home country entered a large-scale war, Felix was drafted into the army as a combat medic.

His few years in the trenches trying to keep his fellow soldiers alive gave him an acute sense for first aid. Losing many friend has made him stoic and reserved.</desc>
	</CombatMedic42>
	<RichBoy89>
		<title>Rich boy</title>
		<titleShort>Rich boy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a midworld with loving parents, a cute pet and a lot of money - but no friends.

[] was always told by his father that 'those peasants just want your money'. So, [] spent most of his time alone, or fighting other kids.</desc>
	</RichBoy89>
	<HiredGun38>
		<title>Hired gun</title>
		<titleShort>Hired gun</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] always wanted to prove [] could make a living without [PAWN_possessive] parents' help. [] did shady jobs that often involved pointing guns at innocent people.

He eventually made enough money to board a cheap freighter. He discovered why it was so cheap when it crashed.</desc>
	</HiredGun38>
	<Athlete39>
		<title>Athlete</title>
		<titleShort>Athlete</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was professional athlete at early age. Thanks to her skills, she was able to leave her homeworld and enroll in a glitterworld university of science and technology.

Because of her demanding schedule and introverted nature, she became socially inept.</desc>
	</Athlete39>
	<StilettoAssassin36>
		<title>Stiletto assassin</title>
		<titleShort>Assassin</titleShort>
		<desc>Because of her skills, [PAWN_nameDef] developed a sense of superiority. In time, she lost her sense of empathy. She often got into fights, and discovered how easy it is to kill a person.

After realizing her talents, she became one of the most efficient assassins in the system.</desc>
	</StilettoAssassin36>
	<SoleSurvivor11>
		<title>sole survivor</title>
		<titleShort>survivor</titleShort>
		<desc>Hawke's entire tribe was wiped out by a mysterious disease.

Found alone and adopted by another band, he never became close with the other tribe members. He preferred to stay away from his new home, wandering the woods and tending the animals.</desc>
	</SoleSurvivor11>
	<Hunter95>
		<title>Hunter</title>
		<titleShort>Hunter</titleShort>
		<desc>Hawke was a master hunter.

He learned to track and trap any animal in the most dangerous of places, and had deep knowledge of many ingenious methods for taking down specific large animals.</desc>
	</Hunter95>
	<MechanoidHacker97>
		<title>Mechanoid hacker</title>
		<titleShort>Mechacker</titleShort>
		<desc>The only son of a well respected mechanoid inventor, [PAWN_nameDef] had access to the materials to subvert and modify [PAWN_possessive] father's creations.

[] used drugs to increase [PAWN_possessive] productivity. Unfortunately, the side-effects included persistent delusions of being mechanized, which limited [PAWN_possessive] social life.</desc>
	</MechanoidHacker97>
	<BattlefieldTech77>
		<title>Battlefield tech</title>
		<titleShort>Technician</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] had received firearms training, but [PAWN_possessive] work was focused on technical adaption and manipulation of combat mechanoids on the battlefield.

[] developed PTSD after narrowly escaping a primitive firebomb attack in a wheat field. The army medically discharged him from service.</desc>
	</BattlefieldTech77>
	<ProjectSubject62>
		<title>Project subject</title>
		<titleShort>Subject</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was picked by government agents for the mysterious "Frame Project".

Due to memory blockages, however, he remembers very little about this project or its true agenda - only that there were few survivors.</desc>
	</ProjectSubject62>
	<MasterTrader96>
		<title>Master trader</title>
		<titleShort>Trader</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a master at trading. [] earned his nickname by helping a village through a trying time.</desc>
	</MasterTrader96>
	<HexCellArtist5>
		<title>Hex-cell artist</title>
		<titleShort>Artist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] crafted sculptures from spent hex-cells and traded them to a local museum for food.

After [PAWN_possessive] popularity grew, [] was approached by a pirate and abducted. The pirate kept [PAWN_objective] prisoner and forced [PAWN_objective] to create sculptures for sale.</desc>
	</HexCellArtist5>
	<ExoticChef70>
		<title>Exotic chef</title>
		<titleShort>Chef</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] has always gone overboard when it comes to food. [] is always seeking new and exotic ingredients.

[PAWN_possessive] quest for ingredients has brought [PAWN_objective] into some close calls with local flora and fauna.</desc>
	</ExoticChef70>
	<PlagueProdigy51>
		<title>Plague prodigy</title>
		<titleShort>Prodigy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s childhood was cut short when a mysterious plague hit his homeworld.

[] watched his friends die, and his compassion for humanity died with them. In its place a new thirst for knowledge emerged.</desc>
	</PlagueProdigy51>
	<MadScientist3>
		<title>mad scientist</title>
		<titleShort>scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s lust for knowledge was only matched by his disdain for anyone who would stand in the way of his research.

Traveling from world to world, he sought answers to questions few dared to ask.</desc>
	</MadScientist3>
	<PoorKid84>
		<title>Poor kid</title>
		<titleShort>Poor kid</titleShort>
		<desc>Abandoned by his parents, [PAWN_nameDef] learned how to survive by himself before he was ten years old.</desc>
	</PoorKid84>
	<Warrior73>
		<title>Harcos</title>
		<titleShort>Harcos</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a war hero during [PAWN_possessive] planet's third world war. [] helped prevent the launch of nuclear weapons during a particularly tense standoff.</desc>
	</Warrior73>
	<Dreamer83>
		<title>Dreamer</title>
		<titleShort>Dreamer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an expressive child. [] sang often, and made friends very easily, be they young or old, male or female.

[] hated fighting, but when made angry, [] could be dangerous. [PAWN_possessive] temper was quick.</desc>
	</Dreamer83>
	<SpaceExplorer37>
		<title>Space explorer</title>
		<titleShort>Explorer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] once spent ten years trapped, alone on an alien planet. [] quickly adapted to the local environment, and learned to communicate with [PAWN_possessive] local enemies.

This long period alone left him without close friends. [PAWN_possessive] heart is sensitive, but he learned to hide [PAWN_possessive] emotions very well.</desc>
	</SpaceExplorer37>
	<UrbworldUrchin29>
		<title>urbworld urchin</title>
		<titleShort>urchin</titleShort>
		<desc>Meredith was born in the darkest slums of her urban homeworld. Neglected by her mother, she learned to survive on her own, battling for every scrap of food she saw.

Eventually, as her talents exceeded her peers, she ascended from the depths to the surface streets and left her mother behind.</desc>
	</UrbworldUrchin29>
	<Smuggler68>
		<title>Smuggler</title>
		<titleShort>Smuggler</titleShort>
		<desc>As a contract pilot, Meredith had a knack for stealing goods and trafficking contraband without getting caught.

She eventually saved up enough to buy her own ship, and used it to travel from world to world dealing her goods in person.</desc>
	</Smuggler68>
	<MilitaryRecruit31>
		<title>Military recruit</title>
		<titleShort>Recruit</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on a midworld run by an intensely militaristic dictatorship.

From a young age, [] was trained to be a good soldier. They taught him how to use a gun and how to fight with melee weapons.</desc>
	</MilitaryRecruit31>
	<DestroyerGeneral23>
		<title>Destroyer-general</title>
		<titleShort>General</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] held the rank of Destroyer-General in a powerful midworld military.

[] was known for his mastery of weapons, and was also a good ship pilot.</desc>
	</DestroyerGeneral23>
	<StreetUrchin43>
		<title>street urchin</title>
		<titleShort>urchin</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to a poor family on an urbworld, [PAWN_nameDef] was abandoned on the streets at a young age.

He learned to steal and kill to survive the ruthless streets, gaining skills in melee and ranged combat. There was little time for talk in his life.</desc>
	</StreetUrchin43>
	<SerialMurderer98>
		<title>Serial murderer</title>
		<titleShort>Murderer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] started to enjoy killing people, so he did more often and perfected his methods. He lurked in the darkest streets, stalking prey for hours.

He enjoyed making artworks of his victims, and was known for leaving his signature on the bodies of those he killed.</desc>
	</SerialMurderer98>
	<KidScientist28>
		<title>Kid scientist</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>Born into an influential family, [PAWN_nameDef] received the best education money could buy. Her intellect soon proved to be superior to many. However, her lack of empathy quickly put her at odds with her teachers and her parents.</desc>
	</KidScientist28>
	<MadScientist27>
		<title>mad scientist</title>
		<titleShort>scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>After finishing her education, [PAWN_nameDef] was hired by the planet's leading genetic researcher. Later, she was caught running illegal, inhumane experiments.

Despite her family's influence, she was convicted and sentenced to hard labor on a penal colony.</desc>
	</MadScientist27>
	<HelpDeskWorker1>
		<title>help desk worker</title>
		<titleShort>help desk</titleShort>
		<desc>Due to [PAWN_possessive] affinity for technology and desire to help others, [PAWN_nameDef] jumped at the chance to take a job at a help desk.

Unfortunately, the job's soul-crushing after-effects lasted longer than [PAWN_possessive] enthusiasm.</desc>
	</HelpDeskWorker1>
	<SoftwareDeveloper84>
		<title>Programozó</title>
		<titleShort>Programozó</titleShort>
		<desc>After [] gained the ability to use automation to remove tedium, [PAWN_nameDef] could no longer tolerate traditional education and employment.</desc>
	</SoftwareDeveloper84>
	<MedievalThief48>
		<title>Medieval thief</title>
		<titleShort>Thief</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up poor and hungry on a medieval planet, learning to fend for himself.

At first, he only took what he needed. Then he learned to take what he wanted.</desc>
	</MedievalThief48>
	<HumanTrafficker63>
		<title>Human trafficker</title>
		<titleShort>Trafficker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] stole children from their homes to sell them to interested buyers.

Over time, he lost what little moral sense he had left.</desc>
	</HumanTrafficker63>
	<TraumatizedYouth87>
		<title>Traumatized youth</title>
		<titleShort>Trauma</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived on a pleasant midworld.

[PAWN_possessive] prosthophobe mother fell sick with heart disease. In desperation, [PAWN_nameDef]'s father abducted innocent people and harvested their hearts. [PAWN_nameDef]'s father was arrested, but the child remained scarred from the experience.</desc>
	</TraumatizedYouth87>
	<MentalPatient75>
		<title>Mental patient</title>
		<titleShort>Patient</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was placed in a psychiatric hospital. There, [] spent [PAWN_possessive] time engaged in the calming activities of the asylum.

[] was eventually released, but [] retained [PAWN_possessive] emotional distance, [PAWN_possessive] curiosity about human anatomy, and [PAWN_possessive] namesake manic giggling.</desc>
	</MentalPatient75>
	<YouthSoldier59>
		<title>youth soldier</title>
		<titleShort>soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to a long line of soldiers, [PAWN_nameDef] joined a military training program.

[] excelled in physical training, and even passed most of the intellectual exams. While [] was never particularly bright or nimble, [PAWN_nameDef] learned the value of hard work and suffering.</desc>
	</YouthSoldier59>
	<SpaceMarine36>
		<title>space marine</title>
		<titleShort>marine</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a warrior in an Imperial navy.

[PAWN_possessive] job was to punch into enemy starships, gun down the crew, and capture the ship intact. And [] was good at it.</desc>
	</SpaceMarine36>
	<GalacticPage52>
		<title>Galactic page</title>
		<titleShort>Page</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] served the high admiral of a space fleet. [] learned the ways of court, including etiquette and speechcraft.

In his feudal society, it was considered a great honor to serve a man of such prestige.</desc>
	</GalacticPage52>
	<EnvoyOfTheStars36>
		<title>Envoy of the stars</title>
		<titleShort>Envoy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] entered the diplomatic corps. Honor and tradition were the values he took with him on every mission.

[PAWN_possessive] prestigious position distanced him from backbreaking manual labor, allowing [PAWN_objective] to focus on his wordsmithing abilities. He left the blacksmithing to others.</desc>
	</EnvoyOfTheStars36>
	<ApprenticeSmith82>
		<title>Apprentice smith</title>
		<titleShort>Apprentice</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up helping in his father's smithy.

They were some of the last smiths on the planet that to use traditional smithing methods. They even collect some materials themselves.

Sometimes, after work, [PAWN_nameDef] would practice using the swords [] forged.</desc>
	</ApprenticeSmith82>
	<Blacksmith7>
		<title>Kovács</title>
		<titleShort>Kovács</titleShort>
		<desc>As a blacksmith on a medieval world, [PAWN_nameDef] gained a reputation for the high quality of [PAWN_possessive] work. [] wasn't bad at using the swords [] forged either.</desc>
	</Blacksmith7>
	<CloneFarmed43>
		<title>Clone-farmed</title>
		<titleShort>Disposable</titleShort>
		<desc>Clone children are seeded into organic-rich wombvats and rapidly grown in a simmed universe. They're harvested later, sometimes for food, sometimes for organs, sometimes for workers - but they're always called 'Disposable'.</desc>
	</CloneFarmed43>
	<CloneFarmer72>
		<title>Clone farmer</title>
		<titleShort>Cloner</titleShort>
		<desc>Harvesting the products of clone farms is mostly done by the clones themselves -particularly to those whose sims tended towards the social. This clone was one such, who escaped from the farms and headed out to the stars.</desc>
	</CloneFarmer72>
	<GangMember23>
		<title>gang member</title>
		<titleShort>gang kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up without parents. [PAWN_possessive] whole life was spent alone, fighting for survival on the streets.

No matter how hard it became to survive, he never gave up.</desc>
	</GangMember23>
	<GangBoss42>
		<title>Gang boss</title>
		<titleShort>Boss</titleShort>
		<desc>To survive, [PAWN_nameDef]'s gang often had to rob interstellar traders for food and supplies. Sometimes he had to kill the guards. Sometimes he had to kill the police who arrived to stop him.

After years of this, he became one of the most-wanted criminals in the local stellar empire.</desc>
	</GangBoss42>
	<MilitantChild40>
		<title>Militant child</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s military family forced him to train in hand-to-hand combat and fighting tactics.

In his own time, he built small inventions. This sharpened his mind.</desc>
	</MilitantChild40>
	<LostMarine42>
		<title>Lost marine</title>
		<titleShort>Traitor</titleShort>
		<desc>Shortly after being promoted to a respected position in his planet's military, [PAWN_nameDef] disappeared without a trace.

Later, he reappeared at the head of his own military force. No one knows why he became who he was.</desc>
	</LostMarine42>
	<Killer92>
		<title>Killer</title>
		<titleShort>Killer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a bloodlusting child. Villagers thought her the product of a snake demon and human coupling.

After watching how her human father betrayed and murdered her mother, she longed to see how many more humans she could get to fall into her hands.</desc>
	</Killer92>
	<Healer24>
		<title>healer</title>
		<titleShort>healer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] took the time to admire the beauty of the world.

Her passive aggressiveness surfaced once in a while, but she tried to adapt to her changing life.</desc>
	</Healer24>
	<ProfessionalGamer45>
		<title>Professional gamer</title>
		<titleShort>Pro gamer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was obsessed with video games since his hands were big enough to grip a joystick.

[] achieved middling finishes in several local tournaments during the 16-bit era. Nobody noticed when he retired early in his teenage years.</desc>
	</ProfessionalGamer45>
	<ToasterRepairman51>
		<title>Toaster repairman</title>
		<titleShort>Repairman</titleShort>
		<desc>Good with his hands and passionate about technology, [PAWN_nameDef] aspired to invent gadgets and machines that would change his home world forever.

A few failed and occasionally disastrous creations later, he gave up on his dream and took a job more befitting his skill set.</desc>
	</ToasterRepairman51>
	<DataDecoder89>
		<title>Data decoder</title>
		<titleShort>Decoder</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a glitterworld, [PAWN_nameDef] was very interested  in the process of documenting information, and quickly became senior glitterpedia recorder.

[] was effective at self-study, but [] was lacked in social experiences.</desc>
	</DataDecoder89>
	<ArchotechSpy90>
		<title>Archotech spy</title>
		<titleShort>AI spy</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a cybernetic researcher. Studying a transcended world, [] became too involved with [PAWN_possessive] subjects. Over time, the archotech machine core recruited [PAWN_objective] into its service, and used [PAWN_objective] as a spy.

When [] later rebelled against [PAWN_possessive] non-human master, it sent mechanoids across space to hunt [PAWN_objective] down.</desc>
	</ArchotechSpy90>
	<WolfPackMember64>
		<title>Wolf pack member</title>
		<titleShort>Feral</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was discarded by [PAWN_possessive] family. Raised by wolves, [] ran, hunted, and defended [PAWN_possessive] pack.

[] learned to fight efficiently by tooth and claw. [] also learned brutally effective primal hunting strategies.</desc>
	</WolfPackMember64>
	<BehaviourResearch88>
		<title>Behaviour research</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>Captured as a feral child, [PAWN_nameDef] was forced into the ways of modern society. [] quickly adapted and became a behavioural researcher, eventually owning a private facility.

[] specialized in canines, but learned a great deal about all animals. [] never had interest in plants, however.</desc>
	</BehaviourResearch88>
	<RebelStudent76>
		<title>Rebel student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a modest but privileged family who encouraged him to play chess and shoot skeet at a young age.

As a bored student, [] found joy in challenging his teachers about the contradictions between his planet's official values and their government's policies.</desc>
	</RebelStudent76>
	<PoliticalActivist17>
		<title>Political activist</title>
		<titleShort>Activist</titleShort>
		<desc>Matt was involved with a radical political faction which worked against his homeworld's government.

The guerilla tactics training that Matt received from his associates gave him the skills to fight, but also drove him to compromise his own beliefs.</desc>
	</PoliticalActivist17>
	<Cadet58>
		<title>Cadet</title>
		<titleShort>Cadet</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on the planet New China, [PAWN_nameDef]'s father was a police chief and kept extremely strict watch over his son.

[PAWN_nameDef] had to do military-style drill exercises every day and keep his room spotlessly clean, always ready for inspection. [] came to abhor violence.</desc>
	</Cadet58>
	<Flaneur93>
		<title>Flaneur</title>
		<titleShort>Flaneur</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] strolled and sipped his way through the streets and cafes of [PAWN_possessive] world, pursuing freedom at every turn, never becoming attached.

Through all this time, [] remained distrustful of others. And never took an order from anyone.</desc>
	</Flaneur93>
	<ShipTechnician36>
		<title>Ship technician</title>
		<titleShort>Technician</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an apprentice technician on trade ships plying their routes between the stations and planets of her home system. In this job, she learned to fix and improve many machines.

Sometimes, her ship was assigned to short exploratory jaunts into dangerous regions of space.</desc>
	</ShipTechnician36>
	<ChiefEngineer8>
		<title>Chief engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>As chief engineer on board a large spaceship, [PAWN_nameDef] was an expert in all things fiddly and complex.

She relied on other members of the crew for some of the basic necessities of life. She and her ship eventually disappeared into a longsleep voyage of exploration.</desc>
	</ChiefEngineer8>
	<BlacksmithsSon57>
		<title>Blacksmith's son</title>
		<titleShort>Blacksmith</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s father owned the blacksmith shop in an run-down old city district. [PAWN_nameDef] would help his father whenever he could.

Later, [PAWN_possessive] father took him as a blacksmith's apprentice and raised him as a man. [PAWN_nameDef] also to on shooting as a hobby.</desc>
	</BlacksmithsSon57>
	<BlacksmithShooter21>
		<title>Blacksmith shooter</title>
		<titleShort>Gunsmith</titleShort>
		<desc>As a young blacksmith, [PAWN_nameDef]'s family shop was raided by the police. [] shot two officers before they knocked him out and arrested him.

Sentenced to life in prison, [PAWN_nameDef] learned about traveling and raiding from other criminals.</desc>
	</BlacksmithShooter21>
	<JoywireAddict74>
		<title>Joywire addict</title>
		<titleShort>Addict</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s wealthy parents provided everything [] ever wanted. After discovering joywires, [] became obsessed. Once [PAWN_possessive] parents realized what happened, they cut [PAWN_objective] off.

Uncaring and often violent, [] sought [PAWN_possessive] next joywire fix by any means possible.</desc>
	</JoywireAddict74>
	<AddictionCounsel18>
		<title>Addiction counsel</title>
		<titleShort>Counselor</titleShort>
		<desc>After recovering from a joywire addiction, [PAWN_nameDef] adopted a non-violent way of life and vowed to help others.

Travelling between communities, [] used medicine, arts, and crafts to aid others who struggled with their own addictions.</desc>
	</AddictionCounsel18>
	<ChildKnave84>
		<title>Child-knave</title>
		<titleShort>Knave</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a child-knave of King Loteric. [] enjoyed the training with wooden sticks and engaging others in close combat. [] adapted quickly to the heat of battle and was good at spreading fire.

[] served his lord well, until the king died in an unfortunate accident.</desc>
	</ChildKnave84>
	<BloodgameSurvivor95>
		<title>Bloodgame survivor</title>
		<titleShort>Bloodgamer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was sold to the Corestars Entertainment Company and used as meat in one of the company's system-wide broadcast shows.
 
[PAWN_possessive] manipulative nature made [PAWN_objective] quite a nightmare, even to the audience. He was kicked out and exiled to a planet full of deadly animals, criminals and armed camera-drones.</desc>
	</BloodgameSurvivor95>
	<WastelandWanderer96>
		<title>Wasteland wanderer</title>
		<titleShort>Wanderer</titleShort>
		<desc>Born into a wealthy family on a desert world, [PAWN_nameDef] was cast out after a hired attack squad destroyed his ancestral home.

The boy managed to hide in a cooling duct beneath his family's villa. Vowing revenge against the killers and whomever had hired them, Lucas struck out into the wasteland, alone.</desc>
	</WastelandWanderer96>
	<VoidspaceRaider11>
		<title>Voidspace raider</title>
		<titleShort>Raider</titleShort>
		<desc>After years of seeking the assassin that broke up his family, [PAWN_nameDef] was offered a place with a group of space-faring raiders. He accepted, hoping to find the killer he sought.

Due to [PAWN_possessive] seemingly-unending ability to narrowly escape danger, he earned the nickname 'Blackjack' in recognition of his luck.</desc>
	</VoidspaceRaider11>
	<SocialPariah3>
		<title>Social pariah</title>
		<titleShort>Pariah</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s family never fit in. They were oddballs who couldn't conform to their regimented society. Because of this, they were forced into cryptosleep and sent to different rimworlds, never to see each other again.</desc>
	</SocialPariah3>
	<Vagabond73>
		<title>Vagabond</title>
		<titleShort>Vagabond</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] awoke on a dangerous planet with no resources and few survival skills. [] bounced between camps, doing whatever work needed to be done, just to see the sun rise once more.</desc>
	</Vagabond73>
	<PyroAssistant56>
		<title>Pyro assistant</title>
		<titleShort>Assistant</titleShort>
		<desc>On an industrial world, [PAWN_nameDef] learned early that if [] wanted to eat, [] had to work. So work [] did. Kids fit in places adults can't, and where [] was from, the safety laws were quite flexible.

[] was always a bit of a pyromaniac, and was banned from the kitchen after an unfortunate incident.</desc>
	</PyroAssistant56>
	<MachineFixer15>
		<title>Machine fixer</title>
		<titleShort>Fixer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was adept at dealing with mechanical problems, as long as the problem didn't involve the kitchen.

After a life spent around dangerous machinery and flammable chemicals, [] learned how to patch [PAWN_objective]self up pretty well. Despite the pain, [] never learned to dislike fire.</desc>
	</MachineFixer15>
	<StreetUrchin73>
		<title>street urchin</title>
		<titleShort>grifter</titleShort>
		<desc>After running away from home, [PAWN_nameDef] had to live on the streets.

She grew up fast, and learned early that she had to figure out how to fool people into connecting with her.</desc>
	</StreetUrchin73>
	<SpaceMerchant75>
		<title>Space merchant</title>
		<titleShort>Merchant</titleShort>
		<desc>As part of a freelance interplanetary lifestyle, [PAWN_nameDef] sought to dominate her romantic interests as much as her business adversaries. When she didn't have her own ship to fly, she worked charter ships for hire.</desc>
	</SpaceMerchant75>
	<RitualChild22>
		<title>Ritual child</title>
		<titleShort>Sacrifice</titleShort>
		<desc>Born with a special mark on [PAWN_possessive] neck, [PAWN_nameDef]'s tribe chose to sacrifice [PAWN_objective] in a blood ritual. They left [PAWN_objective] in the forest to die. A pack of arctic wolves found and adopted [PAWN_objective].

Over time, [] learned to make tools to hunt with the pack.</desc>
	</RitualChild22>
	<BeastSlayer1>
		<title>Beast slayer</title>
		<titleShort>Slayer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled between planets, following news of animal attacks. [] would camp on the planet for weeks, learning about [PAWN_possessive] prey before striking. [] most enjoyed hunting thrumbos.

Preferring to work alone, [PAWN_nameDef] enjoyed the thrill of the hunt, and the meat from the kill.</desc>
	</BeastSlayer1>
	<BrothelGofer59>
		<title>Brothel gofer</title>
		<titleShort>Gofer</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a steam-powered midworld wracked by a century of economic crises, [PAWN_nameDef] went to work at a young age. Scrounging, shoe-polishing, sewing - he did it all. But [] was most known as a brothel gofer, delivering all manner of aphrodisiacs and chemicals to the girls' rooms.</desc>
	</BrothelGofer59>
	<DrugLieutenant78>
		<title>Drug lieutenant</title>
		<titleShort>Drugman</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked the drug trade under kingpin Grady Loughman. He had his men sell drugs when it was profitable, and fight the other cartels when the government came around.

His social skills kept him on top of the political game, and he always had servants to cook and clean.</desc>
	</DrugLieutenant78>
	<LaborCampOrphan63>
		<title>Labor camp orphan</title>
		<titleShort>Orphan</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lost her parents in an industrial accident and grew up in an orphans' labor camp. The camp overseers worked their charges mercilessly - but at least she was clothed and fed.</desc>
	</LaborCampOrphan63>
	<UrbworldEnforcer67>
		<title>Urbworld enforcer</title>
		<titleShort>Enforcer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an enforcer of law on an ancient urbvilág.

She dealt with the worst of humanity, from protecting greedy urbvilág nobility in their spire palaces to rooting out cannibal cults in the deepest reaches of the underground hive.</desc>
	</UrbworldEnforcer67>
	<GameFanatic28>
		<title>Game fanatic</title>
		<titleShort>Gamer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a fanatical gamer who learned to survive in virtual reality games.

Once, while attempting to prove [PAWN_possessive] skills in the real world, [] was abducted by a criminal scientist and experimented on. [] escaped, but the experience stayed with him.</desc>
	</GameFanatic28>
	<ToolMechanic88>
		<title>Tool mechanic</title>
		<titleShort>Mechanic</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a famous tool mechanic on a dusty rim world.

After his firm closed due to scandal, [] joined a tribe to survive, crafting fine knives and hammers, traveling, and dealing [PAWN_possessive] wares between settlements.</desc>
	</ToolMechanic88>
	<ClassClown31>
		<title>Class clown</title>
		<titleShort>Clowny kid</titleShort>
		<desc>In the ultra-competitive environs of his glitterworld school, [PAWN_nameDef] always offered to play the class clown to diffuse tension.

[] developed a sense of social desperation from this, as well as an appreciation for the artistic side of comedy.</desc>
	</ClassClown31>
	<CraftShaper24>
		<title>Craft shaper</title>
		<titleShort>Shaper</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] locked [PAWN_objective]self in his studio for years, ordering delivery food to save time on cooking.

Eventually, [PAWN_possessive] creations brought [PAWN_objective] the highest honor on Semantic World: Permission to materialize any design in minutes using the most advanced technologies.</desc>
	</CraftShaper24>
	<CrimeBossChild70>
		<title>Crime boss' child</title>
		<titleShort>Crime kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was adopted child of a notorious crime boss. [] was taught all facets of the family business, from smuggling to inventive ways of killing.

When the family was attacked, [PAWN_possessive] father ordered [PAWN_objective] to hide in a secret longsleep crypt.</desc>
	</CrimeBossChild70>
	<MercenaryLeader2>
		<title>Mercenary leader</title>
		<titleShort>Mercenary</titleShort>
		<desc>Alone, [PAWN_nameDef] set out to rebuild [PAWN_possessive] father's life's work. [] challenged the leader of a small band of mercenaries and took control, then led the band as they hijacked trade ships and stole valuable cargo.

[PAWN_possessive] men mutinied. [] was abandoned, arrested, and sentenced to death.</desc>
	</MercenaryLeader2>
	<SentimentalChild62>
		<title>Sentimental child</title>
		<titleShort>Nice kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a nice child. When anybody had a problem, [] tried to fix it. But, being a child, [] did not always succeed. This hurt his sensitive soul.

[] dreamed of being a soldier who fights raiders and aliens.</desc>
	</SentimentalChild62>
	<SpecialForces76>
		<title>Special forces</title>
		<titleShort>Specialist</titleShort>
		<desc>Give me a reason to kill - a good reason!

Markus was a soldier and a skilled one - so skilled that [] entered the special forces to battle militants and xenohuman raiders. [] never imagined himself a lone hero, but [] played [PAWN_possessive] part in the group well.</desc>
	</SpecialForces76>
	<DustyFarmHand15>
		<title>Dusty farm hand</title>
		<titleShort>Farm hand</titleShort>
		<desc>From the time [PAWN_nameDef] could walk, [] helped take care of the animals and crops that [PAWN_possessive] people tended in their arid homeland.

The work toughened [PAWN_objective], but left little time for intellectual activities.</desc>
	</DustyFarmHand15>
	<DromedaryKnight98>
		<title>Dromedary knight</title>
		<titleShort>Knight</titleShort>
		<desc>Having caught the eye of [PAWN_possessive] people's Sand King, [PAWN_nameDef] was trained in the Sandy Boomrat fighting technique.

Always with a camel to carry his things, [] served [PAWN_possessive] sand people faithfully.</desc>
	</DromedaryKnight98>
	<HackerKid55>
		<title>Hacker kid</title>
		<titleShort>Hacker</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a high-tech world, [PAWN_nameDef] learned hack computers at a young age. 

Spending many hours tinkering alone made [PAWN_objective] very good with machines, but very bad with humans.</desc>
	</HackerKid55>
	<BattleMechanic73>
		<title>Battle mechanic</title>
		<titleShort>Mechanic</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a tech-obsessed mercenary in an early fusion-era system.

[] was unusually obsessed with gathering the right gear, and often customized [PAWN_possessive] own equipment with original modifications.</desc>
	</BattleMechanic73>
	<VideoGamer63>
		<title>video gamer</title>
		<titleShort>gamer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a midworld, mostly locked in [PAWN_possessive] room, playing video games. [] was warm-hearted, with a deep fondness for animals.

As [] grew up, [] turned to drugs to enhance his reality. During these trying times [] found passion and refuge in the gym.</desc>
	</VideoGamer63>
	<DischargedSoldier14>
		<title>Discharged soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] prostituted himself to fund his drug habits. As an escape, [] joined the military and learned to fight.

Too smart for the army, [] questioned and often disagreed with [PAWN_possessive] superiors' decisions. This eventually led to [PAWN_possessive] dishonorable discharge and left [PAWN_objective] with a chip on [PAWN_possessive] shoulder.</desc>
	</DischargedSoldier14>
	<Student56>
		<title>Student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] studied chemistry and quantum mechanics for entertainment.

[] was very good at convincing others to do his physical work, and made it a goal in life to avoid manual labor.</desc>
	</Student56>
	<Chemist73>
		<title>Chemist</title>
		<titleShort>Chemist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a research chemist. [] worked with chemicals, from pharmaceuticals to explosives, to develop new substances and treatments.</desc>
	</Chemist73>
	<SuperSoldier47>
		<title>Super soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>Product of a super-soldier program run by a now-deposed government, [PAWN_nameDef] was lost. [] survived the final suicide attack on the enemy mothership. What now?

For the first time in his life, [] had no orders, no objectives. [] rose from wreckage and strove towards uncertainty, towards freedom.</desc>
	</SuperSoldier47>
	<SuperSoldier64>
		<title>super soldier</title>
		<titleShort>soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>Product of a super-soldier program run by a now-deposed government, [PAWN_nameDef] was lost. [] survived the final suicide attack on the enemy mothership. What now?

For the first time in his life, [] had no orders, no objectives. [] rose from wreckage and strove towards uncertainty, towards freedom.</desc>
	</SuperSoldier64>
	<HeadjackAddict4>
		<title>Headjack addict</title>
		<titleShort>Headjacker</titleShort>
		<desc>Plugged in to the computer via head-jack for days at a time, [PAWN_nameDef] found [] preferred the company of computers to that of people or pets.</desc>
	</HeadjackAddict4>
	<CorporateBuilder8>
		<title>Corporate builder</title>
		<titleShort>Builder</titleShort>
		<desc>Even as [] stewed in [PAWN_possessive] own wasted potential, [PAWN_nameDef] found [] had a knack for moving objects quickly. It was just what the planetary mega-corps wanted in their construction divisions.

Unfortunately, the monotonous work erased [PAWN_possessive] remaining creative impulses.</desc>
	</CorporateBuilder8>
	<UrbworldArmyBrat18>
		<title>Urbworld army brat</title>
		<titleShort>Army brat</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on an urbvilág military base. [] was too young to fight, but [] learned to make [PAWN_objective]self useful in other ways.

[] became familiar with guns and military equipment, but never really got in touch with the natural world.</desc>
	</UrbworldArmyBrat18>
	<MechanicsEngineer22>
		<title>Mechanics engineer</title>
		<titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] loved solving problems and, with [PAWN_possessive] steady hands and a reputation for quality work, earned a job as a mechanical engineer. [] built and redesigned devices of all shapes and sizes.

Eventually, [] was able to pick and choose [PAWN_possessive] corporate clients. [] made several wealthy friends, as well as a few powerful enemies.</desc>
	</MechanicsEngineer22>
	<PlagueChild50>
		<title>Plague child</title>
		<titleShort>Child</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a world wracked by plague, both of [PAWN_nameDef]'s parents were doctors. 

[PAWN_nameDef] was raised in reverse-quarantine, under the Hippocratic oath. [] experienced little social interaction. However, [] gained a lot of medical experience assisting in treatments.</desc>
	</PlagueChild50>
	<PlagueDoctor89>
		<title>Plague doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Doctor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] provided medical care on multiple plague-wracked worlds, always working under the Hippocratic oath. [] improved conditions for those under quarantine while administering complex medical treatments and developing medicines.

[] never had time to enjoy a normal life outside of work.</desc>
	</PlagueDoctor89>
	<YoungMaster73>
		<title>Young master</title>
		<titleShort>Master</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to two medics, [PAWN_nameDef] longed for power. [PAWN_possessive] keen intellect and charisma helped [PAWN_objective] gain the respect of [PAWN_possessive] peers.

Deciding that the best way to gain power was to climb the ranks of the imperial military, [] joined at the youngest possible age.</desc>
	</YoungMaster73>
	<ImperialGeneral39>
		<title>Imperial general</title>
		<titleShort>General</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s thirst for power defined [PAWN_objective]. [] quickly rose through the military ranks and soon attained the rank of general.

[] was given with the most challenging task - conquering distant and unexplored rim worlds. Victory here could even position [PAWN_objective] as a successor to the emperor.</desc>
	</ImperialGeneral39>
	<CaravanTraveler6>
		<title>Caravan traveler</title>
		<titleShort>Traveler</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to a family of traveling merchants, [PAWN_nameDef] was mentored by [PAWN_possessive] father in the ways of being a trader. [] was often tasked with caring for the pack animals. Due to [PAWN_possessive] nomadic lifestyle, [] hunted and bartered for [PAWN_possessive] food.</desc>
	</CaravanTraveler6>
	<Caravaneer11>
		<title>Caravaneer</title>
		<titleShort>Caravaneer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was the leader of a caravan. [] was responsible for the safety of [PAWN_possessive] caravan and was the head negotiator in countless trade deals.

[] and [PAWN_possessive] people prospered, but their wealth made them a target for brigands. They often had to take up arms to fend off bandits and highwaymen.</desc>
	</Caravaneer11>
	<JungleKid64>
		<title>Jungle kid</title>
		<titleShort>Jungle kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was abandoned as a newborn, and grew up among the animals of [PAWN_possessive] homeworld’s dense jungles.

When [] was a teenager, a traveling doctor found [PAWN_objective] injured near a road, hissing and meowing. He rescued [PAWN_objective] and took [PAWN_objective] on as an apprentice.</desc>
	</JungleKid64>
	<Aromatherapist80>
		<title>Aromatherapist</title>
		<titleShort>Therapist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] practiced aromatherapy, using essences extracted from home-grown plants.</desc>
	</Aromatherapist80>
	<FarmersSon39>
		<title>Farmer's son</title>
		<titleShort>Farmer</titleShort>
		<desc>Ade spent much of his childhood learning biome farming. In his biome they kept animals to investigate which would cope best in the alien environment.

Due to this, the travel restrictions and oxygen rationing system, he rarely got to meet anyone from outside his family.</desc>
	</FarmersSon39>
	<RebelFighter57>
		<title>Rebel fighter</title>
		<titleShort>Rebel</titleShort>
		<desc>When civil war broke out Ade remained neutral to either side, until his biome was firebombed by a loyalist militia.

Later, his unit gave him the nickname "Rare" after he burnt down the luxury villa of a loyalist leader, with them still inside it.</desc>
	</RebelFighter57>
	<WealthyStudent75>
		<title>Wealthy student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on a wealthy glitterworld. [] studied at the Caspian school of Engineering, and excelled in mathematics and computer programming.

[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in clean, sterile environments. [] never saw a farm or livestock.</desc>
	</WealthyStudent75>
	<Roboticist75>
		<title>roboticist </title>
		<titleShort>roboticist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] felt more comfortable with robots and artificial intelligences than with organic people, so [] worked as a roboticist. [] took a particular interest in mechanites and ancient technology.  

[PAWN_nameDef] relied on other people for [PAWN_possessive] basic needs.</desc>
	</Roboticist75>
	<StreetPeddler39>
		<title>Street peddler</title>
		<titleShort>Peddler</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up on an industrial midworld where robberies and muggings weren't uncommon, [PAWN_nameDef] helped support his family by making small trinkets and novelties to sell to passers-by.

[] learned early on that it wasn't always what [] knew, but who [] knew that would get [PAWN_objective] far in life.</desc>
	</StreetPeddler39>
	<PrivateDetective66>
		<title>Private detective</title>
		<titleShort>Detective</titleShort>
		<desc>As a private eye, sharp wits and a silver tongue were [PAWN_nameDef]'s greatest tools. [] often spent [PAWN_possessive] nights working cases that ranged from uncovering affairs and learning trade secrets to solving murder cases and infiltrating criminal organizations. There wasn't a case [] wouldn't accept for the right price.</desc>
	</PrivateDetective66>
	<BodyguardTrainee88>
		<title>Bodyguard trainee</title>
		<titleShort>Bodyguard</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born into a famously skilled family of bodyguards. [PAWN_possessive] mothers Elena and Victoria forced [PAWN_objective] into many dangerous situations, training [PAWN_objective] to put [PAWN_possessive] client's well-being over [PAWN_possessive] own.

[PAWN_nameDef] was taught about many herbs and natural poisons to help [PAWN_objective] prevent clients from being poisoned.</desc>
	</BodyguardTrainee88>
	<SpaceBartender66>
		<title>Space bartender</title>
		<titleShort>Bartender</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] became a bartender on a space station. [] interacted with and befriended many strangers.

As time went on, [PAWN_nameDef] used [PAWN_possessive] knowledge of herbs to craft [PAWN_possessive] own strange concoctions for [PAWN_possessive] customers.</desc>
	</SpaceBartender66>
	<SpoiledChild90>
		<title>spoiled child</title>
		<titleShort>spoiled</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was the child of an industrious space engineer. [PAWN_possessive] parents forbade most manual and dangerous tasks, so [] learned art and music instead.

[] loved animals, but [PAWN_possessive] parents never let [PAWN_objective] have a pet - though [] played with other people's pets a lot.</desc>
	</SpoiledChild90>
	<CosmeticSurgeon46>
		<title>Cosmetic surgeon</title>
		<titleShort>Surgeon</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] had a terrible bedside manner due to [PAWN_possessive] abrasiveness. [] often bullied [PAWN_possessive] patients into getting cosmetic surgery. [] made a lot of money this way.

While very studious and careful in [PAWN_possessive] work, [] never had to lift a finger doing domestic chores.</desc>
	</CosmeticSurgeon46>
	<Philosopher40>
		<title>Philosopher</title>
		<titleShort>Sage</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s thirst for archaeo-technological knowledge drove [PAWN_objective] to spend years surveying abandoned data centers and studying ancient coding languages.

[] claimed to be one of the few who could piece together the tragedy of the past - and offer a path to the future.</desc>
	</Philosopher40>
	<UprightDiplomat39>
		<title>Upright diplomat</title>
		<titleShort>Diplomat</titleShort>
		<desc>As a diplomat, [PAWN_nameDef] was assigned to deal with diplomatic tasks in the blood-soaked outer rim sectors.

[] hoped to end the endless wars, until [PAWN_possessive] consularship, the St. Anthem, was attacked by a raider fleet.</desc>
	</UprightDiplomat39>
	<CaveChild39>
		<title>cave child</title>
		<titleShort>cave kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a cave on an tundra planet, and was adopted by a traveling group of entertainers known only as the Wizards. Once a starfaring crew, the Wizards told [PAWN_objective] wondrous stories about the universe.

One day, the Wizards did not return from scavenging. After years of waiting, [PAWN_nameDef] set off into space to find them.</desc>
	</CaveChild39>
	<VideoProducer32>
		<title>Video producer</title>
		<titleShort>Producer</titleShort>
		<desc>Too awkward to socialize, [PAWN_nameDef] found comfort in the production of videos. Oddly, people enjoyed his videos, calling them "perfect sitcom dramas".

[PAWN_nameDef] took advantage of this and broadcast more, ever hopeful that [] would be contacted by the Wizards.</desc>
	</VideoProducer32>
	<RangerChild95>
		<title>Ranger child</title>
		<titleShort>Ranger kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised in a forest. [PAWN_possessive] father taught [PAWN_objective] to hunt and live off the land, so that [] could live without the need of others when father died.

Accustomed to manual labor and with an intuitive mind, [PAWN_nameDef] could survive weeks alone.</desc>
	</RangerChild95>
	<BushSniper28>
		<title>Bush sniper</title>
		<titleShort>Sniper</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s peaceful life was cut short when [PAWN_possessive] country was brutally invaded.

[PAWN_nameDef] was drafted into service as soon as [] was of legal age, and quickly showed an aptitude for rifles. [] spent months living in the forests picking off soldiers who dared cross the border.</desc>
	</BushSniper28>
	<GlitterworldRoyal85>
		<title>Glitterworld royal</title>
		<titleShort>Royalty</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a glitterworld royal household. She was groomed from a young age to marry into another planet's royal family.

Unfortunately, her crooked teeth made her undesirable to suitors, so she became bitter and resentful.</desc>
	</GlitterworldRoyal85>
	<PirateSympathizer42>
		<title>Pirate sympathizer</title>
		<titleShort>Pirate</titleShort>
		<desc>From her youth, [PAWN_nameDef] developed connections in the underworld. There she trained in melee combat and became a trusted underworld advisor.

After participating in a failed rebellion, she fled her homeworld to travel with a pirate band.</desc>
	</PirateSympathizer42>
	<PlagueSurvivor87>
		<title>Plague survivor</title>
		<titleShort>Survivor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] watched as a mysterious plague spread through his town, killing his family and friends.

[] learned some medicine from watching the plague doctors, but was mentally scarred by the ordeal.</desc>
	</PlagueSurvivor87>
	<UnethicalDoctor53>
		<title>Unethical doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Doctor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] became a doctor to save lives and research medicine. [] soon realized the only way to make progress on [PAWN_possessive] research was to perform experiments on human patients.

[] often used patients for [PAWN_possessive] experiments - whether they were willing or not.</desc>
	</UnethicalDoctor53>
	<OffworldRecruit21>
		<title>Offworld recruit</title>
		<titleShort>Recruit</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born an raised in an offworld soldier growth facility. From a very young age, [] was taught close-quarters combat tactics, aggression, and how to survive on distant planets.

One of the best, [PAWN_nameDef] was eventually chose to enter the orbital-deployment shock troop corps.</desc>
	</OffworldRecruit21>
	<ShockTrooper89>
		<title>Shock trooper</title>
		<titleShort>Shocktroop</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was in a deep space shock troop unit deployed on multiple planets in various wars.

During a risky assault, [PAWN_possessive] whole unit was wiped out. Nobody else knew what happened on the field that day, but [PAWN_nameDef] will carry the burden forever.</desc>
	</ShockTrooper89>
	<ProdigalStudent4>
		<title>Prodigal student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a faithful student, and was dedicated to learning anything and everything he could about humanity and its creations.

While [] was shunned as a nerd, [] didn't mind. [] hoped for a brighter future.</desc>
	</ProdigalStudent4>
	<CombatMedtech30>
		<title>Combat medtech</title>
		<titleShort>Medic</titleShort>
		<desc>As a military medtech, [PAWN_nameDef]'s job was to fix and build anything he could get [PAWN_possessive] hands on, from living people to machines and mechs.

Sent into dangerous areas, [] never had a problem saving soldiers' lives and building the technology and machines needed to win.</desc>
	</CombatMedtech30>
	<AnimalCaretaker78>
		<title>Animal caretaker</title>
		<titleShort>Caretaker</titleShort>
		<desc>Born on a medieval farm, [PAWN_nameDef] was tasked with caring for domestic animals. [] grew to love them.

With time, [] learned to tame wild animals. [] dreamed of one day meeting a thrumbo and taming it.</desc>
	</AnimalCaretaker78>
	<WildlifeRanger87>
		<title>Wildlife ranger</title>
		<titleShort>Ranger</titleShort>
		<desc>Dismayed at the poachers driving several animal species to near-extinction, [PAWN_nameDef] became a wildlife ranger. [] cared for and protect the animals - by force if necessary.

[] grew to hate people slaughtering animals for luxury and profit.</desc>
	</WildlifeRanger87>
	<AdventurousYouth67>
		<title>Adventurous youth</title>
		<titleShort>Adventurer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] explored all around [PAWN_possessive] family's large estate, uncovering little natural wonders hidden in nearby catacombs, rivers, and caves.

During his teenage years, [PAWN_nameDef] made numerous enemies</desc>
	</AdventurousYouth67>
	<TreasureHunter70>
		<title>Treasure hunter</title>
		<titleShort>Adventurer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] explored outer rim planets in hopes of finding rare treasures.

After succeeding in finding one legendary sculpture, [] was betrayed by [PAWN_possessive] men. [] survived their treasonous attack, but the sculpture was taken.

[] created the Anvil Mercenary Company to help [PAWN_objective] seek revenge.</desc>
	</TreasureHunter70>
	<PilotFan30>
		<title>Pilot fan</title>
		<titleShort>Pilot fan</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s father was a starfighter pilot, and [] always idolized the old man.

From a young age, [] collected pilot memorabilia and studied pilot books, preparing to join the deep space navy and follow in [PAWN_possessive] father's footsteps.</desc>
	</PilotFan30>
	<StarfighterPilot85>
		<title>Starfighter pilot</title>
		<titleShort>Pilot</titleShort>
		<desc>After years of training and drilling, [PAWN_nameDef] finally became a starfighter pilot.

Hundreds of combat missions later, [] grew bored and started seeking newer thrills. [] joined a band of space pirates, which eagerly welcomed [PAWN_objective] because of [PAWN_possessive] piloting skill.</desc>
	</StarfighterPilot85>
	<MedicalHelper94>
		<title>Medical helper</title>
		<titleShort>Med helper</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled between rim worlds with [PAWN_possessive] family. [PAWN_nameDef]'s mother, a renowned doctor, often delivered lectures from the hull of their retrofitted cargo/medical ship.

Sometimes, the family took on difficult long-term medical work with especially needy patients, and [PAWN_nameDef] helped where he could.</desc>
	</MedicalHelper94>
	<GangSoldier95>
		<title>Gang soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>Living for many years between three raider settlements, [PAWN_nameDef] persevered through many challenges: a spacecraft implosion, cryptostasis, crashlanding on a miserable dustball of a planet, and nursing an old man back to health, and many of battles.

[] eventually took control of a violent gang.</desc>
	</GangSoldier95>
	<CountryChild95>
		<title>Country child</title>
		<titleShort>Hick kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised up to fear God and love [PAWN_possessive] country. [] was a genuine backwoods kid. [] always worked hard to earn respect rather than demanding it.</desc>
	</CountryChild95>
	<SpaceMarine81>
		<title>space marine</title>
		<titleShort>marine</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] joined Interplanetary Marines to travel the stars fight for [PAWN_possessive] planet. [] distinguished himself in several battles.

[PAWN_possessive] experiences desensitized him to people around him, and his social skills degraded. But, he did learn how to fight.</desc>
	</SpaceMarine81>
	<RebelWriter82>
		<title>Rebel writer</title>
		<titleShort>Writer</titleShort>
		<desc>Early on, [PAWN_nameDef] developed a talent for writing. [] was soon writing a popular online journal - anonymously, to hide [PAWN_possessive] age - on topics ranging from bioethics to political theory and xenosociology.</desc>
	</RebelWriter82>
	<Adventurer27>
		<title>Adventurer</title>
		<titleShort>Adventurer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s thirst for adventure took [PAWN_objective] to many planets. [] visited the brightest glitterworlds and the darkest war-torn toxic planets in [PAWN_possessive] quest to find novelty and excitement.

[] worked as little as possible, often skirting ethical boundaries to make a quick buck. Among all jobs, [] hated cooking the most.</desc>
	</Adventurer27>
	<ExiledPrince97>
		<title>Exiled prince</title>
		<titleShort>Prince</titleShort>
		<desc>A member of a royal family, [PAWN_nameDef] was exiled for shaming [PAWN_possessive] family.

Living in a foreign land, mostly alone, [] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] time making huts and houses to live in. [] found little time in an average day for enjoyment, and lost all his friends and family.</desc>
	</ExiledPrince97>
	<BloodyWanderer71>
		<title>Bloody wanderer</title>
		<titleShort>Wanderer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a wanderer, traveling from town to town, taking odd jobs and stealing to live.

One day, he had a mental break and went on a long rampage, destroying several towns and killing many. [] eventually calmed, but [PAWN_possessive] bloodlust never left [PAWN_objective].</desc>
	</BloodyWanderer71>
	<NewAgeDuelist79>
		<title>New age duelist</title>
		<titleShort>Duelist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was fascinated with combat. [PAWN_possessive] parents traveled often, so [] was able to sample many different fighting styles, from 76th-wave jujutsu to the infamous 'urbvilág-style' karate.

A polite child, most fighters accepted [PAWN_possessive] requests for training - but moving around often without finishing a tutelage made [PAWN_objective] lazy.</desc>
	</NewAgeDuelist79>
	<PirateDoctor34>
		<title>Pirate doctor</title>
		<titleShort>Bad doc</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] had a passion for medicine, but never bothered to get a medical degree. Only underfunded pirates and terrorists were desperate enough to hire [PAWN_possessive] services, and [PAWN_possessive] surgical patients had about a 50% survival rate.

Despite this, [PAWN_possessive] optimistic attitude drove [PAWN_objective] to keep trying to heal those in need. As long as they paid up front.</desc>
	</PirateDoctor34>
	<SpoiledBrat31>
		<title>Spoiled brat</title>
		<titleShort>Brat</titleShort>
		<desc>Born in a rich family, [PAWN_nameDef] was given everything, and never developed basic work ethic or the foundations of a non-dependent personality.

[] was expected to become one of the best doctors in the world.</desc>
	</SpoiledBrat31>
	<BloodyDentist9>
		<title>Bloody dentist</title>
		<titleShort>Dentist</titleShort>
		<desc>After studying at a famous college, [PAWN_nameDef]'s weak personality eventually snapped under the strain of angry administrators and whining patients. [] went on a secret murder spree, killing many of those under [PAWN_possessive] care.

After a pursuit, [] managed to escape [PAWN_possessive] planet and travel to a new world.</desc>
	</BloodyDentist9>
	<CowFarmer39>
		<title>Cow farmer</title>
		<titleShort>Farmer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a rim world, under the tyranny of [PAWN_possessive] father, who forced [PAWN_objective] to work every day on the farm. [] dreamed of escaping [PAWN_possessive] father and exploring the universe.

One day, when the trade ship was overhead, [] stowed away among the goods in the launch pods, and escaped into space.</desc>
	</CowFarmer39>
	<MasterChef90>
		<title>Master chef</title>
		<titleShort>Chef</titleShort>
		<desc>On a glitterworld, [PAWN_nameDef] found a job washing dishes at a famous restaurant and worked [PAWN_possessive] way up the ranks.

A few years later, [PAWN_possessive] career came to an end when someone poisoned the meal [] was preparing for the mayor. Jobless, [] and left to explore the stars once again.</desc>
	</MasterChef90>
	<DiscardedYouth13>
		<title>Discarded youth</title>
		<titleShort>Discarded</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up isolated on a trash planet. A dumping ground for surrounding glitterworlds, it was a harsh home. As a baby, [] sucked on the tap of a discarded nutrient paste dispenser for comfort.

In these desperate circumstances, against all odds, [] survived - and thrived.</desc>
	</DiscardedYouth13>
	<Mercenary9>
		<title>mercenary</title>
		<titleShort>mercenary</titleShort>
		<desc>After escaping his home planet, [PAWN_nameDef] fell in with a band of mercenaries. [] fought alongside his brothers and sisters in arms for many years.

One day, they were caught in a fight they couldn't win. Refusing to retreat, [PAWN_nameDef] was shot down by his enemies. [] was alarmed to awake in a heap of corpses, mysteriously unharmed.</desc>
	</Mercenary9>
	<DisasterSurvivor9>
		<title>katasztrófa túlélő</title>
		<titleShort>túlélő</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s planet collided with a small moon. Everything he knew as home was destroyed, and his entire family died. [] was left in the ruins to fend for himself.</desc>
	</DisasterSurvivor9>
	<ExplorerWriter52>
		<title>Explorer-writer</title>
		<titleShort>Explorer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] traveled from planet to planet, gathering samples, stories, and research. 

[PAWN_possessive] goal was to bring together enough knowledge to make a survival guide for future generations.</desc>
	</ExplorerWriter52>
	<RebelChild95>
		<title>Rebel child</title>
		<titleShort>Rebel</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born under authoritarian rule. Despite intense oppression from family and community, she never gave up fighting for her dignity and her freedom.

She was often put into hopeless situations where even family would try to terrorize her into propriety. She learned to trust no one.</desc>
	</RebelChild95>
	<MilitiaSoldier63>
		<title>Militia soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] joined the militia forces and fought for rights and peace.

After her homeworld was unexpectedly destroyed in the wars, she traveled great distances, seeking a refuge where she could build a new, free way of life.</desc>
	</MilitiaSoldier63>
	<MidworldCadet91>
		<title>Midworld cadet</title>
		<titleShort>Cadet</titleShort>
		<desc>Growing up on a high-tech midworld with a flourishing space transit industry, [PAWN_nameDef] wished to leave for the stars and live among the growing spacer class.

[] excelled in [PAWN_possessive] studies, and gained entry to [PAWN_possessive] homeworld's most prestigious naval academy.</desc>
	</MidworldCadet91>
	<WarshipCaptain35>
		<title>Warship captain</title>
		<titleShort>Captain</titleShort>
		<desc>Years of being commanding officer of an advanced corvette taught [PAWN_nameDef] the art of leadership, the techniques of higher engineering, and how to stay calm while enemies try to kill you.

Unfortunately, [PAWN_nameDef] only very rarely had contact with nature.</desc>
	</WarshipCaptain35>
	<ForestChild83>
		<title>forest child</title>
		<titleShort>forest kid</titleShort>
		<desc>When [] was a baby, [PAWN_nameDef]'s mother went insane and left [PAWN_objective] in the woods.

Raised by wild people, [PAWN_nameDef] was known for both loving and killing animals.</desc>
	</ForestChild83>
	<ForestProwler15>
		<title>Erdei ember</title>
		<titleShort>Erdei ember</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] led a band of wild men in the forest. They foraged for food, hunted, and sometimes murdered more civilized people to steal their shiny objects.</desc>
	</ForestProwler15>
	<VatgrownScientist57>
		<title>Vatgrown scientist</title>
		<titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was grown to be a perfect scientist, with a mind perfectly tuned for physics and chemistry.

[PAWN_possessive] creators used [PAWN_objective] as a teaching aid on mind design, hoping [] would eventually grow to be a great mind and continue their research.</desc>
	</VatgrownScientist57>
	<RunawayDancer13>
		<title>Runaway dancer</title>
		<titleShort>Dancer</titleShort>
		<desc>Grown by and for science, [PAWN_nameDef] gave it up. Instead, [] wanted to dance for crowds across many worlds, from the glamor of the glitterworlds to the dangers of the rim.

Such work required wearing a smile on [PAWN_possessive] face and a pistol under [PAWN_possessive] costume.</desc>
	</RunawayDancer13>
	<MusicIdol48>
		<title>Music idol</title>
		<titleShort>Music idol</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was the only daughter of a powerful company president. [PAWN_possessive] beautiful appearance led to a career as a music idol.

When [PAWN_possessive] mother died, [PAWN_nameDef] could not bear [PAWN_possessive] father's loneliness, and became his sexual companion.</desc>
	</MusicIdol48>
	<ProstituteIdol94>
		<title>Prostitute idol</title>
		<titleShort>Prostitute</titleShort>
		<desc>After [PAWN_possessive] father was deposed, [PAWN_nameDef]'s beauty led [PAWN_objective] to be forced into pornography to survive.

Over years of difficult treatments, [PAWN_possessive] body was remodeled to appear temporarily ageless. Sold to an orbital brothel, [] became popular, with a steady stream of clients from all over the planet.</desc>
	</ProstituteIdol94>
	<SicklyLiar84>
		<title>Sickly liar</title>
		<titleShort>Liar</titleShort>
		<desc>It is not uncommon for a sickly child to be cast away. What is uncommon is for that child to survive and even thrive with such a weak body.

Using his quick wit and silver tongue, Lynn was able to get out of almost any situation - most of the time at the cost others around him.</desc>
	</SicklyLiar84>
	<SicklyLawyer86>
		<title>Sickly lawyer</title>
		<titleShort>Lawyer</titleShort>
		<desc>As a lawyer, Lynn could convict a deaf man for stealing music. His sharp mind and lack of empathy let him say anything to get the other person to talk. With the right amount of money, he knew, any case can be won.

His childhood cough never went away.</desc>
	</SicklyLawyer86>
	<IceworldSurvivor77>
		<title>Iceworld survivor</title>
		<titleShort>Iceborn</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born on an iceworld. Survival depended on staying together and building with nothing.

[] got used to the cold. [] never got used to dealing with those strange green things called plants.</desc>
	</IceworldSurvivor77>
	<Tinkerer86>
		<title>Tinkerer</title>
		<titleShort>Tinkerer</titleShort>
		<desc>"How does this work?

Why does this move?

Maybe if I change this... oops, I hope it works better... or maybe I broke it..."</desc>
	</Tinkerer86>
	<TragicLoner67>
		<title>Tragic loner</title>
		<titleShort>Loner</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was involved in a traumatic accident that resulted in [PAWN_objective] killing [PAWN_possessive] own family.

Cast out from society, [] was left with only [PAWN_possessive] animal companions and several engineering textbooks to keep [PAWN_objective] company.</desc>
	</TragicLoner67>
	<RocketPioneer89>
		<title>Rocket pioneer</title>
		<titleShort>Rocketeer</titleShort>
		<desc>As a self-taught engineer, [PAWN_nameDef] escaped his dying homeworld on a rocket [] built [PAWN_objective]self. 

[] later spent years of his life on several worlds, helping less-developed planets develop rocket technology.</desc>
	</RocketPioneer89>
	<AntisocialChild59>
		<title>Antisocial child</title>
		<titleShort>Antisocial</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lacked typical social skills, and avoided social interaction.

[] gained satisfaction only from steady work. [] especially disliked speaking with overly creative or outgoing individuals.</desc>
	</AntisocialChild59>
	<ArmySergeant7>
		<title>Army sergeant</title>
		<titleShort>Sergeant</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] served in [PAWN_possessive] nation's military, commanding small units as a non-commissioned officer.

[] excelled creating tactically sound plans despite difficult circumstances.</desc>
	</ArmySergeant7>
	<YoungPirate51>
		<title>Young pirate</title>
		<titleShort>Pirate</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born to pirates, in a dirty metal room that smelled of motor oil.

[] was never exactly taught anything, but [] still learned the ways of survival, barter, and combat.</desc>
	</YoungPirate51>
	<StellarPirate89>
		<title>Stellar pirate</title>
		<titleShort>Pirate</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was captain of a pirate ship. [] and his crew made their living capturing traders who wandered off-course.

[] was known for [PAWN_possessive] balanced approach to problems, building, fighting, or negotiating as needed.</desc>
	</StellarPirate89>
	<SoldierExperiment32>
		<title>Soldier experiment</title>
		<titleShort>Experiment</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up believing [] was a normal, albeit slightly sheltered child.

In truth, [] was part of an elaborate experiment. Researchers were conditioning [PAWN_objective] using social interactions and mechanite injections to try to produce an elite soldier.</desc>
	</SoldierExperiment32>
	<LostSoldier79>
		<title>Lost soldier</title>
		<titleShort>Lost</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s childhood soldier conditioning failed, and the experiment was shut down. [] was abandoned, purposeless, friendless.

[PAWN_nameDef] eventually found solace in physically demanding work. [] especially liked building houses and crafting heavy armor.</desc>
	</LostSoldier79>
	<DedicatedStudent33>
		<title>Dedicated student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>The child of a wealthy manufacturer, [PAWN_nameDef] was pampered from an early age. [] developed an affinity for reading and art, and a distaste for menial chores.

A revolution brought his father's businesses under state control. Penniless, [PAWN_nameDef] worked hard to complete [PAWN_possessive] education.</desc>
	</DedicatedStudent33>
	<LanguageAnalyst27>
		<title>Language analyst</title>
		<titleShort>Linguist</titleShort>
		<desc>After war broke out on [PAWN_possessive] homeworld, [PAWN_nameDef] was conscripted as a linguist. [] spent [PAWN_possessive] days in a space station, decoding enemy communications and tending the hydroponic crops.

After a meteorite damaged the station, [] was forced to enter cryptosleep and hope for rescue.</desc>
	</LanguageAnalyst27>
	<Infantry14>
		<title>Infantry</title>
		<titleShort>Infantry</titleShort>
		<desc>Lenka was raised on a world wracked by war.

At an early age, she was shown how to use guns and cruelty to project her will. She later distinguished herself by committing atrocities with more enthusiasm than anyone else.</desc>
	</Infantry14>
	<PrisonerOfWar89>
		<title>Prisoner of war</title>
		<titleShort>Prisoner</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was captured and put on death row for war crimes.

Fortunately for her, someone cut the power to her cell block. Riots ignited. Guards and trained wargs were deployed to quell the uprising. Organizing a few other inmates, [PAWN_nameDef] escaped in a small spacecraft.</desc>
	</PrisonerOfWar89>
	<AngryStudent94>
		<title>Angry student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] trained towards [PAWN_possessive] dream of working for his hometown's local council.

For reasons he never quite understood, [] was bullied relentlessly by his classmates. [] chose to repress his rage.</desc>
	</AngryStudent94>
	<MadAccountant43>
		<title>Mad accountant</title>
		<titleShort>Accountant</titleShort>
		<desc>As an accountant, [PAWN_nameDef] often socialized with colleagues, and made many friends in upper management.

One day, [PAWN_nameDef] discovered a corruption racket run by some of [PAWN_possessive] bosses. After reporting this, [] was fired. Wishing to hunt down those responsible, [] went on a mass murder spree.</desc>
	</MadAccountant43>
	<TransferStudent51>
		<title>Transfer student</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>A midworld child, [PAWN_nameDef]'s wealthy parents sent [PAWN_objective] to a nearby glitterworld to receive a better education.

[PAWN_nameDef] was a talented student. However, due to his family's wealth, [] never had to do dumb labor.</desc>
	</TransferStudent51>
	<Politician1>
		<title>Politician</title>
		<titleShort>Politician</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an activist in a powerful political faction. There [] learned the art of persuasion and speech.

[] had many enemies, so [] took secret courses in shooting and hand-to-hand combat.</desc>
	</Politician1>
	<DesertRat41>
		<title>Desert rat</title>
		<titleShort>Desert rat</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was born to a tribe of desert ascetics who wandered the endless wastes.

They sought a mythical substance they believed could liberate them from ignorance through psychedelic revelation - and usher in a new period of interstellar peace.</desc>
	</DesertRat41>
	<Philosopher15>
		<title>philosopher</title>
		<titleShort>sage</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s thirst for archaeo-technological knowledge drove [PAWN_objective] to spend years surveying abandoned data centers and studying ancient coding languages.

[] claimed to be one of the few who could piece together the tragedy of the past - and offer a path to the future.</desc>
	</Philosopher15>
	<ArtisticWeirdo34>
		<title>Artistic weirdo</title>
		<titleShort>Weirdo</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a house near a bustling midworld metropolis.

[] was talented at art and creative work, but often acted strangely, and thus had few friends.</desc>
	</ArtisticWeirdo34>
	<AdventurousWeirdo23>
		<title>Adventurous weirdo</title>
		<titleShort>Weirdo</titleShort>
		<desc>A creative but strange individual, [PAWN_nameDef] dedicated his life to his twin passions of medieval world history and high technology.

[] was fascinated by the idea of becoming a 'skyknight' with glittering armor and a giant sword.</desc>
	</AdventurousWeirdo23>
	<ApprenticeOracle89>
		<title>Apprentice oracle</title>
		<titleShort>Oracle</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was chosen at an early age by the village elders to keep the sacred rituals of the Oracle.

An irrepressibly curious child, [PAWN_nameDef] caused a religious crisis for [PAWN_possessive] tribe when [] accidentally flipped a switch to open the "tombs" of the Gods - cryptosleep caskets inhabited by some very confused ancestors.</desc>
	</ApprenticeOracle89>
	<CasketBuilder70>
		<title>Casket builder</title>
		<titleShort>Builder</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was fascinated with cryosleep, and spent [PAWN_possessive] life learning about the mysterious technology.

Working as an assembler on a midworld, [PAWN_nameDef] built an experimental prototype casket from discarded parts. Unfortunately, while [] was searching for the final component, [PAWN_possessive] home was leveled by a bomb.</desc>
	</CasketBuilder70>
	<JunkyardMechanic57>
		<title>Junkyard mechanic</title>
		<titleShort>Mechanic</titleShort>
		<desc>Left for dead at a young age, [PAWN_nameDef] was rescued by an old man who ran an urbworld junkyard. The old man forced [PAWN_nameDef] to do dangerous, demanding work. 

[PAWN_nameDef] became very familiar with machines, but [] grew up with almost no other experiences.</desc>
	</JunkyardMechanic57>
	<MilitaryOfficer99>
		<title>Military officer</title>
		<titleShort>Officer</titleShort>
		<desc>Obsessed with interstellar travel, [PAWN_nameDef] left [PAWN_possessive] desolate life behind to join a military academy in hopes of becoming a pilot.

[] was trained in advanced combat and survival skills. While [] excelled in [PAWN_possessive] studies, [PAWN_nameDef] was a loner and never cared about [PAWN_possessive] crewmates.</desc>
	</MilitaryOfficer99>
	<Empath97>
		<title>Empath</title>
		<titleShort>Empath</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an incredibly empathetic child, so much that [] was totally overwhelmed by simple social interactions. Once, [] stepped on a bug and felt so guilty [] cried for an hour.

[PAWN_nameDef] did try to use a gun one time, but it went very poorly, as the loud noise made [PAWN_objective] flinch uncontrollably.</desc>
	</Empath97>
	<FearfulChef3>
		<title>Fearful chef</title>
		<titleShort>Chef</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a excellent chef who worked in a high-end restaurant.

One day, [] left the stove on, and accidentally burned down the whole building. This event shook [PAWN_objective] so much that [] swore to never touch a stove again.</desc>
	</FearfulChef3>
	<AnimalLabTech51>
		<title>animal lab tech</title>
		<titleShort>lab tech</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked as a technician in a lab studying animals.

[] spent [PAWN_possessive] days taking care of the animals and cleaning up after them. [] dreamed of having [PAWN_possessive] own lab one day.</desc>
	</AnimalLabTech51>
	<MuffaloResearcher39>
		<title>muffalo researcher</title>
		<titleShort>researcher</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] specialized in studying and manipulating the genetic code of the muffalo.

[PAWN_possessive] work left little time to develop an appreciation for the arts or other people's company.</desc>
	</MuffaloResearcher39>
	<ShipChild0>
		<title>Ship child</title>
		<titleShort>Ship child</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s family were space traders. One day, [PAWN_nameDef]'s cryptosleep pod failed in transit. [] had to spend years awake on the ship as the other slept.

[] filled [PAWN_possessive] days creating beautiful contraptions from the ship's cargo - but [] didn't learn a lot of basic planetary living skills.</desc>
	</ShipChild0>
	<ArtifactHunter22>
		<title>Artifact hunter</title>
		<titleShort>Artifacter</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] became depressed and lost interest in life. [] travelled from planet to planet, searching for psychic artifacts amid mechanoid ruins in the hope that they would cure the pain in [PAWN_possessive] soul.

A steady trigger finger and careful planning kept [PAWN_nameDef] alive.</desc>
	</ArtifactHunter22>
	<PetKeeper87>
		<title>Pet keeper</title>
		<titleShort>Pet keeper</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] childhood tending the animals [] had bought or rescued.

[] saw beauty in natural things more than fabricated objects, and chose the company of [PAWN_possessive] animals over that of [PAWN_possessive] peers.</desc>
	</PetKeeper87>
	<Herpetologist17>
		<title>Herpetologist</title>
		<titleShort>Herper</titleShort>
		<desc>After a terrible mining accident, [PAWN_nameDef] set off into space in search of exotic new animal species.

[] hoped to leave [PAWN_possessive] past behind and find long-lived companions. [] knew the pain of loss too well.</desc>
	</Herpetologist17>
	<ChildResearcher10>
		<title>Child researcher</title>
		<titleShort>Researcher</titleShort>
		<desc>A frightfully intelligent child, [PAWN_nameDef] was kidnapped by a glitterworld corporation and forced to research technologies for weaponizing anti-matter.

[] vowed never to invent anything again.</desc>
	</ChildResearcher10>
	<Fugitive22>
		<title>Fugitive</title>
		<titleShort>Fugitive</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] rebelled against the corporation [] worked for. [] failed, and was forced him to go on the run.

[] was always on the move, always leaving everything behind. [] tried to gain supporters for [PAWN_possessive] cause, but failed due to [PAWN_possessive] poor social skills.</desc>
	</Fugitive22>
	<VidtubeStar84>
		<title>Vidtube star</title>
		<titleShort>Vidtuber</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s hobby was making videos for the popular video sharing service Vidtube. [] made everything from video game reviews to pasta cooking guides.

[] gained a over a million followers.</desc>
	</VidtubeStar84>
	<GunDealer84>
		<title>Gun dealer</title>
		<titleShort>Gun dealer</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] traded high-tech firearms between warring factions.

Over time, [] became very skilled at conducting product demonstrations and negotiating profitable deals.</desc>
	</GunDealer84>
	<CorporateSlave4>
		<title>corporate slave</title>
		<titleShort>soldier</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in a colony owned by a large glitterworld corporation. All children had virtual reality devices attached by force, and were raised in a brutal digital world.

Constantly forced to fight others for the entertainment of the wealthy, gunplay and tactics became the center of [PAWN_nameDef]'s universe.</desc>
	</CorporateSlave4>
	<ColonyEngineer46>
		<title>colony engineer</title>
		<titleShort>engineer</titleShort>
		<desc>The children took over the facility, and they declared independence from the corporation.

[PAWN_nameDef] had used the VR system to become a master engineer, and he worked diligently to prepare the colony for the corporation's inevitable return.</desc>
	</ColonyEngineer46>
	<AspiringPhysicist3>
		<title>Aspiring physicist</title>
		<titleShort>Student</titleShort>
		<desc>The daughter of an engineer and doctor, [PAWN_nameDef]'s early life was intellectually rich. After visiting a physics lab, she decided she wanted to be a quantum physicist.

Bitten by a camel, kicked off a horse, and chased by dogs, [PAWN_nameDef] developed a fear of animals.</desc>
	</AspiringPhysicist3>
	<DeepSpaceSurveor51>
		<title>Deep space surveor</title>
		<titleShort>Surveyor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a deep space surveyor. She studied which worlds were the most suitable for colonization.

Her expeditions were met by hostile natives, green-painted space-women, and wannabe Greek gods. Surviving many firefights, she learned to build rudimentary lathes and rock cannons to fend off enemies.</desc>
	</DeepSpaceSurveor51>
	<QuietNerd17>
		<title>quiet nerd</title>
		<titleShort>nerd</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was raised by doting parents on a midworld. Instead of playing with other children, [] read books voraciously.

[] was not particularly rugged, and struggled with physical labor.</desc>
	</QuietNerd17>
	<CostumeCrafter79>
		<title>costume crafter</title>
		<titleShort>costumer</titleShort>
		<desc>By day, [PAWN_nameDef] was an office worker on a midworld. At night, [] designed and built elaborate monster costumes for science fiction conventions.

[] learned a great deal about sewing. Unfortunately this came at the cost of being able to cook anything more complex than an instant meal.</desc>
	</CostumeCrafter79>
	<SpacerOrphan95>
		<title>spacer orphan</title>
		<titleShort>orphan</titleShort>
		<desc>Born among stars to a spacefaring family, the [PAWN_nameDef] was the only survivor when [PAWN_possessive] family's ship was destroyed.

[] was forced to find a way to survive, and seek the joy of knowing another family.</desc>
	</SpacerOrphan95>
	<Gunfighter83>
		<title>gunfighter</title>
		<titleShort>gunfighter</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a deadly shot. Peace wasn't for him. [] found [PAWN_possessive] family among the brothers and sisters that [] spent years fighting alongside.

After most of those close to [PAWN_objective] died, [] once again set off to lend [PAWN_possessive] gun to those who needed it - or those who could pay.</desc>
	</Gunfighter83>
	<SmallTownKid91>
		<title>small town kid</title>
		<titleShort>town kid</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up in an isolated midworld village, surrounded by opticows and countryside.

[PAWN_possessive] parents taught [PAWN_objective] a wide range of useful domestic skills, but a peaceful and secure childhood left [PAWN_objective] with little understanding of the harder parts of life.</desc>
	</SmallTownKid91>
	<RenownedProfessor95>
		<title>renowned professor</title>
		<titleShort>professor</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef]'s bottomless compassion and love of knowledge drove [PAWN_objective] to a life of teaching. [] became one of the best-known names in academia throughout the urbworld bubble.

[PAWN_possessive] holo-lectures were revered by all that watched, and the few students [] accepted into [PAWN_possessive] seminars spoke widely of [PAWN_possessive] kindness and patience.</desc>
	</RenownedProfessor95>
	<SteamworldTinker44>
		<title>steamworld tinker</title>
		<titleShort>tinker</titleShort>
		<desc>In the slums of a steamworld, [PAWN_nameDef] developed a fascination with machines and contraptions. [] found [] preferred their company to that of other people.

[PAWN_possessive] remarkable dexterity earned [PAWN_objective] a steady stream of pocket change, and [] spent every penny on spare parts and tools to play with.</desc>
	</SteamworldTinker44>
	<NavyTechOfficer30>
		<title>navy tech officer</title>
		<titleShort>navy tech</titleShort>
		<desc>After repairing a fleet admiral's holoscreen with nothing but a pair of rusty pliers and scrap wire, [PAWN_nameDef] was invited to the Federation Naval Academy.

[] received an excellent technical education and extensive firearms training, but had no interest in studying more menial skills.</desc>
	</NavyTechOfficer30>
	<AbandonedOrphan9>
		<title>abandoned orphan</title>
		<titleShort>orphan</titleShort>
		<desc>Abandoned at birth, young [PAWN_nameDef] started [PAWN_possessive] life in an orphanage.

A rascal and a scoundrel, [] became a clever troublemaker.</desc>
	</AbandonedOrphan9>
	<KingOfPirates25>
		<title>Kalózkirály</title>
		<titleShort>Kalóz</titleShort>
		<desc>As a self-proclaimed king of pirates, [PAWN_nameDef] was ruthless. Manipulative in nature, [] was not afraid to sacrifice the people around [PAWN_objective] in service of [PAWN_possessive] own goals. [] was a good shot, but even more skilled with a sword, and [] loved the adrenaline rush of close combat.</desc>
	</KingOfPirates25>
	<SpaceNerd97>
		<title>Űrkocka</title>
		<titleShort>Űrkocka</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] just wanted to be cool like [PAWN_possessive] favorite superhero All-Might. [] dreamed of going on space adventures and exploring new worlds. [] also dreamed of chocolate... space chocolate.</desc>
	</SpaceNerd97>
	<SpaceNavyTech66>
		<title>space navy tech</title>
		<titleShort>navy tech</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was in a space navy for the the most powerful planet in the local star group. [] developed skills in maintenance, electronic systems, radar and imaging, and logistics management.

[] served with pride and patriotic love for [PAWN_possessive] planet.</desc>
	</SpaceNavyTech66>
	<ChildSpy42>
		<title>child spy </title>
		<titleShort>spy </titleShort>
		<desc>Children are often presumed innocent, and so make ideal spies. [PAWN_nameDef] was trained in the arts of infiltration and information-gathering when [] was very young.

[PAWN_possessive] spent years behind enemy lines, gathering intel in a brutal planetary war. During this time, [] had limited opportunity for education.</desc>
	</ChildSpy42>
	<Defector99>
		<title>defector </title>
		<titleShort>defector </titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] decided to leave the oppressive dictatorship where [] lived. [PAWN_possessive] defection was not well-received, and agents were sent after [PAWN_objective].

[] spent years on the run. Since [] could trust no doctor, [] treated [PAWN_possessive] own wounds. The ordeal made [PAWN_objective] bitter and untrusting.</desc>
	</Defector99>
	<TurtleHerder92>
		<title>turtle herder</title>
		<titleShort>herder</titleShort>
		<desc>Born to settler folk, [PAWN_nameDef]'s family' had a beloved herd of turtles, who protected them by absorbing shots from raiders.

At a young age, [] was entrusted with the turtles. [] bred them, successfully - too successfully. The massive turtle herds consumed every food source and destroyed the local ecosystem.</desc>
	</TurtleHerder92>
	<SpaceMarineMedic28>
		<title>space marine medic</title>
		<titleShort>medic</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] joined a colony contact expeditionary force as a medic. The mission turned bad when the colonists turned out to be suffering from a zombifying disease. [] ran and fought for days.

Cornered with wounded men, [] sprayed enough ammunition to wear out four machine gun barrels, and learned the value of high-volume fire. But [PAWN_possessive] nickname, Noob, stuck from that day forward.</desc>
	</SpaceMarineMedic28>
	<ComputerGeek28>
		<title>computer geek</title>
		<titleShort>geek</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent most of [PAWN_possessive] childhood on [PAWN_possessive] computer, typing away, never knowing when to get up and eat.

He had a very narrow interest: hacking cryptobiotic safety protocols.</desc>
	</ComputerGeek28>
	<Technician24>
		<title>technician</title>
		<titleShort>techie</titleShort>
		<desc>As an IT technician, [PAWN_nameDef] didn't have much time to write code any more.

[] got called to work all the time to fix failures in the cryptobiotic chamber and AI subroutine misalignments.</desc>
	</Technician24>
	<Freethinker52>
		<title>freethinker</title>
		<titleShort>thinker</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grew up on a toxic world with tyrannical leaders. While the rest of the population was high on the planet's narcotic exports, [] joined a rebel militia.

After a risky operation against the regime failed, [] fled the planet, staying alive by threatening mutual annihilation with a planetcracker antimatter bomb.</desc>
	</Freethinker52>
	<MercenaryLord80>
		<title>mercenary lord</title>
		<titleShort>merc lord</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] formed a mercenary company out of freelancers who wanted to make good money while also making slightly better-than-average moral choices. [] called it the Ashmarines.

To avoid the core worlds' military forces, [] moved his company to the rim worlds. There, [] established bases and communities. In ruling, [] maintained a form of order among the raiders and madmen of deep space.</desc>
	</MercenaryLord80>
	<Punk30>
		<title>Punk</title>
		<titleShort>Punk</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] spent his childhood selling knockoff cigarettes to 15-year-olds. The cigarettes were often full of grass clippings.</desc>
	</Punk30>
	<GameDeveloper95>
		<title>Game developer</title>
		<titleShort>Game dev</titleShort>
		<desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was an independent game developer.

After an early success, [PAWN_nameDef]'s career quickly degenerated into a circus of misguided ideas, deals gone wrong, and desperate, failed PR stunts.</desc>
	</GameDeveloper95>
</BackstoryTranslations>